<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.advisor">
    <category name="zoo.advisor.buttons">
      <item name="zoo.advisor.buttons.1"><![CDATA[Animal species]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.buttons.2"><![CDATA[Satisfaction]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.buttons.3"><![CDATA[Decoration]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.buttons.4"><![CDATA[Animal breeding]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.buttons.5"><![CDATA[Trash]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.advisor.descriptions">
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.1.A"><![CDATA[Great! No one can really complain about the lack of variety in your zoo. Keep it up!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.1.B"><![CDATA[Visitors like it when they can admire a large variety of animals in a zoo. You have %currentspecies% of different species, that's a lot! Check out the shop, you'll find at least %missingspecies% more in there.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.1.C"><![CDATA[Zoogoers want to see as many animals as possible. But your zoo is worth it. You currently own %currentspecies% of animals. You can find at least %missingspecies% more species in the pet shop.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.1.D"><![CDATA[Anyone who goes to the zoo wants to see animals! Your zoo could have an even bigger selection: You currently have %currentspecies% animal species. The pet shop offers at least %missingspecies% more.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.1.E"><![CDATA[Oh! There aren't many species of animals in your zoo. Visitors can admire %currentspecies% species, which they can handle fairly quickly. Quickly buy at least %missingspecies% more animals in the Zoo Shop.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.2.A"><![CDATA[Your animals are completely satisfied. You are an exemplary zoo director.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.2.B"><![CDATA[You are taking great care of your animals, but look, some of them deserve even more attention.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.2.C"><![CDATA[Oh! Your animals are a little bored. Wouldn't you like to play with them a little, feed them or give them water? That would be great for them and they would be really happy again!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.2.D"><![CDATA[Oh my! Your animals are sad because you haven't been taking care of them. Play with them a little! Some food and water will also cheer them up. Then your zoo will shine again and delight visitors!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.2.E"><![CDATA[Oh no! Your animals are hungry and thirsty! Come on, take care of them! Once they are fed and the enclosures are cleaned, it will be fun to play with the animals again!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.3.A"><![CDATA[Wow! Your zoo is beautifully decorated! There's so much for visitors to see. Keep it up!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.3.B"><![CDATA[Great! You've decorated your zoo nicely! Check out the zoo shop: you'll find lots of other nice and funny decorations there. Your visitors love a change!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.3.C"><![CDATA[Your zoo is nice, but it could use a little more change! You can find lots of nice and funny decorations in the zoo shop.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.3.D"><![CDATA[Practical and functional, but a bit boring. More decorations will be appreciated by visitors. Let everyone see that you can show more!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.3.E"><![CDATA[Your zoo could use a little more decoration. Delight your visitors with new striking decorations.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.4.A"><![CDATA[So many cute babies! You really have golden hands and your animals have so many offspring. Great!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.4.B"><![CDATA[Thumbnail headlines about the zoo's baby animals draw visitors in. But every zoo director is always looking for ways to improve. Check it out: You can currently raise %missingbabies% more baby animals.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.4.C"><![CDATA[News of the zoo's new additions are spreading far and wide. Visitors love the little clumsy cubs! Currently, you can raise %missingbabies% more cubs.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.4.D"><![CDATA[Your zoo could use more offspring. Check out: %missingbabies% of couples are currently looking for a baby. Try to breed!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.4.E"><![CDATA[There's a lot of concern about your offspring at your zoo: %missingbabies% of couples are currently expecting a baby. Try to breed and delight your visitors with the sight of your clumsy cubs.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.5.A"><![CDATA[Great, your zoo is looking great! And the visitors love it. Keep it up!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.5.B"><![CDATA[You're doing well, but your zoo would be even nicer if you cleaned up the rest of the trash.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.5.C"><![CDATA[The trash in your zoo is slowly piling up. At last, clean it up.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.5.D"><![CDATA[There's a lot of trash lying around in your zoo. You should definitely tidy up and clean everything up.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.descriptions.5.E"><![CDATA[Your zoo is drowning in trash! Clear the mountains of trash from the paths and empty the bins.]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.advisor.help">
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.1"><![CDATA[In the "Animal Species" category, you can see whether all possible animal species are represented in your zoo.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.2"><![CDATA[The "Satisfaction" category shows how happy your animals are currently.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.3"><![CDATA[In the "Decoration" category, you can see whether the decorations in your zoo are attractive to visitors.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.4"><![CDATA[Visitors love cute babies! The "Animal Breeding" item will show you the level of success of your breeding.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.5"><![CDATA[The "Trash" item will show you if your zoo is clean or if visitors are tripping over mountains of trash.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.6"><![CDATA[Use keys 1 to 7 to get to the store faster.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.7"><![CDATA[Use the letters Q, W, E and R to move (W), flip (E), sell (R) or change game mode (Q) items.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.8"><![CDATA[Remember to use a secure password that you don't share with anyone!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.9"><![CDATA[You can turn game tips and various other features such as visitors, background effects, and sound effects on or off to make the game run faster on weaker computers.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.10"><![CDATA[Buy Zoo Dollars at the bank. You can sometimes get them as a reward for completing daily tasks. You can also get them if you level up enough.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.11"><![CDATA[There will also be promotions with bonus codes every now and then, so keep an eye out for official announcements in the forum.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.12"><![CDATA[Your animals can get sick by accident. The better you take care of them, the longer they will stay healthy. But if your animal is not sick, you can't even give it an injection.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.13"><![CDATA[Your animals feel great in all enclosures. And it doesn't matter which enclosure you put them in.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.14"><![CDATA[You cannot currently move any animals to other enclosures.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.15"><![CDATA[If you sell the enclosure, you also sell the animal in it.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.16"><![CDATA[There are two types of meerkats in the game - normal and the gray meerkat Beda. Beda only appears during certain events and can only be purchased on special days.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.17"><![CDATA[If you click on "adopt for zoodollars", you are 100% sure of a new addition and you don't have to wait for it.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.18"><![CDATA[You can save your ZooMumba friends to your address book. Unfortunately, you cannot invite any neighbors at the moment.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.19"><![CDATA[The more stores you own, the more zoogros you earn.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.20"><![CDATA[Don't have time? Then hire assistants. Remember that assistants only work when you click on them (they don't work automatically).]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.21"><![CDATA[If you hire a cashier, Kešík, you will increase your income.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.22"><![CDATA[Using assistants is worth it: you will gain more experience points.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.23"><![CDATA[If you have all the assistants, you activate David's representative - he can make all the assistants work with just one click.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.24"><![CDATA[The more waste you sort at the zoo, the less of it will end up on the streets.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.25"><![CDATA[Buy a male and a female of the same species and you'll soon have cute babies in the zoo.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.26"><![CDATA[You can only store a certain amount of admission money in the main building, so make sure to collect it regularly.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.27"><![CDATA[In order to make a profit from your buildings, they must always be connected by a path. How else would visitors be able to reach them?]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.28"><![CDATA[Keep your eyes open: From time to time, special animals or items appear in the store that you can only purchase for a limited time.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.29"><![CDATA[Feed your animals superfood, they will stay full longer!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.advisor.help.30"><![CDATA[Oh! Are your animals sick? Give them super drugs and they'll be as healthy as fish again!]]></item>
    </category>
  </category>
</language>
