<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.genus">
    <category name="zoo.window.shopAnimalInfo">
      <item name="zoo.genus.title.1"><![CDATA[Arakanga Macaw]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.1"><![CDATA[These cheerful parrots are very chatty! Always keep them as a pair or group. Visitors love these smart guys with their brightly colored feathers!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.title.4"><![CDATA[Pink flamingo]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.4"><![CDATA[These beautiful pink animals attract the attention of visitors. Their main food is plankton, but they also enjoy fresh fish. A treat for sweet-toothed birds!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.title.5"><![CDATA[Mountain zebra]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.5"><![CDATA[Stripes, stripes, stripes everywhere! It's mind-boggling! In a world full of zebra stripes, it's good camouflage, but in our part of the world, zebras look quite comical. Zebras definitely belong in every zoo, so don't let that fool you!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.titel.9"><![CDATA[Rhinoceros]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.9"><![CDATA[These large pachyderms are loners. It's no wonder they wear such horns! Despite their powerful appearance, they rarely engage in fights. However, it's best to keep only a male and a female together.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.title.12"><![CDATA[Amphibian hippopotamus]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.12"><![CDATA[On land they look like lumbering colossuses, but appearances are deceiving. Be careful not to anger them, as once they start running, it is not advisable to get in their way. Fortunately, they are easy-going animals if their privacy is respected.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.title.13"><![CDATA[Marbled giraffe]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.13"><![CDATA[Always high in the clouds! Giraffes reach the sweetest fruits right up to the tops of the trees. It's no wonder then that the trees are well-grazed. With their long necks, they reach very high and they like to eat the young green leaves the most!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.title.32"><![CDATA[Arctic reindeer]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.genus.text.32"><![CDATA[Reindeer live in herds far north. Even in the harsh Arctic conditions, the fearless reindeer find a place to survive.]]></item>
    </category>
  </category>
</language>
