<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo">
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_1"><![CDATA[Gravel road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_1"><![CDATA[This gravel path connects your zoo enclosures. A quality network of paths helps your visitors find their way and leads them to all the enclosures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_2"><![CDATA[Blue and white sidewalk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_2"><![CDATA[This blue and white cobblestone path not only looks great, but it's also a great surface for strollers, scooters and roller skates. Smooth movement and quality fun, that's great!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_3"><![CDATA[Sand road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_3"><![CDATA[There are rarely paved roads in the steppe. You want your zoo to resemble the wild!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_4"><![CDATA[Pink and white sidewalk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_4"><![CDATA[How lovely: This stone path made of precious pink mosaic stones is something truly special. The perfect catwalk for visitors in high heels.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_5"><![CDATA[Black and white sidewalk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_5"><![CDATA[Black and white precious stones in the form of a mosaic beautifully line this path. They are worked with great care and become a jewel of your zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_6"><![CDATA[The rocky road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_6"><![CDATA[Just like in the wild, small tufts of grass grow from the gaps between the stones. Not for the pedantic, but nature lovers will certainly enjoy it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_7"><![CDATA[Pebble path]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_7"><![CDATA[This gravel path looks nice and I'm sure no one will slip on it. Safe and pretty, what more could you want?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_8"><![CDATA[Dirt road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_8"><![CDATA[Dirt paths are popular in Africa. They add authenticity to your zoo and will make many animals feel at home.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_9"><![CDATA[Waterway]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_9"><![CDATA[Splash, splash, splash! Put on your rubber boots, inflate your rubber boat and grab a rubber duck - there will be a lot of water on this trip!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_10"><![CDATA[Ice road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_10"><![CDATA[Yay! An ice road - that's going to be fun! Your visitors will have fun sliding down the frozen road. Be careful, it's not salted!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_11"><![CDATA[Savannah Road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_11"><![CDATA[A well-trodden path winds through the savannah, making it ideal for searching for tracks as on a safari.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_12"><![CDATA[Desert road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_12"><![CDATA[Under the scorching heat of the sun, sand blows across the desert, obliterating any traces.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_13"><![CDATA[Stone path]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_13"><![CDATA[This path is quite bumpy. There are large stones and boulders on it, so good footwear is a must. Be careful not to fall!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_14"><![CDATA[Tundra Trail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_14"><![CDATA[Your visitors will need a compass on this trail, but it is also wise to stick to the beaten path.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_15"><![CDATA[Snow road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_15"><![CDATA[Sticky snow lies on the snow path, which your visitors will trudge along in their warm boots. Everything is so beautiful here!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_16"><![CDATA[Desert trail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_16"><![CDATA[In the wilderness, it's best to stay on the road. There are toxins and waste everywhere. Rubber boots with good soles are a must!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_17"><![CDATA[Alpine route]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_17"><![CDATA[This hiking trail will take you up and down through the Alps. Good shoes with solid ankle support will protect you from slipping!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_18"><![CDATA[Cave path]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_18"><![CDATA[Keep your eyes open so you don't slip. Maybe you'll spot a glittering grain of gold among the stones.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_19"><![CDATA[Forest path]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_19"><![CDATA[On rainy days this path can be a bit muddy, but in the summer the forest is absolutely idyllic.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_20"><![CDATA[Coastal road]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_20"><![CDATA[Walking barefoot on sparkling sand, shells, seaweed and occasionally some starfish is very beneficial for your health!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_21"><![CDATA[Magical trail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_21"><![CDATA[The bright blue trail, which is out of this world, may seem scary, but it is also adventurous. Where does it lead?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_22"><![CDATA[Sugar Land Trail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_22"><![CDATA[Crumb! Oops! Did you step on a candy? Be careful, there are chewing gums on the way! How beautifully colorful it is here!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_23"><![CDATA[Bamboo forest trail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_23"><![CDATA[The fog drifts through a vast, almost impenetrable bamboo forest. The tapping of a woodpecker can be heard in the distance. Simply idyllic!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_24"><![CDATA[Forest trail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_24"><![CDATA[If you don't want to swing from vine to vine in this jungle, you can walk along this well-trodden path. Be careful: From time to time, a snake or spider may cross the path.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_25"><![CDATA[The path through the swamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_25"><![CDATA[Your visitors should remember to stay on the right path in the swamp. One wrong step and they'll fall into the mud!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.titel_26"><![CDATA[Wooden platform]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopRoadsInfo.text_26"><![CDATA[There's nothing better than walking along a wooden pier and hearing the creaking of a ship's deck. Your visitors will have a true coastal experience.]]></item>
  </category>
</language>
