<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.speciesItems">
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.1"><![CDATA[Parrot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.1"><![CDATA[Some parrots are known to be quite talkative. Some of them even speak in complete sentences.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.4"><![CDATA[Flamingo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.4"><![CDATA[Flamingos don't swim on lakes like ducks. However, they do like to dip their long legs into the water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.5"><![CDATA[Zebra]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.5"><![CDATA[What do zebras and snowflakes have in common? The stripes on each zebra's body create a unique pattern. Like snowflakes, no two zebras are the same.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.7"><![CDATA[Penguin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.7"><![CDATA[Penguins are seabirds even though they can't fly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.8"><![CDATA[Kangaroo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.8"><![CDATA[Kangaroos live in Australia and hop across the steppes at speeds of up to 50 km/h.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.9"><![CDATA[Rhinoceros]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.9"><![CDATA[Despite their impressive appearance, rhinos are calm and shy animals. But that changes if they feel threatened - once they get moving, they become an unstoppable avalanche!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.10"><![CDATA[Chimpanzee]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.10"><![CDATA[Chimpanzees love to climb trees, but they also like to catch things that fall from trees.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.11"><![CDATA[Lion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.11"><![CDATA[Lions are the second largest felines in the world after tigers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.12"><![CDATA[Hippopotamus]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.12"><![CDATA[Even though a hippopotamus weighs as much as a small truck at up to 4.5 tons, it prefers to spend its day doing nothing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.13"><![CDATA[Giraffe]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.13"><![CDATA[With their long necks, giraffes can reach high treetops. Their favorite are acacia trees.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.14"><![CDATA[Elephant]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.14"><![CDATA[An elephant takes eight to ten liters of water into its trunk when drinking.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.16"><![CDATA[Panda]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.16"><![CDATA[The giant panda is a black and white bear native to China.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.18"><![CDATA[Hare]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.18"><![CDATA[Hares live in a variety of areas - from deserts through forests, to cold polar regions.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.21"><![CDATA[Giant tortoise]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.21"><![CDATA[Tortoises and turtles are reptiles. They most often live near or in the water. The largest turtles are water turtles.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.27"><![CDATA[Llama]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.27"><![CDATA[Llamas are known for their kind and gentle nature. They love people and are very curious.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.28"><![CDATA[Koala]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.28"><![CDATA[Koala bears are marsupials, so they are not bears in the true sense of the word.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.31"><![CDATA[Wolf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.31"><![CDATA[Wolves live in packs and have their own fixed hunting grounds. Before humans began hunting wolves, they were the most widespread predator in the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.32"><![CDATA[Reindeer]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.32"><![CDATA[Reindeer, also known as caribou in North America, are among the northernmost large mammals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.43"><![CDATA[White pigeon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.43"><![CDATA[The white dove is a symbol of peace.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.45"><![CDATA[Peacock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.45"><![CDATA[Peacocks are impressive exotic birds. They roam freely in many zoos and parks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.47"><![CDATA[Giant scorpion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.47"><![CDATA[This species of scorpion is active mainly at night. It is a predator that likes to ambush its victims. However, it only uses venom if it fails to catch the prey with its claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.57"><![CDATA[Alligator]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.57"><![CDATA[Alligators belong to the crocodilian family. They are slightly calmer than crocodiles themselves. This, however, doesn't mean they can't attack unexpectedly. Their favorite place is a mudflat in the sun.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.63"><![CDATA[Lynx]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.63"><![CDATA[The lynx has large paws. This prevents it from falling into the snow in winter.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.65"><![CDATA[Toucan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.65"><![CDATA[Toucans are known for their long and brightly colored beaks. They live in subtropical and tropical rainforests.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.76"><![CDATA[Komodo dragon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.76"><![CDATA[The young are very good climbers: they forage in trees and hide high in the treetops and bask in the sun. As they grow older, they become larger and keep more to the ground.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.115"><![CDATA[Slow loris]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.115"><![CDATA[Not so fast! Slow climbing is an Olympic discipline for the loris. It veeery slowly moves one foot after the other.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.117"><![CDATA[Rake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.117"><![CDATA[Vultures are very shy animals and live in large burrows that they create themselves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.118"><![CDATA[Donkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.118"><![CDATA[Yaaaaa!! Under pressure, the donkey stops and doesn't move a bit.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.119"><![CDATA[Eagle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.119"><![CDATA[With its broad wings, this raptor is an imposing hunter that soars majestically through the air.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.125"><![CDATA[Jaguar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.125"><![CDATA[The jaguar lives in South and Central America, but its range used to be much larger. It is a welcome exotic sight in your zoo, which visitors will be very happy to see.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.126"><![CDATA[Hummingbird]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.126"><![CDATA[Hummingbirds are the smallest birds in the world. Like little fairies, they fly through the air and use their long tongues to suck nectar from flowers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.130"><![CDATA[Platypus]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.130"><![CDATA[A mammal, bird, and reptile in one: as an egg-laying mammal, the platypus surprises scientists and animal lovers alike.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.131"><![CDATA[Ant eater]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.131"><![CDATA[Thanks to its long snout, the anteater is a specialist in catching insects - it uses a long tongue to reach even the deepest hiding places.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.132"><![CDATA[Green iguana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.132"><![CDATA[These lizards love to bask in the sun in groups! At the slightest sign of danger, they can blend in with their surroundings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.139"><![CDATA[Mandrill]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.139"><![CDATA[The male's distinctive facial coloring serves as a signal of leadership in the mandrill group. The louder the call, the more distinctive the facial coloring.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.140"><![CDATA[Raven]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.140"><![CDATA[Ravens are very smart animals and are a symbol of wisdom and intelligence.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.141"><![CDATA[Tarantula]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.141"><![CDATA[This fearsome climber is very hairy. It is also extremely venomous; keep your distance from it!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.145"><![CDATA[Puffins]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.145"><![CDATA[These little friends are commonly found on the North Atlantic coast. Their call is a loud growl, similar to a muffled chainsaw.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.149"><![CDATA[Squirrel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.149"><![CDATA[Squirrels often can't find their way back to their looted treasures, thus contributing to the preservation of the forest. Why? Because the nuts are starting to sprout!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.150"><![CDATA[Arctic fox]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.150"><![CDATA[Arctic foxes live in family groups, with pairs remaining together for life. They breed in dens, which sometimes have complex tunnel systems.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.154"><![CDATA[Seal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.154"><![CDATA[Seals are great divers, even though they have to come to the surface for air. Their torpedo-shaped bodies allow them to shoot through the water with ease.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.155"><![CDATA[Kinkajju]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.155"><![CDATA[The kinkajou is a nocturnal animal that sleeps curled up in a hollow tree during the day. Its eyes are very sensitive to light, so it covers them with its paws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.159"><![CDATA[Ferret]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.159"><![CDATA[Ferrets are probably descendants of the polecat. It is not known whether it originally came from Europe or North America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.163"><![CDATA[Margay]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.163"><![CDATA[The Margay spends most of its time in the treetops and is rarely seen on the ground. It can be spotted while hunting.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.164"><![CDATA[Stork]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.164"><![CDATA[High up in their nests, storks have a great view of the surroundings. Once they have built a nest, they live there with their young.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.165"><![CDATA[Emu]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.165"><![CDATA[The emu cannot fly, but it has long legs that allow it to escape quickly. It grows up to two meters tall, which helps keep it safe from predators.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.166"><![CDATA[Wildebeest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.166"><![CDATA[The wildebeest migration is one of the most famous forms of animal migration. They search for food in the Masai Mara reserve, but crocodiles also claim the area.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.167"><![CDATA[Jackal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.167"><![CDATA[These agile runners are wild dogs. They are monogamous, meaning they mate with only one partner for life.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.168"><![CDATA[Annelied anteater]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.168"><![CDATA[The anteater uses its pointed snout and keen sense of smell to find food, running from one termite nest to another.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.169"><![CDATA[Falcon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.169"><![CDATA[Falcons search for prey while flying. They can track their prey over long distances from the air.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.170"><![CDATA[White-bearded marmoset]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.170"><![CDATA[In the wild, these monkeys live in large groups, with only the dominant females capable of reproduction.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.173"><![CDATA[Mustang]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.173"><![CDATA[Wild mustangs were widely used by brave cowboys and Indians.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.174"><![CDATA[Kiwi]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.174"><![CDATA[Once hatched, kiwi chicks look like miniature versions of their parents. They are relatively mobile and mature, and can leave the nest on their own at night.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.175"><![CDATA[Butterfly]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.175"><![CDATA[Butterflies have beautiful antennae that they use for smell, taste, temperature detection, and sometimes even feeling.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.176"><![CDATA[Otter]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.176"><![CDATA[Otters live near water, but they also live on land. They are expert divers and can hold their breath underwater for up to 8 minutes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.180"><![CDATA[Mole]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.180"><![CDATA[Some people believe that the origin of the word "mole" comes from Crete. But this is a mistake!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.181"><![CDATA[Scottish Highland Cattle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.181"><![CDATA[This sturdy breed hails from Scotland and the Hebrides. Their long, shaggy coat protects them from the wind. Wow!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.182"><![CDATA[Dodo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.182"><![CDATA[This is sensational! Even though this bird has been extinct for centuries, the dodo is back in the zoo! But be careful, it gets fat pretty quickly. Don't overfeed it!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.183"><![CDATA[Vulture]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.183"><![CDATA[When vultures fly in circles, it means they are waiting for the carcass of a dead animal. Vultures are the most famous scavengers!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.187"><![CDATA[Bearded dragon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.187"><![CDATA[These Australian lizards are found across most of their continent. They live in trees and bushes, basking in the desert sun or hiding in the bushes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.188"><![CDATA[Pangolin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.188"><![CDATA[Pangolins are nocturnal animals that live on the ground or in trees. They love insects and can close their ears and nose when they poke their nose into an insect nest.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.189"><![CDATA[Moufflon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.189"><![CDATA[Mouflon herds do not change their territories often. And when they do, they travel one after the other in a long line.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.194"><![CDATA[Mangalica]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.194"><![CDATA[The Mangalica, also known as the "wool pig," is a breed of pig originating in Hungary. It was very popular from 1890 to 1950. Today, the breed is considered rare.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.195"><![CDATA[Puli]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.195"><![CDATA[The Puli is a brave and determined dog. Hungarian shepherds love them for their excellent herding skills. Their coat can get a bit smelly when it gets wet. Yuck!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.196"><![CDATA[Quokka]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.196"><![CDATA[Quokkas are nocturnal animals. They hide in the undergrowth during the day. They have adapted to life on Rottnest Island, approaching tourists and begging for food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.197"><![CDATA[Long-tailed hawk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.197"><![CDATA[The tailed ksukol is a nocturnal creature and often lives in different parts of its territory. Each ksukol builds up to 7 nests and travels between them. It is a vagrant!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.198"><![CDATA[Werewolf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.198"><![CDATA[If the myths are true, the werewolf is half-human, half-wolf. They inspire fear and hatred from humans, but in many cases they are pitiful creatures, condemned to howl at the moon.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.199"><![CDATA[Turkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.199"><![CDATA[Turkeys grow up to 1 meter tall. The males have beautiful feathers, but the females look plain.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.200"><![CDATA[Whiz]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.200"><![CDATA[Marmots live in colonies and greet each other by rubbing their noses. If there is a threat nearby, they put their heads together and whistle loudly as a warning to others.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.201"><![CDATA[Weasel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.201"><![CDATA[The common weasel is shy and usually active in the dark. It likes to crawl into hollow trees, cracks in rocks or into the burrows of other animals. It even snuggles up in old mouse nests. Very smart!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.202"><![CDATA[Huskies]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.202"><![CDATA[Huskies are always very warm because they have two layers of fur. Beneath the outer hairs, the husky has a soft undercoat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.203"><![CDATA[Hoatzin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.203"><![CDATA[Hoatzins are extremely social and live in large groups. They enjoy the sun and rain in the high treetops. They also like to spread their wings and enjoy life. Cute stinkers!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.204"><![CDATA[Manuel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.204"><![CDATA[There are fewer than 50,000 of them left worldwide, making these cats an endangered species. Luckily for you, you can admire them in your zoo. Take good care of them and help them reproduce!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.205"><![CDATA[Sphinx]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.205"><![CDATA[Although it is not very visible, Sphynx cats are not naked. Their fur is very soft and light.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.206"><![CDATA[Desert fox]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.206"><![CDATA[A desert fox is born with reddish fur, but the older it gets, the lighter its fur becomes. The fur of old foxes is almost white!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.207"><![CDATA[Clouded leopard]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.207"><![CDATA[Have you ever heard a big cat purr? If so, it was probably a clouded leopard! These big cats are said to be related to small cats. But that's just a rumor. Very little research has been done to date, all we know is that it is shy and lives in the branches of trees.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.208"><![CDATA[Red-bellied Ibis]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.208"><![CDATA[This gregarious bird lives in large groups of several hundred animals. It is difficult to tell the females from the males because they look almost the same!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.209"><![CDATA[Pug]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.209"><![CDATA[The Pug was bred in China from similar dog breeds 2,000 years ago. The Pug was always considered an imperial dog and only the emperor could pet it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.210"><![CDATA[Cheetah]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.210"><![CDATA[The cheetah has two black stripes on its head that look like "tears" running from its eyes down to its muzzle.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.211"><![CDATA[Kahau-nosed]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.211"><![CDATA[Due to deforestation of its natural habitat, the kahau has become an endangered species.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.212"><![CDATA[Wallis Black-nosed Sheep]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.212"><![CDATA[The cute Welsh Black Nose Sheep are completely covered in wool. You'd love to hug and pet them, wouldn't you?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.213"><![CDATA[Dik-dik]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.213"><![CDATA[Dik-diks are monogamous throughout their lives. Pairs spend about two-thirds of their time together - how romantic. They watch over each other lovingly and always alert each other if there is any danger in sight.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.214"><![CDATA[Capybara]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.214"><![CDATA[Capybaras live near water. They have webbed feet and can submerge their heads almost completely underwater to avoid being seen by predators.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.215"><![CDATA[Madagascar Felsuma]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.215"><![CDATA[This dark green species of gecko has a reddish-brown stripe that extends from its nose to its eye and ear.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.216"><![CDATA[Spectacled bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.216"><![CDATA[The face of a spectacled bear is marked with white or cream stripes that run from its forehead across its cheeks and down its neck. It looks like it's wearing glasses, right?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.217"><![CDATA[Bandicoot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.217"><![CDATA[These playful, nocturnal marsupials will bring the special charm of the Australian outback right to your zoo!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.218"><![CDATA[Southern cassowary]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.218"><![CDATA[The southern cassowary is also called the helmeted cassowary because of its helmet-shaped head.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.219"><![CDATA[Maned dog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.219"><![CDATA[The maned dog is only a distant relative of the typical wolf. Alongside the forest dog and false foxes, the maned dog represents the third lineage of dogs in South America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.220"><![CDATA[Anaconda]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.220"><![CDATA[A crawling, voracious anaconda will draw the attention of both your visitors and other zoo animals!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.221"><![CDATA[White-cheeked tern]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.221"><![CDATA[The White-faced Owl is a medium-sized owl with beautiful large plumes and a white face edged in black.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.222"><![CDATA[Squirrel-like roller]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.222"><![CDATA[These cheerful monkeys jump from tree to tree. Their tails help to keep them balanced. They are like squirrels!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.223"><![CDATA[Desert warthog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.223"><![CDATA[Who would have thought: The common warthog has a long mane that runs from the neck across the entire back. When in danger, the mane bristles.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.224"><![CDATA[Striped hyena]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.224"><![CDATA[Striped hyena has the longest mane of them all. It's covered with stripes, that's why the name!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.225"><![CDATA[Canada lynx]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.225"><![CDATA[The Canada lynx has long tufts on its ears. These tufts are actually black fur. Don't they look cute?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.226"><![CDATA[Kingfisher]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.226"><![CDATA[Kingfishers have an elaborate way of understanding each other. Older birds communicate with younger ones by responding to their calls. Loud beeping sounds fill the entire forest.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.227"><![CDATA[Ringtail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.227"><![CDATA[The fluffy and bushy tail has black and white stripes. The ferret cat belongs to the bear family and has little in common with cats.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.228"><![CDATA[Praying mantis]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.228"><![CDATA[This insect uses the front pair of limbs for capturing its prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.229"><![CDATA[Silkie]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.229"><![CDATA[Silky hens do not fly because their feathers are not connected and do not form a single wing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.230"><![CDATA[Lion-tailed macaque]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.230"><![CDATA[Macaques are among the most endangered primates. Their population is threatened by the gradual destruction of their habitat and they avoid contact with humans.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.231"><![CDATA[Muskox]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.231"><![CDATA[Wherever there are musk oxen, there must be a musk ox wave. This soft wool flies everywhere and the birds on the tundra use it to stuff their nests.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.232"><![CDATA[Dingo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.232"><![CDATA[Dingoes are nocturnal animals. During that time they either hunt their prey or explore their \nsurroundings looking for animals of the same species.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.233"><![CDATA[Pelican]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.233"><![CDATA[Pelicans are very good flyers. They can fly up to 24 hours, during which they fly up to 500 km.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.234"><![CDATA[Wombat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.234"><![CDATA[Wombats have the driest feces of any mammal, and their droppings are cube-shaped. Every morning, they scatter them around their den to mark their territory.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.235"><![CDATA[The Nose]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.235"><![CDATA[The muzzle, chin and neck are usually white. It also has a very cute nose.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.236"><![CDATA[Cormorant\n]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.236"><![CDATA[Outside their nests, cormorants don't make much noise. However, in their colonies they are quite noisy, competing with each other with loud guttural calls of chro-chro-chro or chroho-chroho-chroho.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.237"><![CDATA[Dragonfly]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.237"><![CDATA[Larvae of the green shiner grow in water. No wonder their homes are near the water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.238"><![CDATA[Ocelot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.238"><![CDATA[Ocelots come from South America and resemble a miniature leopard with the facial features of a domestic cat. The artist Salvador Dalí had one like this as a pet.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.239"><![CDATA[Oystercatcher]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.239"><![CDATA[If sheep or other oystercatchers approach its young, the oystercatcher will start to squeak and whistle loudly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.240"><![CDATA[Wild yak]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.240"><![CDATA[Thanks to its hump and slightly vertical back, it can walk even on more difficult terrain.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.241"><![CDATA[Dolphin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.241"><![CDATA[There are 40 species of dolphins in the world. Among the better known are the bottlenose dolphin and the killer whale.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.242"><![CDATA[Rajka]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.242"><![CDATA[The male first makes noises to attract attention, then shows off his beautiful feathers. What a beauty!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.243"><![CDATA[Seagull]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.243"><![CDATA[Most seagulls live near the coast and are used to strong winds. Thanks to their long, pointed wings, they can fly in any wind and weather.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.244"><![CDATA[Cape ladder]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.244"><![CDATA[The Cape Ladder Crab has black spots and stripes on its nose and under its eyes, which make it a real beauty!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.245"><![CDATA[Elephant shrew]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.245"><![CDATA[Bércoun has an excellent sense of smell and can smell everything that blows under his nose!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.246"><![CDATA[Banded mongoose]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.246"><![CDATA[The banded mongoose eats mainly insects, small reptiles and birds. It uses its sense of smell to find prey in the ground and in trees, then picks it up with its long claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.247"><![CDATA[Crab]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.247"><![CDATA[There are approximately 5,000 species of crabs in the world, but 500 of them, including the hermit crab and the king crab, are not "true crabs."]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.248"><![CDATA[Kashmiri goat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.248"><![CDATA[There are up to 20 species of Kashmir goats in the world. They come in different colors and shades. But they are all fluffy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.249"><![CDATA[Fruit bat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.249"><![CDATA[Fruit bats are the largest species of bats, with a wingspan of up to 1.7 meters. Their heads can be up to 40 cm long.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.250"><![CDATA[Sperm whale]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.250"><![CDATA[The sperm whale has very distinctive shapes. Its square head is up to one third of its entire length!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.251"><![CDATA[Dromedary]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.251"><![CDATA[The main features of the dromedary are a long curved neck, a single hump, and long hair on the neck, shoulders, and hump.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.252"><![CDATA[Blue-footed booby]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.252"><![CDATA[The blue color on his feet is caused by eating a certain type of fresh fish every day. The brighter his feet, the healthier he is.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.253"><![CDATA[Greater kudu]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.253"><![CDATA[The greater kudu is a species of antelope with impressive spiral horns, characteristic stripes on its trunk, and a thick beard.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.254"><![CDATA[Spotted skunk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.254"><![CDATA[The spotted cat is known as the eastern cat, even though it is not a feline, but a marsupial!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.255"><![CDATA[Giant squid]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.255"><![CDATA[Although various stories have been told about the octopus for centuries, the first photograph of the octopus is from 2004 and the first video from 2012.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.256"><![CDATA[Blue marlin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.256"><![CDATA[The blue marlin is one of the largest fish in the world, reaching up to 5 meters in length! It is a solitary fish, but can also be found in pairs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.257"><![CDATA[Clownfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.257"><![CDATA[The clownfish lives in symbiosis with an anemone, where it also lays its eggs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.258"><![CDATA[Jellyfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.258"><![CDATA[Jellyfish are invertebrate animals that have bell-shaped or flattened shapes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.259"><![CDATA[Four-toothed]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.259"><![CDATA[Quadrupeds are known for being able to inflate their bodies to scare away predators.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.260"><![CDATA[Kraken]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.260"><![CDATA[The Kraken is a legendary sea monster that has appeared in various stories for centuries.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.266"><![CDATA[Seahorse]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.266"><![CDATA[The seahorse is very easy to recognize - it has a distinctively shaped head, a segmented bony body, a curled tail and an upright posture.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.267"><![CDATA[Jib]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.267"><![CDATA[The killer whale is also known as the killer whale, mainly due to its predatory nature. However, this name is incorrect, as killer whales are not whales, but dolphins.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.269"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.269"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.270"><![CDATA[Cockatoo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.270"><![CDATA[Most cockatoos are medium or large in size, but one species is much smaller.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.271"><![CDATA[Bonobo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.271"><![CDATA[Bonobos are closely related to humans, sharing up to 98% of their DNA!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.272"><![CDATA[Owl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.272"><![CDATA[There are around 200 species of owls found all over the world. They vary in size, but all have similar shapes and features.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.273"><![CDATA[Manta]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.273"><![CDATA[There are two species – the larger one, Alfredi, is found in the Indian and Pacific Oceans and the eastern Atlantic, while the smaller one, Birostris, lives in tropical oceans.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.274"><![CDATA[Sun bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.274"><![CDATA[The Malayan sun bear lives in the tropical forests of Southeast Asia. It loves honey so much that it is nicknamed the honey bear.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.275"><![CDATA[Kakapo owl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.275"><![CDATA[These large flightless birds from New Zealand are critically endangered. There are about 150 left.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.276"><![CDATA[Beautiful bird of paradise]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.276"><![CDATA[These small South Asian birds are known for their colorful plumage and elaborate courtship rituals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setName.277"><![CDATA[Arrow frog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.speciesItems.setInfo.277"><![CDATA[Not all of these brightly colored frogs are poisonous!]]></item>
  </category>
</language>
