<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.collectableItems">
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.3"><![CDATA[Wild meadow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.3"><![CDATA[If no one takes care of a "transitional meadow" for a long time, a wild forest will soon grow on it again.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.4"><![CDATA[Flowers]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.4"><![CDATA[In spring, the meadows turn into a sea of ​​wildflowers. And your animals love them!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.5"><![CDATA[Stump]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.5"><![CDATA[A transitional meadow is created by clearing trees. Once the forest is gone, small grass shoots will first grow there.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.6"><![CDATA[Mushrooms]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.6"><![CDATA[Mushrooms are tasty mushrooms and grow, for example, in North America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.7"><![CDATA[Elfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.7"><![CDATA[The meadows are also often home to elves, who emerge from their hiding places at night. These shy but friendly creatures often share their homes with hares.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.8"><![CDATA[Icicles]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.8"><![CDATA[The sparkling icicles form in freezing temperatures. Of course, the warmth of the sun melts them again.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.9"><![CDATA[Popsicle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.9"><![CDATA[Few people know this, but penguins also like popsicles and sometimes steal them from tourists.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.10"><![CDATA[Ice cubes]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.10"><![CDATA[Ice cubes are the perfect way to cool down a hot drink. They provide refreshment on a hot summer day.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.11"><![CDATA[Skate]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.11"><![CDATA[Ice skating is an amazing sport. Historians believe that it was invented about 4,000 years ago. The Finns probably contributed to the invention.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.12"><![CDATA[Igloo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.12"><![CDATA[Igloo means house to the Eskimos, who are the original inhabitants of North America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.13"><![CDATA[Bamboo wings]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.13"><![CDATA[People have been making wings from bamboo for a long time. The lightweight yet strong material allows them to reach incredible heights.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.14"><![CDATA[Bamboo branch]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.14"><![CDATA[Bamboo is a collective name for several genera of woody grasses.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.15"><![CDATA[Gong]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.15"><![CDATA[The gong is a nice decoration for your bamboo garden. And that exotic sound... seems to be made to start meditation.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.16"><![CDATA[Asian statue]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.16"><![CDATA[An Asian-style statue will add an atmosphere of calm and peace to the bamboo garden.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.17"><![CDATA[Lampion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.17"><![CDATA[Hang a pretty lantern in your bamboo garden and brighten the night with a soft light.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.18"><![CDATA[Fruit fans]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.18"><![CDATA[Parrots like to eat seeds and nuts, but they will also enjoy fruit. It doesn't matter if it's fresh or dried, the main thing is that it's sweet.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.19"><![CDATA[Peru]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.19"><![CDATA[The jungles of the Amazon region of Peru are home to many parrots, and the rainforest provides them with an ideal habitat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.20"><![CDATA[Parrot's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.20"><![CDATA[Parrots actually have 4 claws. Two are in front and two in back. That way they won't fall off the branch even if they fall asleep.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.21"><![CDATA[Plush parrot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.21"><![CDATA[Parrots are very social and popular pets, but they need plenty of space to run around.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.22"><![CDATA[Blackjack]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.22"><![CDATA[Parrots are actually pirates who were transformed into colorful birds by evil magicians.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.23"><![CDATA[Whole grain fan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.23"><![CDATA[Hares are vegetarians. In addition to grains, they eat grass, herbs, lettuce, and colorful flowers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.24"><![CDATA[Portugal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.24"><![CDATA[European wild hares originally lived in Portugal, Spain and northwest Africa, but they have also reached Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.25"><![CDATA[Rabbit's foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.25"><![CDATA[Rabbit's feet are a symbol of good luck in many cultures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.26"><![CDATA[Plush hare]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.26"><![CDATA[Hares have been around for centuries. Fossils show that hare-like creatures lived in China 60 million years ago.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.27"><![CDATA[Color palette]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.27"><![CDATA[Once a year, the Easter Bunny arrives and hides chocolate and colored eggs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.28"><![CDATA[Fish fans]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.28"><![CDATA[Penguins are absolute gourmets. They prefer fish, but they also enjoy sea creatures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.29"><![CDATA[Antarctica]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.29"><![CDATA[The Subpolar Islands are home to one of the largest and heaviest penguins - the emperor penguin.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.30"><![CDATA[Penguin flipper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.30"><![CDATA[A penguin's walk on land looks clumsy, but in the water, the penguin is an agile swimmer and diver.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.31"><![CDATA[Plush penguin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.31"><![CDATA[Penguins are very social and competitive animals that often enjoy dancing underwater.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.32"><![CDATA[Tuxedo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.32"><![CDATA[Some people also call a tuxedo a penguin tailcoat because it strikingly resembles the appearance of a penguin.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.33"><![CDATA[Nutrition specialists]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.33"><![CDATA[Most turtles are omnivores, but some species specialize in only one type of food, such as jellyfish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.34"><![CDATA[Ecuador]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.34"><![CDATA[Elephant tortoises come from the Galapagos Islands, which belong to Ecuador in South America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.35"><![CDATA[Turtle's foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.35"><![CDATA[The feet of a water turtle have webbed feet between the toes, while those of land turtles have feet that are more like stumps.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.36"><![CDATA[Plush turtle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.36"><![CDATA[Baby giant tortoises communicate with their siblings while still in the egg. They simply bump into each other with their egg shells.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.37"><![CDATA[Swing]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.37"><![CDATA[Elephant tortoises can live to be over 100 years old, but they never grow a gray beard.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.38"><![CDATA[Steak lovers]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.38"><![CDATA[Lions, like all felines, are carnivores. They feed on wildebeest, zebras, and buffalo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.39"><![CDATA[Tanzania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.39"><![CDATA[Today they live mainly in national parks such as in Tanzania or on the coast of East Africa.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.40"><![CDATA[Lion's paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.40"><![CDATA[They command respect with their large paws and their claws firmly grip their prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.41"><![CDATA[Plush lion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.41"><![CDATA[White lions are actually completely normal lions, only their fur has been bleached by the sun.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.42"><![CDATA[Crown]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.42"><![CDATA[Although they inhabit savannas and steppes, they are often referred to as the "kings of the jungle".]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.43"><![CDATA[Grain lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.43"><![CDATA[Peacocks eat mostly grain and grains, but from time to time they will also eat flowers and the occasional beetle.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.44"><![CDATA[India]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.44"><![CDATA[In India, the peacock has been the national bird since 1963. Indians value these birds because they hunt poisonous cobras.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.45"><![CDATA[Peacock claws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.45"><![CDATA[Male peacocks are quite vain. They can spend hours combing their beautiful feathers with their claws. And finally they spread them out in all their glory.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.46"><![CDATA[Plush peacock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.46"><![CDATA[Peacock tail feathers are beautiful. In Greek mythology, peacock eyes are a symbol of the guardian Argus, who guarded Zeus's lover Io.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.47"><![CDATA[Mirror]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.47"><![CDATA[Peacocks can do some pretty cool stunts to arouse the interest of females, and females also like to flirt with them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.48"><![CDATA[Bamboo expert]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.48"><![CDATA[Pandas prefer to chew bamboo, especially the leaves and young twigs. Because they are large animals, they consume a lot of it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.49"><![CDATA[China]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.49"><![CDATA[The last wild pandas live in China, the largest country in the world. Unfortunately, there are only a few of these giant pandas left.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.50"><![CDATA[Panda paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.50"><![CDATA[Giant pandas have a crooked thumb. They use it to hold food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.51"><![CDATA[Plush panda]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.51"><![CDATA[Baby pandas are very small indeed. They weigh only 100 to 200 grams and are about 15-17 cm long.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.52"><![CDATA[Chopsticks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.52"><![CDATA[Clever pandas use bamboo sticks to skewer their food, just as people eat with chopsticks in Asia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.53"><![CDATA[Master of cuddling]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.53"><![CDATA[Sonia is a master of cuddling. Hire her and you'll get 12% more BZ for her services!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.54"><![CDATA[Bear cub]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.54"><![CDATA[The bear cubs would just cuddle all the time. Some of them don't want to leave their caregiver at all.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.55"><![CDATA[Top]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.55"><![CDATA[With her cheerfully spinning top, Soňa can cheer up even the grumpiest rhino.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.56"><![CDATA[Mouse toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.56"><![CDATA[Cute house cats like to chase toy mice, but lions prefer larger prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.57"><![CDATA[Elephant toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.57"><![CDATA[Monkeys are cheerful companions. They like to play with, for example, brightly colored wooden elephants.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.58"><![CDATA[Water area]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.58"><![CDATA[Water is essential for all living things. The human body alone contains over 60% water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.59"><![CDATA[Sailing boat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.59"><![CDATA[Sailboats are relatively small boats powered by wind.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.60"><![CDATA[Diving goggles]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.60"><![CDATA[If you look around in the water with diving goggles, everything will look a little bigger. This is due to the refraction of light.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.61"><![CDATA[Life buoy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.61"><![CDATA[Fish often mistake lifebuoys for donuts, so sometimes they bite into the rings a little.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.62"><![CDATA[Frog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.62"><![CDATA[During the larval stage, these amphibians still have a tail, but it later disappears.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.63"><![CDATA[Snow paddock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.63"><![CDATA[Animals that live in the snow enclosure have strikingly white fur.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.64"><![CDATA[Snowman]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.64"><![CDATA[Snowmen are best built from fresh snow; powder snow is too soft.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.65"><![CDATA[Toboggan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.65"><![CDATA[A sled can withstand a lot if it is lubricated with good wax.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.66"><![CDATA[Hat with pompom]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.66"><![CDATA[The hat with a pompom hides a small bell that can be used to attract birds to feed them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.67"><![CDATA[Snowflake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.67"><![CDATA[When the temperature is below freezing, water vapor forms snowflakes that resemble wads of cotton wool.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.68"><![CDATA[Swamp area]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.68"><![CDATA[Some plants need moist, mineral-rich soil to grow, which is ideal in swamps.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.69"><![CDATA[Waterlily]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.69"><![CDATA[Water lily seeds spend 2 to 3 days on the surface before sinking to the bottom and starting to germinate.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.70"><![CDATA[Firefly]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.70"><![CDATA[There are over 2,000 species of fireflies in the world. Most of them use light signals to find each other.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.71"><![CDATA[Strange flytrap]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.71"><![CDATA[The common flycatcher doesn't just like to catch tasty flies. It also treats itself to chewing gum.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.72"><![CDATA[Crazy canoe]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.72"><![CDATA[The canoe was probably invented 6,000 years ago.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.73"><![CDATA[Flamingo enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.73"><![CDATA[Adult flamingos are pink because they absorb special pigments called carotenoids with their food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.74"><![CDATA[USA flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.74"><![CDATA[The United States is home to 3 different species of flamingos.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.75"><![CDATA[Flamingo leg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.75"><![CDATA[Experts believe that flamingos stand on one leg to keep warm, as they spend a significant portion of the day in cold water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.76"><![CDATA[Plush flamingo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.76"><![CDATA[Flamingos are very social birds, often living in flocks of thousands.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.77"><![CDATA[Flamingo feather]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.77"><![CDATA[If you feed flamingos colorful jelly candies, their feathers will become more colorful.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.78"><![CDATA[Kangaroo enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.78"><![CDATA[Kangaroos are marsupials and carry their young in a pouch at all times after birth.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.79"><![CDATA[Flag of Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.79"><![CDATA[The Southern Cross is featured on the Australian flag.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.80"><![CDATA[Kangaroo paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.80"><![CDATA[Trackers can tell the color of a kangaroo's paw print by its color.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.81"><![CDATA[Plush kangaroo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.81"><![CDATA[The plush kangaroo is quite ticklish. Just squeeze its belly and it will immediately start laughing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.82"><![CDATA[Boxing glove]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.82"><![CDATA[A boxing kangaroo is a common motif and points to the animals' natural defensive reflex.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.83"><![CDATA[Lynx enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.83"><![CDATA[The lynx is the largest feline in Europe and, in addition to small animals, can also attack deer.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.84"><![CDATA[Russian flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.84"><![CDATA[Russian does not use the Latin alphabet for writing, but the Cyrillic alphabet (or another name for the Cyrillic alphabet).]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.85"><![CDATA[Lynx paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.85"><![CDATA[The lynx has a characteristic track in the snow - it lacks claw marks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.86"><![CDATA[Plush lynx]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.86"><![CDATA[Lynx cubs are breastfed until they are 5 months old.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.87"><![CDATA[Pocket lamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.87"><![CDATA[If a lamp is shone on a lynx, it immediately changes color.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.88"><![CDATA[Omnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.88"><![CDATA[Chimpanzees are omnivores and like fruits and nuts.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.89"><![CDATA[Primeval forest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.89"><![CDATA[They feel comfortable in the tropical rainforest in the Democratic Republic of Congo, just like elephants, lions and hyenas.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.90"><![CDATA[Chimpanzee footprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.90"><![CDATA[Chimpanzees are as good with their feet as they are with their hands. Their big toe is almost as big as their thumb.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.91"><![CDATA[Plush chimpanzee]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.91"><![CDATA[Chimpanzees live in large groups that are divided into subgroups. They include both solitary and social animals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.92"><![CDATA[Banana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.92"><![CDATA[Scientists agree that bananas are crooked because no one bent them in a straight line in the rainforest.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.93"><![CDATA[Giraffe enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.93"><![CDATA[Giraffes live in the African savannahs. They can go for weeks without drinking.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.94"><![CDATA[Kenyan flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.94"><![CDATA[The Kenyan flag has 4 symbols. In the center is a Maasai shield with a spear.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.95"><![CDATA[Giraffe hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.95"><![CDATA[The giraffe is an even-toed ungulate, as can be seen from its cloven hoof.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.96"><![CDATA[Plush giraffe]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.96"><![CDATA[How cute! The little plush giraffe has two cheerful horns, just like its real counterpart.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.97"><![CDATA[Blue ball]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.97"><![CDATA[Giraffes like to lick the blue paint off their balls, which is why this one has white spots.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.98"><![CDATA[Elephant enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.98"><![CDATA[The Indian elephant is smaller than the African one. It has smaller ears, just look!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.99"><![CDATA[Flag of Malaysia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.99"><![CDATA[The star on the flag of Malaysia has 14 points, each symbolizing 1 federal state.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.100"><![CDATA[Elephant footprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.100"><![CDATA[Elephants have huge feet and can even dance on their toes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.101"><![CDATA[Plush elephant]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.101"><![CDATA[Big, strong elephants were once used in war or to carry cargo. This one is just for cuddling.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.102"><![CDATA[Peanut]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.102"><![CDATA[Peanuts come in different variations, such as salted or roasted.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.103"><![CDATA[Flock of pigeons]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.103"><![CDATA[Pigeons are found all over the world. They like to eat whatever they can find.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.104"><![CDATA[Flag of Mexico]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.104"><![CDATA[In the land of the Maya and Aztecs, you can find many temples, pyramids, and impressive buildings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.105"><![CDATA[Pigeon's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.105"><![CDATA[The pigeon claw allows for comfortable seating on branches and cables. 3 claws protrude forward and one backward.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.106"><![CDATA[Plush pigeon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.106"><![CDATA[There are many types of pigeons. Over 40 different genera and over 300 species.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.107"><![CDATA[Olive branch]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.107"><![CDATA[This ice olive is truly special. It grows in Antarctica and melts at -10°C.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.108"><![CDATA[Vegetarian]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.108"><![CDATA[If koalas can't find eucalyptus on land, they go looking for it underwater.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.109"><![CDATA[Flag of Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.109"><![CDATA[Australia is home to many animals and marsupials such as the koala, kangaroo, wombat, Tasmanian devil and opossum.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.110"><![CDATA[Koala paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.110"><![CDATA[To climb trees, koalas simply dig their claws into the bark and swing up using their limbs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.111"><![CDATA[Plush koala]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.111"><![CDATA[Koala bears are popular for their cuteness. Their noses and ears give them the appearance of teddy bears.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.112"><![CDATA[Eucalyptus leaf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.112"><![CDATA[Koalas prefer eucalyptus leaves. Of the 500 known species of eucalyptus, they only eat 70.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.113"><![CDATA[Slávek the super cleaner]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.113"><![CDATA[Slávek keeps all the enclosures clean and has a trick for it: if an animal doesn't move from a spot with a stain, he simply lathers it up!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.114"><![CDATA[Nightingale's brush]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.114"><![CDATA[Slávek uses a brush to clean the floor, but sometimes he also runs over animal hair.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.115"><![CDATA[Slávka's gloves]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.115"><![CDATA[Sławek moves his fingers happily in his gloves. Most animals can even count to five.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.116"><![CDATA[Nightingale's hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.116"><![CDATA[Thanks to the red cap, Slavek got rid of the occasional parrot visitors in his hair.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.117"><![CDATA[Nightingale mushroom]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.117"><![CDATA[The natural sponge foams very nicely. It grows in the deep sea, where the sea is cleanest and clearest.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.118"><![CDATA[Witch hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.118"><![CDATA[A witch's hat serves a vital purpose. If a witch is flying on her broomstick in a thunderstorm, it serves as a lightning rod.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.119"><![CDATA[Sweet or sour?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.119"><![CDATA[This custom originates from medieval Ireland and England, when the poor would go door to door on Halloween, begging for something to eat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.120"><![CDATA[Ghost costume]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.120"><![CDATA[One of the easiest Halloween costumes: Take a sheet, cut two holes for eyes, throw it over yourself. And we have a spooky ghost!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.121"><![CDATA[Horror Arrow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.121"><![CDATA[Want to go after zombies? Then put this horror arrow on your head. It looks like a real bullet through the head!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.122"><![CDATA[Vampire teeth]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.122"><![CDATA[Sneaking through the night like Count Dracula? These terrifying vampire fangs will make everyone run away. According to Bram Stoker's 1897 novel, vampires avoid garlic and sunlight!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.123"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.123"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.124"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.124"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.125"><![CDATA[Christmas flasks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.125"><![CDATA[Best to plant immediately: It takes up to 12 years for a small fir seed to grow into a mature tree.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.126"><![CDATA[Flower candlestick]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.126"><![CDATA[Warning – risk of burns! A candle flame can reach up to 1400°C at its hottest point! Ouch!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.127"><![CDATA[Santa's hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.127"><![CDATA[Even today, reindeer are replacing cars in many Scandinavian regions. In the darkness of the polar winter, many people hang light chains on their reindeer's antlers to avoid car accidents. Even Santa Claus thinks that's clever!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.128"><![CDATA[Star]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.128"><![CDATA[Luminous Pointer: According to Christians, on Christmas night, a bright star showed the 3 holy kings the way to Bethlehem, where Baby Jesus had just been born.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.129"><![CDATA[Candied apple]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.129"><![CDATA[Christmas is considered the “Holiday of Love.” Perhaps especially many of these loving apples are eaten at this time.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.130"><![CDATA[Moss Menu]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.130"><![CDATA[Due to the poor vegetation, reindeer are dependent on lichens, mosses and mushrooms in winter. Enjoy your meal!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.131"><![CDATA[Finnish flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.131"><![CDATA[A good quarter of Finland's land area lies beyond the Arctic Circle. At the northernmost point of Finland, the sun does not set for at least 70 days in the summer.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.132"><![CDATA[Mass migration]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.132"><![CDATA[In the spring, many smaller groups of reindeer join together and embark on a long journey in one large group, up to 5,000 kilometers long.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.133"><![CDATA[Plush reindeer]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.133"><![CDATA[With their large, shovel-shaped antlers, reindeer can easily clear snow from wind-logged roads, which is why they have been valued as practical draft animals since ancient times.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.134"><![CDATA[Bell]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.134"><![CDATA[It has been proven that mostly herbivorous reindeer will occasionally eat rodents, fish, birds and eggs. Something for the insatiable!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.135"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.135"><![CDATA[Green, green and more green, that's all I like! Nothing tastes better to zebras than fresh, juicy meadow flowers and crunchy tufts of grass.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.136"><![CDATA[South African flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.136"><![CDATA[Every year, herds of zebras make the long journey from their homeland in southern Africa to Scandinavia, where they find protection and a bit of coolness, well camouflaged in the undergrowth of the snowy forest.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.137"><![CDATA[Zebra stripes]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.137"><![CDATA[Their black and white striping makes them virtually invisible to certain species of flies that transmit sleeping sickness.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.138"><![CDATA[Plush zebra]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.138"><![CDATA[A very important horse: Some herds have zebra stallions as bodyguards who keep an eye on the zebra ladies as they wander.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.139"><![CDATA[Bird care]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.139"><![CDATA[Birds are responsible for taking care of the zebra's fur. The little caretakers make themselves comfortable on the zebras' backs and pick out all sorts of annoying insects from their fur. Massages included!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.140"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.140"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.141"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.141"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.142"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.142"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.143"><![CDATA[Roses]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.143"><![CDATA[Love passes through...the nose! Besides sweet pralines and fragrant perfumes, flowers are most often given on Valentine's Day.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.144"><![CDATA[Pralines]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.144"><![CDATA[The Swiss are real sweet tooths. On average, they eat the most chocolate.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.145"><![CDATA[Kiss]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.145"><![CDATA[Facial strengthening: Up to 34 facial muscles are involved in a kiss. Just make sure it doesn't turn into muscle fever!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.146"><![CDATA[Diamond ring]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.146"><![CDATA[In ancient Rome, the wedding ring was worn on the left hand because people believed that a vein led directly to the heart from here.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.147"><![CDATA[Cupid]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.147"><![CDATA[The most faithful of all animals are swans - there are known cases when a swan fell in love with a water strider.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.148"><![CDATA[Hippo diet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.148"><![CDATA[Hippos eat only plants. They certainly don't get fat from such a diet! But they do secretly go out at night to snack on chocolate!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.149"><![CDATA[Nile dweller]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.149"><![CDATA[Hippos used to live on the Nile River, but today they are only found north of the Sahara.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.150"><![CDATA[Swimming champions]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.150"><![CDATA[You might not believe it, but hippos are excellent swimmers! They can thank the webbed feet between their toes for this, among other things.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.151"><![CDATA[Plush hippo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.151"><![CDATA[Mom, Mom!! Hippo mothers have a very close relationship with their babies, which usually lasts their entire lives.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.152"><![CDATA[Giant baby]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.152"><![CDATA[At birth, a baby hippo can weigh up to 55 kg. They are quite the lads!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.156"><![CDATA[Crown]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.156"><![CDATA[Shining crown of gold and jewel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.157"><![CDATA[Crowned frog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.157"><![CDATA[A frog with a crown. How cute!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.158"><![CDATA[Fins]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.158"><![CDATA[Special fiberglass reinforced fins]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.159"><![CDATA[Plush rhinoceros]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.159"><![CDATA[Despite their intimidating appearance, rhinos are peaceful animals and prefer to eat plants.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.160"><![CDATA[Rhinoceros footprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.160"><![CDATA[Rhinos have incredibly strong legs, which they use to support the heavy weight of their bodies. Yet this animal is not slow at all!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.161"><![CDATA[Plush rhinoceros]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.161"><![CDATA[While male rhinos prefer solitude, females prefer a herd where they can closely watch over their young.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.162"><![CDATA[South Africa]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.162"><![CDATA[Outside of Asia, rhinos are mainly found in Africa. The endless savannah provides rhinos with plenty of food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.163"><![CDATA[Red-headed Heron]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.163"><![CDATA[Because of their thick skin, rhinos have trouble getting rid of vermin. Luckily, a red-headed heron will help and drive out all the annoying pests!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.164"><![CDATA[Omnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.164"><![CDATA[Crocodiles are definitely not picky when it comes to meat for dinner.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.165"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.165"><![CDATA[Alligators have webbed feet, which is one of the reasons they are such great swimmers!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.166"><![CDATA[Plush crocodile]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.166"><![CDATA[It's hard to believe that crocodile mothers are so caring and attentive!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.167"><![CDATA[America]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.167"><![CDATA[Alligators have everything they need in the swamps and lakes of North America. Their favorite state, of course, is Florida!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.168"><![CDATA[Hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.168"><![CDATA[Alligator wrestling is a sport in the US. But they have to be careful not to lose their hat... or their head!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.169"><![CDATA[Red stone]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.169"><![CDATA[A red stone engraved with a mysterious bird.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.170"><![CDATA[Sunscreen]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.170"><![CDATA[Sunscreen is essential to survive in the Australian sun!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.171"><![CDATA[Surfboard]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.171"><![CDATA[Catch a big wave on a surfboard.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.172"><![CDATA[Run for Lori]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.172"><![CDATA[Lemurs like Lori like to be clean. Their special cleaning claw doesn't help them clean their enclosure, but it does help keep their thick fur clean and soft.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.173"><![CDATA[Indian flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.173"><![CDATA[Big-eyed monkeys are at home in the rainforest. Lori can hide perfectly in the dense foliage of the trees. She just hangs around for hours, enjoying the day.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.174"><![CDATA[Lori's paws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.174"><![CDATA[Lori has a very strong thumb and index finger. Her firm grip is almost impossible to open. That's how she can hang the clock in one place.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.175"><![CDATA[Cuddly Lori]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.175"><![CDATA[Be careful, it's poisonous! The slow loris is one of the species you shouldn't pet too much. It has a poisonous gland on its shoulder that protects it from enemy bites.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.176"><![CDATA[Sun - no, thank you!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.176"><![CDATA[Lories search for food at night. Their large eyes allow them to see perfectly in the dark. During the day it is clear: Close your eyes and rest from the strenuous hunt.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.177"><![CDATA[Eagle cage]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.177"><![CDATA[Eagles nest in dry areas. They inhabit savannas as well as semi-deserts.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.178"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.178"><![CDATA[Many nations have their flags adorned with an eagle's head. It is a symbol of power and victory.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.179"><![CDATA[Eagle's Claws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.179"><![CDATA[When an eagle grabs prey on the ground with its powerful talons, it has no chance.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.180"><![CDATA[Plush eagle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.180"><![CDATA[What a sweet little pet! Newly hatched eaglets have soft, plush feathers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.181"><![CDATA[Uncle Sam's hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.181"><![CDATA[This American top hat is a national symbol of the United States of America - just like the bald eagle.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.182"><![CDATA[Taj Mahal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.183"><![CDATA[Cricket bats]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.184"><![CDATA[Henna tattoo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.185"><![CDATA[Shield]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.185"><![CDATA[On the run, this otherwise lethargic animal is as fast as a cat. When threatened, the raccoon rolls onto its back and attacks its enemies with its sharp claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.186"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.186"><![CDATA[The ground squirrel feels best in the Kenyan savannah, where it goes on night hunts for termites and ants.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.187"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.187"><![CDATA[The groundhog has incredibly strong front claws that can reach through the thickest surface to the termites.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.188"><![CDATA[Plush rake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.188"><![CDATA[It's hard to believe that burrowing owls can reach up to 1.65 m. And the stronger ones weigh up to 70 kg.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.189"><![CDATA[Shovel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.189"><![CDATA[If you want to try digging a burrow for a groundhog, you have to dig a 13 m long tunnel.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.190"><![CDATA[Shield]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.190"><![CDATA[Donkeys can live up to 40 years. They are very loyal and easy-going companions, but they can also be stubborn.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.191"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.191"><![CDATA[Donkeys are an essential part of the life of nomads in the steppes of Mongolia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.192"><![CDATA[Hoofprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.192"><![CDATA[Donkeys are skilled navigators on both rocky terrain and dry land, but in humid climates their hooves require special attention.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.193"><![CDATA[Plush donkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.193"><![CDATA[Some shepherds use donkeys to protect their flocks from attacks by lynxes, bears, and wolves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.194"><![CDATA[Carriage]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.194"><![CDATA[Donkeys are used as draft animals because of their endurance. However, they are often very stubborn.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.195"><![CDATA[Balloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.196"><![CDATA[Trumpet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.197"><![CDATA[Party hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.198"><![CDATA[A glass of sparkling wine]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.200"><![CDATA[Jaguar enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.200"><![CDATA[This soft-bodied predator is very adaptable, especially comfortable where there is plenty of shelter, prey and water. Meow!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.201"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.201"><![CDATA[In the tropical rainforest, these loners sneak up on their prey - and then strike with lightning speed.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.202"><![CDATA[Jaguar paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.202"><![CDATA[As a typical stealth hunter, these big cats are surprisingly quiet despite their body structure.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.203"><![CDATA[Plush jaguar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.203"><![CDATA[Did you know that jaguar cubs are as big as a house cat after just 6 weeks and go hunting with their parents?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.204"><![CDATA[Aztec Gold]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.204"><![CDATA[Jaguar skin was already very rare during the time of the Aztecs and Mayan kings often adorned themselves with it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.205"><![CDATA[Hummingbird cage]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.205"><![CDATA[Wow, look closely: That's not an insect, it's a hummingbird! It can flap its wings up to 50 times per second and fly in place.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.206"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.206"><![CDATA[Where does the hummingbird come from? Among other things, from the Lesser Antilles! There are sweet flowers there, their nectar gives it the strength to flap its wings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.207"><![CDATA[Hummingbird claws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.207"><![CDATA[A hummingbird doesn't just need its talons to find food. It hovers like a helicopter among colorful flowers, sucking nectar from them with its long tongue.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.208"><![CDATA[Plush hummingbird]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.208"><![CDATA[This little creature especially likes colorful flowers, how cute! And if it sometimes swallows a small insect in them, it doesn't matter at all. It just eats it. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.209"><![CDATA[Feed stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.209"><![CDATA[Hummingbirds are the fastest vertebrates and can even fly backwards and sideways to reach food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.210"><![CDATA[Pretzel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.211"><![CDATA[Traditional hat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.212"><![CDATA[Tuplak]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.213"><![CDATA[Platypus enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.213"><![CDATA[The nocturnal platypus spends most of its time in the water. Its eyes are closed, so how can it find its way around? On land, it hides in a burrow.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.214"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.214"><![CDATA[When scientists first brought platypuses to Europe, everyone thought it was a stuffed animal joke. A duck in front, a water rat in the back.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.215"><![CDATA[Platypus claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.215"><![CDATA[Despite having webbed feet, the platypus moves surprisingly quickly on land. Its gait resembles that of a lizard.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.216"><![CDATA[Plush platypus]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.216"><![CDATA[This little mess looks like a living fossil. The oldest finds of this species are 4.5 million years old, and the modern platypus is more than 100,000 years old.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.217"><![CDATA[Boomerang]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.217"><![CDATA[The original inhabitants of Australia, the Aborigines, use boomerangs for hunting. It is unclear whether they have ever caught platypuses with them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.218"><![CDATA[Wolf enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.218"><![CDATA[The wolf is known as a forest animal and feels most at home in the forest. Its pack finds protection and prey there.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.219"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.219"><![CDATA[The Central European wolf is one of the few wild animals that lives even in densely populated areas of Germany.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.220"><![CDATA[Wolf's paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.220"><![CDATA[In the fairy tale "The Wolf and the Seven Little Goats", the wolf reveals himself with his black paw. Read it again quickly!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.221"><![CDATA[Plush wolf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.221"><![CDATA[Children like plush wolves because they resemble domestic dogs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.222"><![CDATA[Little Red Riding Hood]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.222"><![CDATA[Wolves appear in many fairy tales as villains or in horror films as werewolves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.228"><![CDATA[Green iguana enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.228"><![CDATA[The green iguana lives in trees, where it can blend in with its surroundings. But it also feels at home in the water!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.229"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.229"><![CDATA[The green iguana is one of the largest lizards in the Americas. It is also an excellent climber and swimmer.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.230"><![CDATA[Iguana claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.230"><![CDATA[The iguana is able to camouflage itself well from its enemies, but if necessary, it is ready to use its strong and sharp claw.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.231"><![CDATA[Plush iguana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.231"><![CDATA[Did you know that an iguana can hold its breath underwater for up to 30 minutes?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.232"><![CDATA[Dragon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.232"><![CDATA[The green iguana looks like a small dragon and thus inspires kite makers around the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.238"><![CDATA[Raven - enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.238"><![CDATA[Ravens are incredibly intelligent. Just look at how they hide their food. They make sure no one is looking and then they hide it. How clever!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.239"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.239"><![CDATA[Ravens have been kept in the Tower of London for centuries. Back then, it was a prison. Torture and executions were common, and ravens became a symbol of this dark age.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.240"><![CDATA[Raven's Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.240"><![CDATA[When searching for food, it alerts other ravens with a loud screech.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.241"><![CDATA[Plush raven]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.241"><![CDATA[Ravens have mostly black, iridescent feathers and a relatively long lifespan.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.242"><![CDATA[Abacus]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.242"><![CDATA[Ravens are so smart: they can plan complex activities in advance. It wouldn't be surprising if they were also good at counting.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.243"><![CDATA[Anthill enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.243"><![CDATA[Anteaters are solitary creatures that roam forested areas during the day and rest underground at night.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.244"><![CDATA[Flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.244"><![CDATA[This strange animal moves in savannas, forests and swamps in different parts of the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.245"><![CDATA[Anteater's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.245"><![CDATA[The anteater also uses its very sharp claws to reach termites and ants.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.246"><![CDATA[Plush anteater]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.246"><![CDATA[The anteater has a great sense of smell, which it needs to sniff out its favorite treat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.247"><![CDATA[Pan's flute]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.247"><![CDATA[Even an anteater can't resist the sound of a pan flute. It's no wonder that it has poor hearing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.248"><![CDATA[Tarantulas - enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.248"><![CDATA[The tarantula is active at night. During the day it burrows into its cave. When hunting, it jumps on its prey and infects it with its venom.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.249"><![CDATA[Italy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.249"><![CDATA[The name tarantula comes from the Italian city of Taranto, where this giant spider was first described.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.250"><![CDATA[Tarantula - leg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.250"><![CDATA[These eight-legged spiders catch insects not with a web, but by lying in wait for their prey and jumping on it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.251"><![CDATA[Soft tarantula]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.251"><![CDATA[Tarantulas have enlarged hind eyes that face straight ahead, allowing them to see very well.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.252"><![CDATA[Knitting tools]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.252"><![CDATA[Most spiders weave their own webs to catch prey. Tarantulas do not need weaving skills to make webs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.259"><![CDATA[Llama - enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.259"><![CDATA[Llamas live in herds. They spit at each other to create order in the herd or to keep their distance.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.260"><![CDATA[Peru]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.260"><![CDATA[In the Andes, the llama moves with its hooves very confidently, perfectly adapted to the mountainous region.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.261"><![CDATA[Llama's foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.261"><![CDATA[Llamas are ungulates that have "pads" on their hooves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.262"><![CDATA[Plush llama]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.262"><![CDATA[People in the Andes have used llamas as draft animals since ancient times. Their wool is soft and highly sought after.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.263"><![CDATA[Gum]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.263"><![CDATA[If threatened, llamas will spit on the attacker. They are masters at spitting gum.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.254"><![CDATA[Mandrill - enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.254"><![CDATA[The mandrill lives in tropical rainforests and likes fruits, seeds, leaves, mushrooms and small vertebrates. It most often forages on the ground.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.255"><![CDATA[Cameroon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.255"><![CDATA[Mandrills live in the dense tropical forests of central Africa, such as Cameroon. These primates communicate with each other with loud cries and grunts, making them easy to spot by hunters.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.256"><![CDATA[Mandrill paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.256"><![CDATA[The mandrill moves on all fours on the ground, but climbs trees to sleep. Its legs and claws are ideal for this movement.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.257"><![CDATA[Plush mandrill]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.257"><![CDATA[Like other primates, mandrills groom each other. This grooming serves as both communication and as part of social behavior.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.258"><![CDATA[Djembe - drum]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.258"><![CDATA[The body of the African drum called the djembe is made from the hollow of a tree trunk, which is covered with goatskin. The rhythm of these drums can be heard throughout Africa.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.264"><![CDATA[Fish fans]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.264"><![CDATA[Mmm, fish! The seals have fresh fish every day. Sometimes some krill and they have a great dinner!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.265"><![CDATA[Iceland]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.265"><![CDATA[Seals prefer to roam around the Arctic Ocean and Antarctica. They have a thick layer of blubber that keeps them warm. They also like to sleep on floating ice floes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.266"><![CDATA[Seal fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.266"><![CDATA[Even though seals are like missiles in the water, they breed on land. They move forward with their powerful flippers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.267"><![CDATA[Plush seal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.267"><![CDATA[A seal's mustache is essential for survival. It is necessary for the sense of movement in the water, including the movement of their prey. Without it, they would certainly starve.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.268"><![CDATA[Fish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.268"><![CDATA[Seals look quite harmless because of their large eyes, but their hunting instincts flare up around fish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.269"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.269"><![CDATA[Ferrets are carnivores. They do not have a cecum, the part of the intestine that helps omnivores digest plants.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.270"><![CDATA[Italy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.270"><![CDATA[Even the ancient Romans used ferrets to combat rabbit infestations. Quite a large prey for such small mammals!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.271"><![CDATA[Claws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.271"><![CDATA[Ferrets have toe pads and cannot retract their claws. These pads on their front paws are a clue for trackers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.272"><![CDATA[Plush ferret]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.272"><![CDATA[Ferrets are often kept as pets. They have been so domesticated that life in the wild would be very difficult for them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.273"><![CDATA[Retractable mouse]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.273"><![CDATA[What's that sound? A mouse! With this toy, your ferret will maintain its keen hunting instinct.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.274"><![CDATA[Fish fans]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.274"><![CDATA[Puffins love fish and small crustaceans. Herring and sardines are very popular. Small puffins like to bite into snacks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.275"><![CDATA[Ireland]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.275"><![CDATA[During mating, the colorful puffins frolic on the ground. They love the rocky cliffs of Ireland and the British Isles, but they also feel at home in Norway, Iceland, the Faroe Islands and the coast of the Brittany peninsula in France.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.276"><![CDATA[Puffin - paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.276"><![CDATA[Because they spend their time both at sea and on land, their webbed toes are put to good use.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.277"><![CDATA[Plush puffin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.277"><![CDATA[During mating season, these cute puffins stand on a cliff and call out to their partners, who respond to their calls while they wait in the breeding den.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.278"><![CDATA[Fishing net]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.278"><![CDATA[These birds need a lot of fish for nutrition and for their offspring. The incubation period is only 36 days, so you need to start catching fish!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.279"><![CDATA[Hunter]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.279"><![CDATA[Arctic foxes hunt lemmings and other small rodents. Their sense of smell is so sensitive that they can detect prey even through a thick layer of snow.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.280"><![CDATA[Norway]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.280"><![CDATA[Arctic foxes live in the polar regions of northern Europe, Greenland, and Alaska.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.281"><![CDATA[Arctic fox - paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.281"><![CDATA[Arctic foxes live in the tundra and on ice. They can cross large areas of land and ice while searching for new habitat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.282"><![CDATA[Plush Arctic Fox]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.282"><![CDATA[Newborn Arctic foxes are blind, deaf and very small. Their smooth dark brown fur quickly turns light.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.283"><![CDATA[Crystal snowflake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.283"><![CDATA[Arctic foxes are white as snow. Their fur is 70% wool, which keeps them warm.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.284"><![CDATA[Nut lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.284"><![CDATA[Squirrels eat very healthily. They like insects, worms, nuts, seeds, berries and mushrooms.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.285"><![CDATA[Czechia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.285"><![CDATA[Squirrels are common throughout Europe and northern Asia. In winter, they grow a coat-like coat of fur.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.286"><![CDATA[Squirrel's paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.286"><![CDATA[Their long, rounded claws are needed for climbing and holding food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.287"><![CDATA[Plush squirrel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.287"><![CDATA[Squirrels are especially known for their bushy tails. They are very fluffy and help them with their balance when climbing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.288"><![CDATA[Magic nuts]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.288"><![CDATA[Three magic nuts can make many dreams come true. Who knows how many magic nuts the squirrels have already hidden?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.289"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.289"><![CDATA[The kinkajou loves juicy fruit and delicious fruit nectar. Few animals are as addicted to fruit as the kinkajou. It is not for nothing that this sweet tooth has earned the nickname honey bear.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.290"><![CDATA[Bolivia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.290"><![CDATA[These agile climbers are particularly comfortable in the treetops of the tropical rainforest. They are very shy and will make a quiet snort if startled while eating.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.291"><![CDATA[Kinkaj's paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.291"><![CDATA[Finding a kinkajou's paw print is almost impossible because they jump from tree to tree and rarely come down to the ground voluntarily.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.292"><![CDATA[Plush kinkajou]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.292"><![CDATA[The kinkajou is a very adept tree climber, aided by its strong tail, which it uses to hang from branches while sucking nectar from flowers with its long tongue.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.293"><![CDATA[Perfume]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.293"><![CDATA[Although the kinkajou is a social animal, it also marks its territory using its scent.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.295"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.295"><![CDATA[Margays are members of the cat family. As carnivores, they hunt rodents, birds, and lizards. They also eat fruit and insects.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.296"><![CDATA[Mexico]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.296"><![CDATA[Margay lives in the forests of South America - from Mexico to Argentina.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.297"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.297"><![CDATA[The Margay has very flexible toes and especially wide paws, which are great for climbing. Climbing a tree upside down? No problem!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.298"><![CDATA[Plush margay]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.298"><![CDATA[Their spotted fur is highly prized by hunters. Today, these cats are protected. Fortunately, they are also very shy and difficult to spot in the treetops.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.299"><![CDATA[Cat's eye]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.299"><![CDATA[As a day and night hunter, the margay has very good eyesight and can find its prey even in the dark.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.300"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.300"><![CDATA[They use their strong beaks to pick up fruit. A little protein - in the form of insects, spiders and small reptiles - is always welcome.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.301"><![CDATA[Colombia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.301"><![CDATA[The subtropical and tropical rainforests of the Andes are teeming with toucans. The colorful toucans are very popular with tourists.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.302"><![CDATA[Toucan claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.302"><![CDATA[The toucan's claw resembles a woodpecker's claw, which has two in front and two in back, and can easily grab onto any tree.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.303"><![CDATA[Plush toucan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.303"><![CDATA[The toucan's stunning beak has a special function; it can regulate its body temperature by changing its blood supply according to the ambient temperature.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.304"><![CDATA[Rain Caller]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.304"><![CDATA[Rainmakers are used in religious ceremonies in the Andes. The small stones make the sound of rain and are certainly more relaxing than the calls of toucans.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.305"><![CDATA[Cupcake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.306"><![CDATA[Heart balloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.307"><![CDATA[Greeting card]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.308"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.308"><![CDATA[Storks like frogs, fish, tadpoles, lizards and small rodents. Their beaks are an important tool in finding food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.309"><![CDATA[Germany]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.309"><![CDATA[Storks like temperate climates. The original species comes from Germany and their nests can be found on tall poles on farms.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.310"><![CDATA[Stork's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.310"><![CDATA[One claw points backwards and the other three forwards. Their webbed feet are usually stunted. Their long legs carry them particularly majestically in flight.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.311"><![CDATA[Plush stork]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.311"><![CDATA[Most storks live in colonies, but some are solitary - and they are known for their lifelong partnerships. How romantic!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.312"><![CDATA[Pacifier]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.312"><![CDATA[Many people are familiar with the white stork. According to a fairy tale, a stork pecked a pregnant woman in the leg, and she then waited in bed for the stork to bring her a baby.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.315"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.315"><![CDATA[Jackals hunt in groups or alone. They will eat anything that comes their way: insects, birds, eggs or small reptiles.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.316"><![CDATA[Tanzania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.316"><![CDATA[Jackals prowl the savannah, bush, or open pastures. They sometimes follow lions on their hunts, howling when they catch their prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.317"><![CDATA[Jackal's paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.317"><![CDATA[Jackals mate for life. Male jackals perform a courtship dance for their mates.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.318"><![CDATA[Plush jackal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.318"><![CDATA[Jackals live in caves or underground dens. Some jackals nibble each other's fur as a sign of affection.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.319"><![CDATA[Anubis]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.319"><![CDATA[The Egyptian god Anubis is depicted with the head of a jackal. Jackals were believed to guide souls to the afterlife.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.320"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.320"><![CDATA[Mmmm, termites! With his long tongue he pulls termites out of their holes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.321"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.321"><![CDATA[Like many Australian mammals, the spotted anteater is a marsupial. After a 14-day gestation period, two to four young are born.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.322"><![CDATA[Anteater - claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.322"><![CDATA[Thanks to their long claws, they can easily reach termites and even dig burrows. They protect themselves from the midday heat by going underground.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.323"><![CDATA[Plush anteater anteater]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.323"><![CDATA[The spotted anteater is a marsupial without a pouch. The young attach themselves to the fur around their mothers' breasts. When they move to a new burrow, the mothers carry their young on their backs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.324"><![CDATA[Licorice root]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.324"><![CDATA[Its long tongue helps it find termites. Don't you think it's spinning around in its mouth like a licorice stick?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.325"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.325"><![CDATA[Wildebeests travel long distances in search of green pastures. They do not like dry grass.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.326"><![CDATA[Tanzania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.326"><![CDATA[Herds of wildebeest roam the open savannas of the Serengeti in Tanzania.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.327"><![CDATA[Wildebeest hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.327"><![CDATA[Wildebeests are even-toed ungulates, meaning they have an even number of toes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.328"><![CDATA[Plush wildebeest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.328"><![CDATA[Wildebeest live up to 20 years, unless they fall victim to their natural enemies.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.329"><![CDATA[Cup]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.329"><![CDATA[The colorful cup contains a lot of water. Unfortunately, thirsty wildebeests are not good at holding it with their hooves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.330"><![CDATA[Vegetarian]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.330"><![CDATA[The emu has a long neck, so it can pluck leaves from trees and branches. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.331"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.331"><![CDATA[Many flightless birds are native to Australia, including the emu. The mild winter is an ideal breeding season.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.332"><![CDATA[Emu - claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.332"><![CDATA[The emu runs across the steppes on two legs. Due to its weight and underdeveloped chest muscles, it cannot fly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.333"><![CDATA[Plush emu]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.333"><![CDATA[Many species of emus are now extinct or endangered. A stuffed emu is a great way to keep them close to your heart.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.334"><![CDATA[Easter egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.334"><![CDATA[An emu lays between 5 and 15 eggs. Do you think the chicks are as colorful as these eggs?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.335"><![CDATA[Pink chick]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.336"><![CDATA[Yellow chick]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.337"><![CDATA[Green chick]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.338"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.338"><![CDATA[The falcon loves meat and feeds on small mammals, birds and even reptiles.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.339"><![CDATA[Germany]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.339"><![CDATA[Falconry is considered a status symbol. In Germany, people who want to become falconers must have a special permit.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.340"><![CDATA[Falcon's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.340"><![CDATA[Falcons use their talons to catch and hold their prey. Small animals can die from the sheer force of their attack.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.341"><![CDATA[Plush falcon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.341"><![CDATA[Falcons appear in many fairy tales and myths. They are symbols of courage and heroic deeds.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.342"><![CDATA[Glove]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.342"><![CDATA[Falconers must always wear gloves, otherwise a falcon could injure them if it lands on their hand.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.343"><![CDATA[Insectivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.343"><![CDATA[Centipedes and larvae are its main food. It uses its long, pointed beak not only for food but also to maintain its balance so that it does not fall.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.344"><![CDATA[New Zealand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.344"><![CDATA[The kiwi is native to New Zealand and has become a national symbol.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.345"><![CDATA[Kiwi - claws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.345"><![CDATA[Did you know that kiwis have small claws on the ends of their wings? But they are hidden under their feathers. They have 4 toes on their feet, which allows them to move very quickly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.346"><![CDATA[Plush kiwi]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.346"><![CDATA[New Zealanders love their kiwis. The people of New Zealand even call themselves "kiwis".]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.347"><![CDATA[Megaphone]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.347"><![CDATA[Kiwis are nocturnal creatures and are therefore more heard than seen. At night, they can be heard up to 5 km away!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.348"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.348"><![CDATA[Although the mustang is very modest, it enjoys fresh grass. There is more than enough of it on the prairies, which is why the wild mustang population thrives so well here.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.349"><![CDATA[America]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.349"><![CDATA[Mustangs were brought to America by Spanish conquistadors. They were mostly horses of Arabian and Berber origin that had run away from their masters. Thanks to their natural temperament, they were able to easily adapt to life in the wild.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.350"><![CDATA[Mustang hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.350"><![CDATA[Mustangs have small, hard hooves, a strong back, and a muscular rump. Native Americans used them for hunting, fighting, and as draft animals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.351"><![CDATA[Rocking horse]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.351"><![CDATA[At between 140 and 150 centimeters tall at the withers, Mustangs are among the smaller horses, but due to their wild nature, they do not make ideal pets.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.352"><![CDATA[Cowboy boots]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.352"><![CDATA[Mustangs are notorious for their fierce nature and high jumps. Riding a wild mustang is one of the favorite cowboy disciplines at rodeos - a very dangerous sport.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.353"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.353"><![CDATA[Otters are predators and hunt underwater. Fish, frogs, crayfish and other small invertebrates are on their diet.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.354"><![CDATA[Germany]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.354"><![CDATA[Otters are not only native to Germany, but also all over the world. They have not settled in Australia and a few remote islands.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.355"><![CDATA[Otter claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.355"><![CDATA[Otters are very fast in the water and on land. Their claws help them move; some people say it looks like they are crawling.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.356"><![CDATA[Plush otter]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.356"><![CDATA[Young otters learn to swim from as early as 2 months old! Splashing, wading and diving are great fun for them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.357"><![CDATA[Weight]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.357"><![CDATA[They have a fast metabolism, which means they burn about 15-25% of their body weight every day. Eat it up!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.358"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.358"><![CDATA[Butterflies consume liquid food using a tube-shaped proboscis. They sip sap, honeydew, or juice from rotting fruit. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.359"><![CDATA[Jamaica]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.359"><![CDATA[The largest species of butterflies, the so-called swallowtails, live in Jamaica.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.360"><![CDATA[Butterfly foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.360"><![CDATA[The butterfly's legs look dwarfed by its enormous wings. They are made up of chitinous plates arranged in rings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.361"><![CDATA[Plush butterfly]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.361"><![CDATA[Like other insects, butterflies have eyes that are made up of up to 6,000 individual smaller eyes. Look into my eyes, dear!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.362"><![CDATA[Caterpillar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.362"><![CDATA[As caterpillars, butterflies have a huge appetite and eat anything green and tasty. Their body weight doubles with each molt.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.363"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.363"><![CDATA[Scottish Highland cattle love the green grass of the Scottish meadows. Their milk is especially good!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.364"><![CDATA[Scotland]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.364"><![CDATA[The melody of the bagpipes stretches across the entire landscape while a log, called a "caber", is thrown through the air. A truly interesting country!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.365"><![CDATA[Cattle hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.365"><![CDATA[Scottish weather can be a bit fickle and the ground slippery and muddy, but that's no match for the strong hooves of cattle.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.366"><![CDATA[Plush cattle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.366"><![CDATA[Strong and obedient highland cattle have very low demands and females can give birth without human assistance.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.367"><![CDATA[Scottish kilt]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.367"><![CDATA[Tourists in Scotland often ask what Scots wear under their kilts. Do you know?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.368"><![CDATA[Insectivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.368"><![CDATA[Juicy, tasty earthworms and crunchy insects are always on the menu, but moles also enjoy small vertebrates. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.369"><![CDATA[Germany]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.369"><![CDATA[Moles are unwelcome guests in gardens. They help loosen the soil, but their burrows are unsightly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.370"><![CDATA[Mole's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.370"><![CDATA[Their claws are ideally shaped for creating underground labyrinths and they can feast on worms and insects while they work.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.371"><![CDATA[Plush mole]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.371"><![CDATA[Moles are not social creatures. Probably because they have poor eyesight. Their sense of smell and touch is particularly strong. They can even sense electricity.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.372"><![CDATA[Strawberry]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.372"><![CDATA[Their shovel-shaped claws are ideal for digging. Perfect for strawberry gardens!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.373"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.373"><![CDATA[The dodo eats fermented fruit. Maybe he looks stupid because he is stupid?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.374"><![CDATA[Mauritius]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.374"><![CDATA[The last dodo was spotted on the island of Mauritius. The animals that were brought to the island became predators, leading to its extinction.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.375"><![CDATA[Dodo - claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.375"><![CDATA[The dodo lives mostly on the ground. It is quite large and very heavy in winter. It is a flightless bird and had no natural predators on Mauritius.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.376"><![CDATA[Plush dodo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.376"><![CDATA[Sailors often ate its yellowish eggs. Unfortunately, the dodo was too trusting, which contributed to its extinction!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.377"><![CDATA[Fossil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.377"><![CDATA[The Dodo only exists as a fossil. That will draw a lot of people to the zoo. Visitors will be amazed.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.378"><![CDATA[Scavenger]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.378"><![CDATA[Carcasses don't last long in the African desert. Vultures circle until the large predators abandon their prey. Then they pounce on the entrails!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.379"><![CDATA[Ghana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.379"><![CDATA[Vultures live in steppes, semi-deserts, and mountains. They can be found in Europe, Asia, and throughout Africa.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.380"><![CDATA[Vulture's claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.380"><![CDATA[Vultures feed on the entrails of carcasses, but they prefer soft entrails. Their beaks and talons are ideal for obtaining food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.381"><![CDATA[Plush vulture]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.381"><![CDATA[Vultures are very social and live in groups. They feel at home when they snuggle up together.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.382"><![CDATA[Feather]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.382"><![CDATA[Vulture feathers look beautiful in a headband. What do you think? Isn't it pretty?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.383"><![CDATA[Meat lovers]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.383"><![CDATA[The bearded dragon eats anything that comes its way. Small vertebrates are a welcome snack!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.384"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.384"><![CDATA[These lizards can be found on the Australian continent. They reach up to 60 cm and live across most of Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.385"><![CDATA[Lizard claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.385"><![CDATA[The bearded dragon likes to relax on tree trunks, poles, and stumps. It loves the sun and is a good climber.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.386"><![CDATA[Plush lizard]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.386"><![CDATA[The bearded dragon buries its eggs in wet sand and does not guard them. Sometimes up to 35 young can hatch - that's a lot of brothers and sisters!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.387"><![CDATA[Apple]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.387"><![CDATA[In addition to hunting small vertebrates and invertebrates, they also like fresh apples or other fruits.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.388"><![CDATA[Meat lovers]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.388"><![CDATA[Ants and termites are its favorite food. Its tongue is coated with sticky saliva, which helps it catch insects.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.389"><![CDATA[Senegal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.389"><![CDATA[Pangolins are found in forests and savannas from Africa to Asia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.390"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.390"><![CDATA[A pangolin's claw is like a multi-functional tool! Ideal for digging holes and climbing trees.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.391"><![CDATA[Plush pangolin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.391"><![CDATA[Baby pangolins have very soft scales. However, these harden over time. When the pangolins are still young, they can ride on their mother's tail - it's very comfortable!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.392"><![CDATA[Earring]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.392"><![CDATA[Pangolin earrings are very cute. They look like exotic pine cones hanging from the ears.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.393"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.393"><![CDATA[Mouflon herds roam in forests or on cliffs. They love fresh grass.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.394"><![CDATA[France]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.394"><![CDATA[European mouflons like to live in France. The environment there, with its abundance of good feed, suits them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.395"><![CDATA[Mouflon hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.395"><![CDATA[If mouflon cubs are threatened by wolves, their mothers will lead them to rockier areas where the wolves will not follow them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.396"><![CDATA[Plush mouflon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.396"><![CDATA[The young also have to watch out for eagles. The forests will give them sufficient protection.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.397"><![CDATA[Sheep cheese]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.397"><![CDATA[French cheese specialties are a world delicacy. Try the mouflon cheese with rosemary. It's a revelation with the scent of mountain herbs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.398"><![CDATA[Baguette]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.398"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.399"><![CDATA[Croissant]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.399"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.400"><![CDATA[Cheese]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.400"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.401"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.401"><![CDATA[As a breeding breed, these pigs are used to living around people. They fatten up on fruits and vegetables, which keeps them nice and warm.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.402"><![CDATA[Hungary]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.402"><![CDATA[The Mangalica breed was once very popular in Hungary. The woolly pigs were able to withstand difficult living conditions.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.403"><![CDATA[Pig's hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.403"><![CDATA[Like other pig breeds, mangalicas love mud and wallow in it even in winter.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.404"><![CDATA[Plush mangalica]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.404"><![CDATA[Mangalica cubs are striped like wild boars. The wavy coat appears later.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.405"><![CDATA[Ridge]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.405"><![CDATA[Have you ever tried to comb such a wild mane? The wool is quite coarse, but it hides a warm undertone.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.406"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.406"><![CDATA[Like other dogs, the Puli loves meat. It is used to living with people and was domesticated centuries ago.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.407"><![CDATA[Hungary]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.407"><![CDATA[The Puli dog is very popular in Hungary. Hungarians show their love for this dog by saying: That's not a dog, that's a Puli!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.408"><![CDATA[Dog paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.408"><![CDATA[Puli love to run and are very active. They are very warm in the summer due to their thick coat, but in the winter they like to frolic and frolic.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.409"><![CDATA[Plush puli]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.409"><![CDATA[Once puppies lose their fur, it starts to grow back thicker. The fur gradually grows and becomes fluffier, eventually looking like a thick sweater!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.410"><![CDATA[Shepherd's staff]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.410"><![CDATA[Thanks to his strong natural instincts, he is an ideal herding dog. Sometimes his vision can be impaired when his fur gets in his eyes, but there is one solution for that: simply tie his fur!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.411"><![CDATA[Darts]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.411"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.412"><![CDATA[Balloons]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.412"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.413"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.413"><![CDATA[Komodo dragons use their tongues to track down prey. As active hunters, they will either dig up small rodents or pounce on ground-dwelling birds. They also occasionally enjoy bird eggs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.414"><![CDATA[Indonesia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.414"><![CDATA[Komodo dragons live in Indonesia and the Lesser Sunda Islands, such as Komodo Island. They can be found in a variety of habitats, including savannas, grasslands, monsoon forests, and mangrove forests.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.415"><![CDATA[Monitor lizard claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.415"><![CDATA[The Komodo dragon has claws that are adapted to any environment. As a cub, it likes to climb trees and as an adult, it searches for prey on the ground.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.416"><![CDATA[Plush Komodo dragon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.416"><![CDATA[A young Komodo dragon hatches in a clutch of about twenty leathery eggs. The eggs weigh up to 125 grams.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.417"><![CDATA[Poison]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.417"><![CDATA[The poison in the Komodo dragon's glands helps it hunt. It is the only way it can catch a larger animal. If it doesn't kill it right away, it will surely die of blood poisoning a few days later.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.423"><![CDATA[Red pepper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.423"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.424"><![CDATA[Green pepper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.424"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.425"><![CDATA[Yellow pepper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.425"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.426"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.426"><![CDATA[The long-tailed skunk loves the larvae of the beetles. It does not disdain fruit, nuts or seeds. It uses its long fingers to test unripe fruits and extract the ripe flesh.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.427"><![CDATA[Madagascar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.427"><![CDATA[Several species of the genus Ksukola - including the large Ksukola - are now extinct. The remaining species live mainly in the forested areas of Madagascar.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.428"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.428"><![CDATA[Its long spider-like fingers are one of its most distinctive features. Some cultures see this animal as a good omen, others interpret it as a sick spirit. They are also often attributed with magical powers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.429"><![CDATA[Plush tailed fox]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.429"><![CDATA[The tailed foxes have several types of communication sounds. They call to each other with a "eeep" sound, and the cubs call to their mother with a distinctive "scree" sound. When cuddling, they mumble "gnofff" to each other, but when attacking, they scream "aaaak". When it's time to escape, they release with a "hay-hay" sound. Good, right?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.430"><![CDATA[Straw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.430"><![CDATA[When a red-tailed hawk drinks, it quickly moves its long third toe back and forth, splashing water into its mouth. It might use a straw!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.431"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.431"><![CDATA[Like all wolves, the werewolf is a predator. Its prey are other animals, including humans. According to legend, after being bitten by a werewolf, the victim also turns into a werewolf. A terrible thing!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.432"><![CDATA[Greece]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.432"><![CDATA[Myths about wolfmen and werewolves were already present in ancient Greece. For example, in Ovid's Metamorphoses, Zeus transformed a man into a wolf who served human flesh at a feast. That's horrible! Absolutely unimaginable!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.433"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.433"><![CDATA[We've all seen scenes from horror movies, right? You know the one where seemingly peaceful people suddenly turn into terrifying werewolves? It starts with the hands - hair appears and the nails become claws... aaaaah!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.434"><![CDATA[Plush werewolf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.434"><![CDATA[Get one of these cuddly friends! Whoever is brave enough to take him to bed can handle even a real werewolf attack!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.435"><![CDATA[Full moon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.435"><![CDATA[Do you hear that eerie howl in the dark night? Those are werewolves howling at the moon because of their miserable existence! Do you get goosebumps too?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.436"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.436"><![CDATA[A fresh insect salad as an appetizer, a small vertebrate as a main course, and a juicy snail for dessert. Scorpions love meat! And thanks to their dexterous and strong claws, they can often indulge in it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.437"><![CDATA[Mexico]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.437"><![CDATA[The largest species of scorpions live in the desert regions of Mexico. They hide from the sun under rocks or in the sand during the day and go hunting at night.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.438"><![CDATA[Scorpion claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.438"><![CDATA[Scorpions are a member of the order Arachnids and, like other members of this class, are characterized by the fact that one of their pairs of limbs has evolved into a tactile organ, the pedipalps. In the case of scorpions, these pedipalps are also topped with powerful claws, which, in addition to their tactile function, also serve as weapons.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.439"><![CDATA[Plush scorpion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.439"><![CDATA[Scorpion mating is preceded by an elegant courtship. The pair clasp their claws together and dance across the desert. After birth, the young scorpions cling tightly to their mother's back.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.440"><![CDATA[Poisonous sting]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.440"><![CDATA[Once a scorpion spots its prey, it has two weapons at its disposal to catch it: powerful pincers and a nimble stinger. Warning: Some species of scorpion are among the most venomous creatures in the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.441"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.441"><![CDATA[Little quokkas can climb up to 1.5 meters to find juicy leaves. In times of need, they will also eat grass and plants.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.442"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.442"><![CDATA[Cute quokkas hop around in southwestern Australia and also live on Bald and Rottnest Islands.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.443"><![CDATA[Quokka - paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.443"><![CDATA[If they want to increase their speed, they hop on their hind legs. Unlike kangaroos, they do not use their tail for balance.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.444"><![CDATA[Plush quokka]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.444"><![CDATA[Like other marsupials, females carry their young in their pouches for up to 28 days.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.445"><![CDATA[Rat mask]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.445"><![CDATA[Rottnest Island is also nicknamed Rat Island because of its tiny inhabitants. A Dutch navigator mistook quokkas for rats and so named the island. Perhaps it was just a disguise?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.446"><![CDATA[Plasma blob]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.446"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.447"><![CDATA[Swift Flubber]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.447"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.448"><![CDATA[Malicious Swabby]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.448"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.449"><![CDATA[Lame Larry]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.449"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.450"><![CDATA[Grain lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.450"><![CDATA[Turkeys have a varied diet. Young birds love insects, but later they will also enjoy seeds, berries, nuts and roots. Turkeys swallow small stones to clean their stomachs and aid in digestion.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.451"><![CDATA[United States]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.451"><![CDATA[Many Native American tribes included turkey as part of their diet, and in modern times, turkeys are a staple of Thanksgiving dinner.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.452"><![CDATA[Turkey claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.452"><![CDATA[Strong claws are needed especially in winter, when they have to search for and dig for food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.453"><![CDATA[Plush turkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.453"><![CDATA[Fleshly growths hang from its neck. They can be up to 8 cm long.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.454"><![CDATA[Cutlery]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.454"><![CDATA[In North America, turkeys are a traditional part of the Thanksgiving dinner, and this harvest tradition has spread to Europe.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.455"><![CDATA[Plant lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.455"><![CDATA[Marmot loves grass and herbs. But as a typical rodent, he also likes fruits, seeds and insects.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.456"><![CDATA[United States]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.456"><![CDATA[Marmots don't like the heat and prefer to live in the subarctic regions of Canada and the northern United States. They like cool climates because their fur is too warm.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.457"><![CDATA[The paw is buzzing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.457"><![CDATA[Groundhogs dig extensive underground tunnel systems with escape routes and dead ends that can be used as toilets. They're smart, aren't they?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.458"><![CDATA[Plush marmot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.458"><![CDATA[Marmots are deep sleepers. Their hibernation period can last up to 9 months. They curl up in the grass in their sleeping chambers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.459"><![CDATA[Weather]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.459"><![CDATA[Observers at the Groundhog Day wait for the groundhog to emerge from its burrow. If the groundhog casts a shadow, it means that there will be another 6 weeks of cold weather.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.460"><![CDATA[Red leaf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.460"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.461"><![CDATA[Yellow leaf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.461"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.462"><![CDATA[Green leaf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.462"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.463"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.463"><![CDATA[Weasels are predators - from the same genus as martens, but the young are very cute. Weasels are especially suitable for hunting in mouse tunnels.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.464"><![CDATA[Russia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.464"><![CDATA[The common weasel is found far and wide. It loves cold regions, but can also be found in Mediterranean climates and North Africa. In Eurasia, it is popular as a pest hunter.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.465"><![CDATA[Weasel claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.465"><![CDATA[When running, crawling, sneaking or digging... the weasel's claws are versatile. However, when hunting, it uses its teeth and bites its prey in the throat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.466"><![CDATA[Plush weasel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.466"><![CDATA[Weasel babies weigh about 1.5 grams at birth. They are blind at birth and on average about 5 babies are born. It takes about a month for them to open their eyes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.467"><![CDATA[Can of paint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.467"><![CDATA[Weasels have perfect camouflage! At least they don't need a can of paint. Their fur automatically turns white in winter. They blend in perfectly with the snowy surroundings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.468"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.468"><![CDATA[Huskies love meat - just like other dogs! But because they live mainly with people, they eat whatever they can get their hands on.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.469"><![CDATA[Canada]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.469"><![CDATA[The weather in Canada can be very cold. Its fur provides perfect protection from the elements. If it gets stuck in the snow, it will stick its nose under a branch and spend the night under the snow.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.470"><![CDATA[Husky - paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.470"><![CDATA[Huskies have small paws compared to other dogs, which helps reduce the risk of heat loss and injury.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.471"><![CDATA[Plush husky]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.471"><![CDATA[Huskies have a great sense of direction. They won't get lost even if everything is covered in snow. That's why Eskimos love them so much.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.472"><![CDATA[Igloo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.472"><![CDATA[Husky puppies are raised by Eskimos along with their own children. They are part of the family and are, of course, allowed to enter the igloos.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.473"><![CDATA[Yellow ornament]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.473"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.474"><![CDATA[Green ornament]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.474"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.475"><![CDATA[Red ornament]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.475"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.476"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.476"><![CDATA[The Hoatzin can eat both toxic and poisonous plants. Thanks to digestive bacteria, it can completely process the poison. Its claws are very muscular and callused.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.477"><![CDATA[Colombia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.477"><![CDATA[The Hoatzin feels at home in tropical rainforests. It loves living near rivers and lakes. Water is a very important part of its home.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.478"><![CDATA[Hoatzin claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.478"><![CDATA[Their wings are not well developed, so they don't fly very well. Instead, they have claws, which are very important for movement.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.479"><![CDATA[Plush hoatzin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.479"><![CDATA[The young live in nests that are built over water. They can jump from the nest directly into the water. Whoop! Splash! They hide in the water from predators.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.480"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.480"><![CDATA[After jumping into the water, the young climb back up the tree. Their claws help them do this. Over time, they lose these claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.481"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.481"><![CDATA[Because they have no fur, Sphynx cats are very active, otherwise they will lose body temperature. For this reason, they need a lot of food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.482"><![CDATA[Canada]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.482"><![CDATA[This cat is considered sacred and is worshipped throughout Egypt. In ancient times there was a cult of this cat with many statues. They were originally bred in Canada.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.483"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.483"><![CDATA[Like any other cat, the Sphynx loves to scratch trees and soft pillows. She also likes to sneak around quietly!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.484"><![CDATA[Cuddly animal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.484"><![CDATA[If anyone thinks that a Sphynx cat has a higher body temperature than its fur, they are wrong. If you touch it, it is warm because it gives off a lot of heat through its skin.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.485"><![CDATA[Sunscreen]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.485"><![CDATA[Without a protective coat, Sphynx cats are defenseless against the sun's rays. Just like humans, they need to be protected from sunburn. How about sunscreen?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.486"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.486"><![CDATA[These hunters hunt for prey in the deserts of the Arabian Peninsula. They are not picky and eat everything from rodents and lizards to small birds and insects. They like everything!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.487"><![CDATA[Egypt]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.487"><![CDATA[The cinnamon-colored stripe on the desert fox's back gives it a special desert touch!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.488"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.488"><![CDATA[The pads on this fox's feet are perfectly equipped for wandering through the desert and climbing date palms.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.489"><![CDATA[Cuddly animal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.489"><![CDATA[The desert fox has between 2 and 6 young, but most do not survive. Once they leave the den, they find themselves in danger.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.490"><![CDATA[Parasol]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.490"><![CDATA[When a desert fox prowls the Sahara during the day, it can't do without a parasol. Fortunately for it, it's a nocturnal creature.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.491"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.491"><![CDATA[The manul is about the size of a domestic cat. It has thick fur that makes it look much larger. The manul hunts small prey such as pikas, mountain partridges and mice. Meow!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.492"><![CDATA[Afghanistan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.492"><![CDATA[At night, the manul prowls around the rocky steppes of Afghanistan and can also be found in mountains up to 3,000 meters. The manul loves rocks!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.493"><![CDATA[Manula paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.493"><![CDATA[It is not entirely certain whether the manul is closer to lynxes or cats. In any case, its velvet paws resemble our cute cats.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.494"><![CDATA[Plush manul]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.494"><![CDATA[The manul - also known as the steppe cat - is on the verge of extinction. Its way of life is being studied through scratchings in caves. Their tracks have also been discovered at higher altitudes, proving that they live in higher mountain ranges than previously thought.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.495"><![CDATA[Pocket lamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.495"><![CDATA[This nocturnal animal is very shy and sleeps in a cave or comfortable crevice during the day. At night, it hunts and stalks its prey like a real cat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.496"><![CDATA[Yellow scarab]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.496"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.497"><![CDATA[Green scarab]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.497"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.498"><![CDATA[Red scarab]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.498"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.499"><![CDATA[Carnivores]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.499"><![CDATA[Their extremely long canines allow them to catch prey such as monkeys or birds in trees. But that's just an easy meal. On the ground, they can catch wild game such as deer or wild boar. They just crouch down, jump up and bite their necks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.500"><![CDATA[China]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.500"><![CDATA[The clouded leopard lives in the wild in parts of Asia, such as China. Due to hunting for their fur and deforestation, these leopards are an endangered species.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.501"><![CDATA[Pack]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.501"><![CDATA[Like many other cats, the clouded leopard can retract its claws and give them a rest. After all, they need them when climbing trees.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.502"><![CDATA[Stuffed animal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.502"><![CDATA[Clouded leopard cubs don't have to be afraid of heights! They are born high up in the trees. But they are protected by the hollows of the trees, where they are well hidden and don't fall so easily.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.503"><![CDATA[Climbing rope]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.503"><![CDATA[The clouded leopard is quite clumsy on the ground, but it really excels at climbing trees. It doesn't even need a climbing rope! It can even climb trees headfirst! It's a true artist in motion!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.504"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.504"><![CDATA[Yummy! Fruitgliders love to suck sap from trees. They have special teeth that make holes in the bark. But they won't refuse fruit, insects or small vertebrates!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.505"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.505"><![CDATA[These cute marmosets are found mainly in the Amazon in northern Brazil. They love forests, whether rainforest or tropical. As long as there are trees!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.506"><![CDATA[Monkey paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.506"><![CDATA[heir fingers and toes have claws instead of nails, which help them with vertical climbing on trees. In the treetops, they have no competition!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.507"><![CDATA[Plush monkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.507"><![CDATA[The young are usually born as fraternal twins. They only stick around their mother during nursing and are then seen around their father and with other members of the monkey group.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.508"><![CDATA[Brush]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.508"><![CDATA[Oh no! It looks like the little marmosets fell into the paint. Or maybe they painted their ears with a paintbrush? Marmosets are cunning!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.509"><![CDATA[Yellow card]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.509"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.510"><![CDATA[Green card]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.510"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.511"><![CDATA[Red card]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.511"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.512"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.512"><![CDATA[Their slightly curved beak is ideal for searching for tasty crabs and small worms.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.513"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.513"><![CDATA[This exotic bird lives in Brazil, the Amazon estuary, and throughout northern South America. It is even the national bird of the island of Trinidad in the Lesser Antilles.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.514"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.514"><![CDATA[The scarlet ibis breeds in the spring on mangrove islands and builds its nests in bushes and trees. It's a good thing they can hold on to trees with their talons!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.515"><![CDATA[Plush]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.515"><![CDATA[Red ibis chicks have brown feathers at birth. The typical red coloration is achieved at two years. At puberty this is practical, as they reach adulthood at three years!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.516"><![CDATA[Lipstick]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.516"><![CDATA[This slender bird looks as if someone has painted it with lipstick. Its beautiful plumage makes it a star among exotic birds!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.517"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.517"><![CDATA[Like other dogs, pugs love meat. However, pugs need a well-balanced diet because they gain weight quickly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.518"><![CDATA[Great Britain]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.518"><![CDATA[The pug was bred more than a thousand years ago in China. However, the royal patronage of the breed comes from Great Britain. Many artists have created portraits of their Pugs. After all, they are still considered fashionable dogs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.519"><![CDATA[Package]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.519"><![CDATA[The pug stands out not only for its small and cute paws, but also for its round head and bulging eyes. The short muzzle often causes breathing problems in overbred animals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.520"><![CDATA[Plush pug]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.520"><![CDATA[This creature must be loved by everyone. The Pug was originally a highly revered dog. Only the Chinese emperor had the privilege of touching it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.521"><![CDATA[Dragon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.521"><![CDATA[The art of breeding was perfected in China about 2000 years ago. Since then, the pug has been known as an artistically bred breed. Many influential artists have made portraits of pugs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.522"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.522"><![CDATA[The cheetah tracks its prey, runs towards it and catches it between its legs. Small antelopes and impala fall easily and are easy prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.523"><![CDATA[Botswana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.523"><![CDATA[Cheetahs live mostly in savannah and steppe. They love tall grass and open areas for observation. Trees and bushes are not their favorites because they get in their way when they sprint.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.524"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.524"><![CDATA[Cheetah paws have strong and scaly pads, which are very useful during sprints.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.525"><![CDATA[Plush cheetah]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.525"><![CDATA[After birth, cheetah cubs have long, silvery hairs on their backs, which fall out after three months. It is also said that these help to hide the cubs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.526"><![CDATA[Stopwatch]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.526"><![CDATA[Cheetahs are the fastest animals in the world, running up to 93 km/h.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.527"><![CDATA[Yellow Easter egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.527"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.528"><![CDATA[Green Easter egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.528"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.529"><![CDATA[Red Easter egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.529"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.530"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.530"><![CDATA[These cheerful primates enjoy leaves, fruit and sometimes flowers. They prefer to eat food in groups - it tastes better that way.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.531"><![CDATA[Indonesia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.531"><![CDATA[The proboscis monkey lives on the coast of Borneo, where there are mangrove forests and a lot of rain. It often jumps from trees straight into the water. Splash!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.532"><![CDATA[Packet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.532"><![CDATA[The proboscis monkey stays near the coast and is usually active during the day. It is only a bit sleepy in the morning and early afternoon. There is nothing better than a jump into the cold water to wake it up!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.533"><![CDATA[Plush monkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.533"><![CDATA[Unlike males, females have small nostrils. But even the big, thick nose of our long-nosed kahaua is pretty, isn't it?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.534"><![CDATA[Diving goggles]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.534"><![CDATA[The proboscis monkey is an excellent swimmer - the best of all monkeys. And he can dive! Would his nose fit into a diving mask?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.535"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.535"><![CDATA[Like other breeds of sheep, Blacknose sheep like to graze on grass. These sheep are very docile and never stray. They also produce a lot of milk and wool.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.536"><![CDATA[Switzerland]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.536"><![CDATA[The Wallis Black-nosed Sheep can't yodel, but they can climb well! If one gets lost, grab your shepherd's staff and bring it back!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.537"><![CDATA[Hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.537"><![CDATA[The Valais black-nosed sheep live between mountains and valleys. They are perfectly equipped for mountain wandering and occasionally enjoy the alpine edelweiss.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.538"><![CDATA[Woolly sheep]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.538"><![CDATA[They really do have wool everywhere! The Wallis Blacknose sheep is covered in wool from head to toe. Sometimes the wool even gets in their eyes. It might be best to tie it up in a ponytail when climbing mountains.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.539"><![CDATA[Ladder]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.539"><![CDATA[Hop, hop, hop! Lambs happily hop across the rocky countryside and adult sheep love the mountains. They have a strong natural character and wool that protects them from all weathers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.540"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.540"><![CDATA[Dik-diks prefer leaves and grass. They will sometimes enjoy fruits, flowers, and pods. They usually do not require much water because they are very small. However, if water is available, they will occasionally drink a little.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.541"><![CDATA[Tanzania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.541"><![CDATA[The ideal place to live is dry steppes covered in shrubs, such as those in Tanzania.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.542"><![CDATA[Hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.542"><![CDATA[Forward! These small antelopes are good at moving on their feet and are almost always on the run. They run zigzagging to hide behind bushes and warn other animals of predators with "dsik-dsik" sounds.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.543"><![CDATA[Plush dik-dik]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.543"><![CDATA[Dik-diks are so adorable. Even the males, who have small horns that tilt slightly backwards, are not scary at all.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.544"><![CDATA[Dwarf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.544"><![CDATA[Little dik-diks are agile, nimble and of course very cautious. They drink dew drops from the grass and have cute little snouts. They are miniature versions of large antelopes!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.545"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.545"><![CDATA[Geckos like to eat arthropods like spiders, insects, and snakes. They will also snack on overripe fruit, nectar, and pollen. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.546"><![CDATA[Madagascar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.546"><![CDATA[The colorful geckos live in the rainforests and banana plantations of eastern Madagascar. Their habitat is threatened by hotels and insecticides.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.547"><![CDATA[Foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.547"><![CDATA[The colorful Madagascar felsuma has sticky feet, which means it can run even on very smooth surfaces like glass.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.548"><![CDATA[Plush gecko]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.548"><![CDATA[The color and pattern of geckos change as they mature. When threatened, they simply remove their tail and twitch to confuse their enemies.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.549"><![CDATA[Sunglasses]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.549"><![CDATA[Geckos like to lie in the sun on the roofs of huts and houses. They need a lot of light and like high humidity.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.550"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.550"><![CDATA[Capybaras like to fill their bellies with fresh grass from the land. They'll occasionally eat a water plant or two. And because they're so big, they have to eat a lot.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.551"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.551"><![CDATA[You'll find these cheerful creatures in South America near swamps, ponds, and mangrove forests!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.552"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.552"><![CDATA[The capybara is able to run quite fast, but when it runs, it usually jumps into the water because it can swim even better.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.553"><![CDATA[Plush capybara]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.553"><![CDATA[Capybaras communicate with barking sounds, purring, or screeching when they are afraid, and chirping and grunting when they are happy.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.554"><![CDATA[Wood]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.554"><![CDATA[They hide in bushes and thickets before the hot day. Capybaras are active at dusk.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.555"><![CDATA[Chinese starfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.555"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.556"><![CDATA[Barbados cherry]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.556"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.557"><![CDATA[Lime]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.557"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.558"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.558"><![CDATA[The spectacled bear will eat anything it can get its hands on, but it prefers fruits from cacti and bromeliads. From time to time, it will indulge in fresh shoots or insects.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.559"><![CDATA[Peru]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.559"><![CDATA[The spectacled bear lives in the tropical Andes, where it has plenty of space to live. It likes to romp in the humid rainforest, which offers it a rich supply of food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.560"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.560"><![CDATA[Like many other bears, the spectacled bear is plantigrade, with short claws and longer front legs, which are ideal for climbing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.561"><![CDATA[Spectacled teddy bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.561"><![CDATA[Mother and father bears care for their cubs in a den. Depending on food availability and seasonal conditions, up to four cubs may be born.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.562"><![CDATA[Glasses]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.562"><![CDATA[The spectacled bear gets its name from the white markings on its face: Some look like they're wearing glasses, while others have completely white noses. Very stylish!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.563"><![CDATA[Omnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.563"><![CDATA[Bandicoots have a mixed diet that includes insects and small animals. They don't even need any water. They get everything they need from their food!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.564"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.564"><![CDATA[When it gets dark in the Australian outback, bandicoots come out to play, only to return to their burrows before dawn.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.565"><![CDATA[Bandicoot's paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.565"><![CDATA[Bandicoots have very strong claws that they use to dig their burrows. They can disappear under sandy soil in a matter of minutes!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.566"><![CDATA[Plush bandicoot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.566"><![CDATA[Zoo visitors are sure to love these cuddly bandicoots!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.567"><![CDATA[Shovel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.567"><![CDATA[Get out your shovel and dig a big hole!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.568"><![CDATA[Fruit]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.568"><![CDATA[These birds prefer tasty fruits, insects, mushrooms or eggs. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.569"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.569"><![CDATA[From Aborigines to didgeridoos - in Queensland, Australia, tourists are not only treated to tongue twisters, but also to amazing sights.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.570"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.570"><![CDATA[The southern cassowary looks harmless, but its claws can cut through flesh like butter.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.571"><![CDATA[Plush cassowary]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.571"><![CDATA[Cassowaries are monogamous, and males build nests of grass and leaves on the ground.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.572"><![CDATA[Helmet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.572"><![CDATA[This bird is stubborn, literally - its helmet perfectly protects it from impacts.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.573"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.573"><![CDATA[The maned dog hunts small rodents using its long legs. Armadillos and birds are also part of its diet. Together with fruit, it really enjoys such a meal!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.574"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.574"><![CDATA[The maned dog prefers to roam in grasslands, scrubland, and wet areas such as swamps.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.575"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.575"><![CDATA[The maned dog sneaks up on its tiptoes after its prey. Insects, birds, and rodents have no chance of escaping!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.576"><![CDATA[Plush maned dog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.576"><![CDATA[Usually three cubs are born. The male helps with the raising, but then they go their separate ways.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.577"><![CDATA[Brush]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.577"><![CDATA[The maned dog's mane is reddish-brown and very distinctive. The tip of the tail, the inside of the ears and the neck are white. Brush him thoroughly!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.578"><![CDATA[Carnivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.578"><![CDATA[The anaconda can eat a lot of food thanks to its elastic skin and ability to relax its jaw. Enjoy your meal!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.579"><![CDATA[Colombia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.579"><![CDATA[Anacondas love warm, humid places, which is why they thrive in the tropical rainforests of South America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.580"><![CDATA[Anaconda footprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.580"><![CDATA[Like smaller snakes, anacondas crawl on land and in water by sliding their long bodies.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.581"><![CDATA[Plush anaconda]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.581"><![CDATA[Zoo visitors have a unique opportunity to hug an anaconda - not the other way around!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.582"><![CDATA[Scale]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.582"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, the anaconda sheds its skin and gets a new, modern look!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.583"><![CDATA[Primeval forest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.583"><![CDATA[The rainforest is full of uncontrollable growth, huge trees, climbing plants and wild animals. Sometimes even completely overgrown ruins are found. How exciting!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.584"><![CDATA[Liana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.584"><![CDATA[Liana is not a separate genus of plants, but a climbing plant of various plant species. It is also a popular means of transportation for monkeys and Tarzan.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.585"><![CDATA[Compass]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.585"><![CDATA[Right, left, up, down - the jungle can be very dense and it's not easy to find your way around. So don't forget your compass!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.586"><![CDATA[Oil lamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.586"><![CDATA[Even in daylight, it can be dark in the jungle. We have an oil lamp for those occasions!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.587"><![CDATA[Fly swatter]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.587"><![CDATA[The jungle without insect repellent can be very unpleasant. Can a fly swatter really help us?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.588"><![CDATA[Rocks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.588"><![CDATA[Great rocky landscapes repeatedly inspire our imagination: How did these rocks get here? Usually by erosion or glacial movement, but sometimes it's stories and legends.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.589"><![CDATA[Ice axe]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.589"><![CDATA[Cliffs or steep, rocky slopes are popular climbing terrains for all adventurers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.590"><![CDATA[Stone statue]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.590"><![CDATA[A skilled sculptor can carve the most beautiful works from large boulders.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.591"><![CDATA[Bird's nest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.591"><![CDATA[Jagged rocks and difficult terrain provide sufficient protection for birds and are also safe for nesting.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.592"><![CDATA[Stonehenge]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.592"><![CDATA[Stonehenge is one of the oldest examples of stone construction. Many mysteries, legends and stories surround this circle of standing stones.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.593"><![CDATA[Wasteland]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.593"><![CDATA[Contrary to expectations, there are many species of animals that crawl across the hostile environment of the wasteland. The soil is not fertile, but it provides a haven for animals that have adapted well there.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.594"><![CDATA[The little girl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.594"><![CDATA[The lights are only a few centimeters long and only light up for a few seconds.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.595"><![CDATA[Oil pump]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.595"><![CDATA[Thriving landscapes are very often completely destroyed by modern technologies.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.596"><![CDATA[Oil canister]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.596"><![CDATA[A single drop of oil can contaminate 600 liters of water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.597"><![CDATA[Salty hill]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.597"><![CDATA[Salinity is a natural cause of desert development.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.598"><![CDATA[Savanna]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.598"><![CDATA[The savanna is located between tropical rainforests and deserts. The term means something like "distant plain".]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.599"><![CDATA[Flames]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.599"><![CDATA[Fires play an important role in the savanna ecosystem: parts of dead plants are removed and nutrients are returned through a natural process known as remineralization.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.600"><![CDATA[Africa]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.600"><![CDATA[The most famous savanna is in Africa and is called Serengeti.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.601"><![CDATA[Termite construction]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.601"><![CDATA[By far the most common savanna herbivores belong to the insect family. Ants and termites clean the savanna.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.602"><![CDATA[Baobab]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.602"><![CDATA[The baobab can store a large amount of water. Who would have thought that the trunk can measure up to 20 meters in circumference!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.603"><![CDATA[Sugar Land]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.603"><![CDATA[Do your animals have sweet tooths too? They'll love Sugar Land! Don't forget to brush their teeth!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.604"><![CDATA[Chocolate]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.604"><![CDATA[Cocoa butter melts quickly in your mouth. Chocolate has been around as a delicious snack since around 1500 BC.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.605"><![CDATA[Marshmallows]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.605"><![CDATA[Baked, toasted or just plain - this soft chewy candy is a big hit, especially in the US. In the past, it was made from plant products and was considered a medicine!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.606"><![CDATA[Chocolate fountain]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.606"><![CDATA[Sugar Land - a land full of milk, honey, and flowing chocolate! You'll also find fruit here - your animals' favorite snack.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.607"><![CDATA[Flying muffin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.607"><![CDATA[What's flying around here? A muffin? A delicious treat for your animals - it falls straight into their mouths!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.608"><![CDATA[Tundra]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.608"><![CDATA[The tundra is permanently covered in frost, so-called permafrost (e.g. in polar regions), so don't forget to dress appropriately.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.609"><![CDATA[Peat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.609"><![CDATA[Peat is composed of rotted plant remains. It occurs in swamps and is often used as fuel.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.610"><![CDATA[Shovel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.610"><![CDATA[The tundra has soft swamps and is also covered in hard permafrost. A good shovel for every type of soil is a definite must.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.611"><![CDATA[Hood]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.611"><![CDATA[Inuit people often live in the tundra. They are easily recognized by their warm, furry hoods.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.612"><![CDATA[Moss]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.612"><![CDATA[Mosses, lichens, and shrubs grow in the tundra. These plants are very hardy and can survive in any environment.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.613"><![CDATA[Desert]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.613"><![CDATA[Searing heat, changing mirages and distant oases: The desert has always served as a source of inspiration, and not only for the stories from the collection One Thousand and One Nights!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.614"><![CDATA[Dune]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.614"><![CDATA[There are many different types of dunes, such as shifting sand dunes. The longest sand dune is Abu Muharek, which is approximately 600 kilometers long.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.615"><![CDATA[Can]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.615"><![CDATA[Rain showers are rare in the desert, but when it does rain, it really pours!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.616"><![CDATA[Pie chart]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.616"><![CDATA[Deserts, are they rare phenomena? Really? All deserts together may cover one-fifth of the Earth's surface.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.617"><![CDATA[Cactus]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.617"><![CDATA[Thanks to their ability to retain water, cacti can survive very long periods of drought.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.618"><![CDATA[Terrarium]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.618"><![CDATA[What's so great about a terrarium? It allows you to raise exotic animals in their own habitat. Aren't these miniature worlds absolutely fascinating?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.619"><![CDATA[Heat lamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.619"><![CDATA[Exotic environments need a constant supply of air. Most terrariums require a humid and warm climate.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.620"><![CDATA[Cave]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.620"><![CDATA[Reptiles and other small animals like to retreat to secluded caves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.621"><![CDATA[Manual window wiper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.621"><![CDATA[The interior and exterior glass panels of terrariums must be cleaned regularly so that zoo visitors can see what is inside.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.622"><![CDATA[Photo wallpaper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.622"><![CDATA[Are animals homesick? This can't happen! Set up the right photo backdrop and they'll immediately feel like they're in their natural habitat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.623"><![CDATA[Alps]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.623"><![CDATA[Hooray for the mountain meadow! High in the mountains, your animals will love it. Quickly call them and let's go!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.624"><![CDATA[Alpine horn]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.624"><![CDATA[The Alpine horn functions like a telephone in mountain pastures. It can be heard five to ten kilometers away.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.625"><![CDATA[Cowbell]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.625"><![CDATA[There are no fences in the mountain pastures. Instead, cowbells are heard to alert farmers where their cows are grazing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.626"><![CDATA[Snowboarding]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.626"><![CDATA[Under the snow? No way! Snowboarding is a quick way to get to the valley when there's snow everywhere.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.627"><![CDATA[Walking stick]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.627"><![CDATA[The terrain in the mountains is very uneven. The pure nature is irreplaceable. A walking stick will help with stability on steep slopes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.10000"><![CDATA[Tasty cake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.10000"><![CDATA[It's hard to believe - visitors' eyes pop out of their sockets. Look what the cleaner Slavek is doing - visitors feel the gaze on their backs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.10001"><![CDATA[9 million pieces]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.10001"><![CDATA[The first year has passed and ZooMumba has almost 10 million zoo directors.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.10002"><![CDATA[A piece of cake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.10002"><![CDATA[After 12 months, there are over 65 animal species in ZooMumba! Do you have them all in your zoo?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.10003"><![CDATA[Something to eat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.10003"><![CDATA[At first, the animals at ZooMumba could only eat gummy bears and licorice snakes. But then enough was enough. The animals wanted something real to eat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.10004"><![CDATA[1 year]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.10004"><![CDATA[The story of Zoomumba began in August 2010. How time flies!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.629"><![CDATA[Tasty cake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.629"><![CDATA[It's hard to believe - visitors' eyes pop out of their sockets. Look what the cleaner Slavek is doing - visitors feel the gaze on their backs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.630"><![CDATA[One in a million]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.630"><![CDATA[At the end of the fourth year, ZooMumba has over 16 million zoo directors.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.631"><![CDATA[A piece of cake]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.631"><![CDATA[Four years and hundreds of different animals... Do you have them all in your zoo?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.632"><![CDATA[Sweets]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.632"><![CDATA[At first, the animals at ZooMumba could only eat gummy bears and licorice snakes. But then enough was enough. The animals wanted something real to eat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.633"><![CDATA[1 year]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.633"><![CDATA[The story of Zoomumba began in August 2010. How time flies!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.634"><![CDATA[Lair]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.634"><![CDATA[Many animals build dens to protect themselves from enemies. This type of housing offers safety and keeps them warm.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.635"><![CDATA[Stone Age axe]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.635"><![CDATA[It's not just animals that seek out caves to protect themselves from predators. Cavemen did the same! Caves hide many archaeological treasures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.636"><![CDATA[Stalagmite]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.636"><![CDATA[The constant dripping of water leaves behind small calcium deposits that form stalactites.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.637"><![CDATA[Bat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.637"><![CDATA[The deeper the cave, the darker it gets. Bats don't need eyes to find their way, they use sonar instead.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.638"><![CDATA[Mining helmet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.638"><![CDATA[Most caves are located in rock formations, and since rocks are constantly falling, it is wise to wear a helmet. Not only does it offer protection, but it also has a light attached to it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.639"><![CDATA[Forest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.639"><![CDATA[Forests are home to a variety of trees, shrubs and bushes. The undergrowth provides shelter for many shy animals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.640"><![CDATA[Troll]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.640"><![CDATA[The Scandinavian forests are home to several other forest dwellers. Trolls are also spotted here and there!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.641"><![CDATA[Pointer]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.641"><![CDATA[There are many things to discover in the forest. It's easy to get lost, which is why markers are necessary!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.642"><![CDATA[Krmelec]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.642"><![CDATA[In spring and summer the forest is lush with vegetation and green leaves, but in winter the soil is somewhat barren. The meadow with fresh hay is a welcome source of food for the animals during the winter season.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.643"><![CDATA[Tree trunks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.643"><![CDATA[Forests are important suppliers of wood. Many small forest creatures seek refuge among the piles of logs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.644"><![CDATA[Balloons]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.645"><![CDATA[Coast]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.645"><![CDATA[Hurray for the water! The sound of the sea can be heard in the distance between the beach and the sand dunes. Millions of microorganisms live in the muddy banks of the intertidal zone.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.646"><![CDATA[Shipwreck]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.646"><![CDATA[Rough coastlines can be very dangerous for ships. Lighthouses help them navigate. In the past, pirates took advantage of this by lighting false signals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.647"><![CDATA[SOS signal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.647"><![CDATA[What makes your heart beat faster than being shipwrecked? The sight of land, of course! The shore has saved the lives of many shipwrecked people.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.648"><![CDATA[Message in a bottle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.648"><![CDATA[No one knows when or where a bottle will appear. Some wash up right on the shore, while others sail around the globe. How exciting it is when the news finally arrives!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.649"><![CDATA[Buoy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.649"><![CDATA[Buoys mark the boundary between the bay and maritime traffic.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.650"><![CDATA[Mushroom field]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.650"><![CDATA[When mushrooms sprout, it means the soil is very fertile. Who knows what surprises await us!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.651"><![CDATA[Mushroom house]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.651"><![CDATA[In the fairy forest, mushrooms are inhabited by little dwarves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.652"><![CDATA[Mushroom pet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.652"><![CDATA[Although a mushroom has its roots in one place, it is considered part of the animal kingdom rather than the plant kingdom. It lives on organic nutrients and would definitely like to go for a walk. Why not give it a try?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.653"><![CDATA[Mushroom basket]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.653"><![CDATA[Mushroom pickers must be careful when picking mushrooms, as many are poisonous. Pick only the good ones and put them in your basket!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.654"><![CDATA[Moldy apple]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.654"><![CDATA[Mold is actually a fungus, too. Like many of its counterparts, it prefers to grow on spoiled food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.655"><![CDATA[Red slime mold]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.655"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.656"><![CDATA[Green slime mold]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.656"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.657"><![CDATA[Yellow slime mold]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.657"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.658"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.658"><![CDATA[The white-cheeked owl prefers to feast on moths, crickets, or small rodents. It searches for these delicacies from above and catches them in flight.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.659"><![CDATA[Cameroon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.659"><![CDATA[The white-cheeked shrike is native to Africa and also Cameroon. It lives in savannas, tropical moist forests or on the edges of forests.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.660"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.660"><![CDATA[The white-cheeked owl has transversely serrated claws partially covered with feathers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.661"><![CDATA[Plush owl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.661"><![CDATA[Before mating, the male calls a two-syllable "hoo-hoo." The contact call sounds like "twee-twee," and the young beg for food with a hiss. Cute, right?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.662"><![CDATA[He grimaced.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.662"><![CDATA[Whoa! Who's that grinning in the bushes? A white-faced owl can give a real scare in the dark!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.663"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.663"><![CDATA[These little monkeys spend half the day hunting insects, which they enjoy along with fruit.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.664"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.664"><![CDATA[These monkeys love forested areas. They swing from tree to tree and are mainly found in the Amazon and Brazil.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.665"><![CDATA[Paws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.665"><![CDATA[The squirrel monkey has very short fingers and its thumbs do not have the ability to oppose the other fingers like a human's.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.666"><![CDATA[Plush monkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.666"><![CDATA[The squirrel monkey lives in groups in perfect harmony. The young are often born in one group and at the same time.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.667"><![CDATA[Skull]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.667"><![CDATA[These monkeys have a distinctive skull-like pattern on their faces. They don't have a striking hairstyle, but they do have prominent ears. Very funny!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.668"><![CDATA[Fruit]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.668"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.669"><![CDATA[Gingerbread man]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.669"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.670"><![CDATA[Candies]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.670"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.671"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.671"><![CDATA[The savannah pig is a herbivore. It prefers to feast on grasses, tubers, and roots.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.672"><![CDATA[Tanzania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.672"><![CDATA[The savannah pig lives in the forested landscapes and savannas of Africa, south of the Sahara.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.673"><![CDATA[Hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.673"><![CDATA[When grazing, it crawls on all fours and digs into the ground, looking for all sorts of treats.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.674"><![CDATA[Plush savannah pig]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.674"><![CDATA[The savannah pig was nicknamed "Radio Africa" ​​because it often raises its tail like an antenna before attacking or escaping.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.675"><![CDATA[Delicacy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.675"><![CDATA[Did you know that the meerkat's favorite playmate is the savannah pig? They enjoy feasting on cockroaches, beetles, grubs, and worms. The only problem is that they make them a little bloated!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.676"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.676"><![CDATA[The Canada lynx feeds mainly on small mammals, but its favorite prey is the snowshoe hare. The two populations interact with each other.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.677"><![CDATA[Canada]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.677"><![CDATA[The Canada lynx loves forested and snowy areas. It feels at home in Canada, mainly because there are many snowshoe hares there.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.678"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.678"><![CDATA[Its hind legs are longer than its front legs, which makes it look quite funny. It also has a lot of hair on its paws, allowing it to walk on snow with ease.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.679"><![CDATA[Plush lynx]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.679"><![CDATA[The young ones hide under tree roots and in thickets of fallen wood. From their hiding places they have a good view of the surroundings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.680"><![CDATA[Sofa cushion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.680"><![CDATA[The Canadian lynx tracks down its prey and often waits a long time before attacking. A comfortable pillow like this would really come in handy while it waits.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.681"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.681"><![CDATA[The kingfisher hunts its prey - fish, aquatic insects and tadpoles - by diving in flight. It dives headfirst into the water, its eyes open, and when it resurfaces, it soars like a rocket. Fascinating!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.682"><![CDATA[Norway]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.682"><![CDATA[The kingfisher feels at home in northern Scandinavia, where there are many freshwater sources in which to hunt. However, as a migratory bird, it can also be found in many other areas.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.683"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.683"><![CDATA[The legs of this bird change color. Young birds have dark brown legs that turn orange-red during the breeding season.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.684"><![CDATA[Plush kingfisher]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.684"><![CDATA[The monogamous kingfisher has a special mating ritual: the male hands the female a small fish with a bow. It's cute!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.685"><![CDATA[Top]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.685"><![CDATA[When feeding their young in the nest, the kingfishers circle around the nest to get to everyone. Hopefully they don't get dizzy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.686"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.686"><![CDATA[Thanks to its divided upper lip, the wombat selects grass, plants, moss, roots and mushrooms during the long evening hours.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.687"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.687"><![CDATA[Like many other Australian animals, the wombat looks funny. It is a marsupial and lives in southern and eastern Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.688"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.688"><![CDATA[With their sharp claws, they build intricate underground tunnels with comfortable dens. Who knows, maybe they even have furniture there?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.689"><![CDATA[Plush wombat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.689"><![CDATA[The female's pouch faces backwards, preventing sand from getting into it when digging. The young remain in the pouch for up to eight weeks, after which they live near their mother for a year.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.690"><![CDATA[Shield]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.690"><![CDATA[If an enemy approaches the burrow, the wombat will simply close the entrance with its back. It serves as a shield and is quite well padded thanks to its thick skin, cartilage and bones.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.691"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.691"><![CDATA[Pelicans feed mainly on fish. They have a very sophisticated way of hunting: they fly from a great height and plunge their strong beak directly into the water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.692"><![CDATA[New Guinea]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.692"><![CDATA[Pelicans are found all over the world. Outside the breeding season, they roam New Guinea.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.693"><![CDATA[Foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.693"><![CDATA[Pelicans are part of the order of copepods and waders. Their toes are connected by a webbed foot.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.694"><![CDATA[Plush pelican]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.694"><![CDATA[During mating, the male has a brightly colored face. He woos the female with a dance in which he stretches his head and inflates his esophageal sac.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.695"><![CDATA[Fishing net]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.695"><![CDATA[Pelicans use their esophageal pouch as a fishing net.\n It can hold up to 13 liters of water and of course... lots of fish!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.696"><![CDATA[Grain lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.696"><![CDATA[Peck, peck, peck. Like other chickens, silkies like to peck at grains. Their crested feathers shake nicely.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.697"><![CDATA[China]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.697"><![CDATA[According to ancient records, silk chickens, with snow-white feathers and black skin, were first seen in China.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.698"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.698"><![CDATA[The feathers of these chickens also cover their legs, which is why they look like fluffy, furry balls.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.699"><![CDATA[Plush chicken]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.699"><![CDATA[Silky hens are good foster mothers. They lay up to 80 eggs per year and are very reliable.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.700"><![CDATA[Carrot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.700"><![CDATA[During Easter, these hens would appreciate it if people ate carrots instead of their eggs so they could have more chicks!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.701"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.701"><![CDATA[Juicy grass, birch and willow leaves, lichens and mosses - this is a delicacy that musk deer certainly cannot resist.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.702"><![CDATA[Canada]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.702"><![CDATA[The musk ox feels at home in the tundra, where there is not much precipitation. And when everything starts to melt, it also finds lush vegetation there. Great!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.703"><![CDATA[Hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.703"><![CDATA[With its wide, rounded, and sharp hooves, it stomps across the tundra, scraping away snow and crushing ice.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.704"><![CDATA[Plush muskrat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.704"><![CDATA[The young are able to forage just one week after birth, but they continue to feed on their mothers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.705"><![CDATA[Musk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.705"><![CDATA[During mating season, musk oxen release a substance into their urine that smells sweet, which is where the scent gets its name and becomes a kind of trademark.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.706"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.706"><![CDATA[Dingoes prey on almost any mammal that walks on its feet, has fluffy fur or pouches. Most Australian mammals are marsupials, so you should be wary of dingos.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.707"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.707"><![CDATA[Dingoes were once quite rare and lived close to the Australian Aborigines. Today, they can be found all over Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.708"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.708"><![CDATA[Their legs are very long, with the hind feet making up a third of their hind limbs. They lack a fifth claw entirely.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.709"><![CDATA[Plush dingo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.709"><![CDATA[Dingoes live in groups and are very social, although they are mostly seen alone.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.710"><![CDATA[Kennel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.710"><![CDATA[Dingos are related to domestic dogs and are called wild dogs in Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.711"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.711"><![CDATA[It can strike its victim with its strong tentacles in 0.1 second.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.712"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.712"><![CDATA[Praying mantises live mainly in tropical and subtropical regions, where there are lots of insects. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.713"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.713"><![CDATA[The front two legs are toothed and have pointed claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.714"><![CDATA[Cuddly insect]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.714"><![CDATA[It's not uncommon for a much larger female to eat her partner after mating. Oh my!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.715"><![CDATA[Branch]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.715"><![CDATA[Most praying mantises are diurnal predators that sit for hours waiting for their food. They are difficult to spot in the grass.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.716"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.716"><![CDATA[If a macaque is dripping fruit juice from its whiskers, it means it has just enjoyed a juicy fruit. In addition to fruit, it loves leaves, buds, insects and sometimes even small vertebrates. Groats!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.717"><![CDATA[India]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.717"><![CDATA[There are only 2,500 adult macaques left in various parts of India. Help save them from extinction!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.718"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.718"><![CDATA[These good climbers spend most of their time high up in the treetops looking down!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.719"><![CDATA[Plush monkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.719"><![CDATA[Macaques live in groups of ten to twenty animals and have a strong hierarchy. They communicate with each other by screaming.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.720"><![CDATA[Lion's mane]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.720"><![CDATA[The striking lion's mane is their trademark. The tail is also very distinctive: the black tassel at the end of the tail looks like a lion's, which is why this monkey is called the "lion" macaque.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.721"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.721"><![CDATA[The ferret is an omnivore. It eats squirrels, small rodents, birds, but also berries and fruit. It can be easily tamed, which is why it is kept for hunting mice.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.722"><![CDATA[USA]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.722"><![CDATA[The ferret cat is found in many American states, but it prefers to live in dry forests and deserts with minimal vegetation and rocks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.723"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.723"><![CDATA[This raccoon sneaks around at night looking for food. The North American ferret cat has retractable claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.724"><![CDATA[Plush ferret cat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.724"><![CDATA[The ferret cat has large, purple-colored eyes, surrounded by fine fur. It looks as if it is wearing glasses, which also makes its eyes appear larger.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.725"><![CDATA[Half cougar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.725"><![CDATA[The North American Indians called it "cacomistle", which means something like "half puma".]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.726"><![CDATA[red water lily]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.726"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.727"><![CDATA[blue water lily]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.727"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.728"><![CDATA[yellow water lily]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.728"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.729"><![CDATA[red Easter bunny]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.729"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.730"><![CDATA[blue Easter bunny]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.730"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.731"><![CDATA[yellow Easter bunny]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.731"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.732"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.732"><![CDATA[Spotted hyenas have very strong jaws that can crush a turtle's shell or even very strong bones, allowing them to utilize their food very efficiently.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.733"><![CDATA[Turkey]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.733"><![CDATA[Spotted hyenas inhabit rocky mountain areas, semi-deserts, and scrub savannas.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.734"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.734"><![CDATA[Spotted hyenas walk on their toes and their front legs are slightly longer than their hind legs, which is why they have a stooped back.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.735"><![CDATA[Plush hyena]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.735"><![CDATA[They usually have 4 to 5 young and about 30 days after birth they start playing together.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.736"><![CDATA[Cow skull]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.736"><![CDATA[Hyenas not only hunt their own prey, but also feast on carrion, in other words, the remains of animals that have been torn to pieces by cheetahs, leopards, lions or tigers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.742"><![CDATA[Swamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.742"><![CDATA[Marsh plants thrive here mainly thanks to the marshy soil and vegetation that always has enough water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.743"><![CDATA[Swamp light]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.743"><![CDATA[Small, playful lights twinkle all around, dancing merrily in the swamp. Are they ghosts or atmospheric gases in flames?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.744"><![CDATA[Clay jug]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.744"><![CDATA[Archaeologists are searching the swamps for signs of ancient cultures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.745"><![CDATA[Mummy in the swamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.745"><![CDATA[In good conditions, creatures in swamps can be preserved for centuries.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.746"><![CDATA[Mud bath]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.746"><![CDATA[The mud in the marshes is highly valued for its healing properties and is often used in therapies.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.747"><![CDATA[red lantern]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.747"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.748"><![CDATA[blue lantern]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.748"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.749"><![CDATA[yellow lantern]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.749"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.750"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.750"><![CDATA[The oystercatcher's prey depends on the tides. As the water recedes, it picks clams, crabs, and insects from the bottom.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.751"><![CDATA[Faroe Islands]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.751"><![CDATA[The oystercatcher is the national bird of the Faroe Islands and is strictly protected.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.752"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.752"><![CDATA[The oystercatcher not only searches for food in the sand, but also maneuvers quickly around rocks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.753"><![CDATA[Cuddly toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.753"><![CDATA[Oystercatchers live monogamous lives and can have young even at the age of 36.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.754"><![CDATA[Billow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.754"><![CDATA[The ocean waves constantly wash up new food for them. They force open the crab's shell with their beaks and sometimes swallow the mussels whole.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.755"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.755"><![CDATA[The cormorant eats exclusively marine and freshwater fish. It lives near the coast and loves large bodies of water where it can dive for food.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.756"><![CDATA[Japan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.756"><![CDATA[The Japanese cormorant, a subspecies of cormorant, is also known as the Temminck's cormorant. It is native to East Asia, from northern Taiwan to Korea and Japan.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.757"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.757"><![CDATA[Cormorants are very good divers. They hunt underwater and have webbed feet that allow them to propel themselves forward underwater.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.758"><![CDATA[Plush cormorant]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.758"><![CDATA[Cormorants lay their eggs in colonies with thousands of other breeding pairs. They build their nests on hard-to-reach cliffs along the coast or inland in tall trees.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.759"><![CDATA[Fishing hook]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.759"><![CDATA[The cormorant has a hooked beak with which it catches its prey. It is a rival to any fisherman!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.760"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.760"><![CDATA[Green dragonfly larvae can catch prey with their mouthparts. Adult dragonflies catch mosquitoes and flies in flight.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.761"><![CDATA[Taiwan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.761"><![CDATA[Greenish-green sedges are found in many places. They feel at home in Taiwan and around watery and marshy areas.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.762"><![CDATA[Foot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.762"><![CDATA[Green-winged spiders are arthropods. Their delicate legs are dark gray to black in color.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.763"><![CDATA[Plush dragonfly]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.763"><![CDATA[Dragonflies have two lives. First as larvae in the water and then in full glory as dragonflies. Frost or pollution in the water do not have much effect on the larvae.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.764"><![CDATA[Turnover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.764"><![CDATA[Dragonflies move their wings independently. Not only can they suddenly change direction, but they can also fly backwards.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.765"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.765"><![CDATA[Ocelots hunt over a vast territory. They will eat basically anything they can find, but they prefer small prey such as rodents and rabbits.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.766"><![CDATA[Brazil]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.766"><![CDATA[Ocelots are found in Central America and the Amazon rainforest. They live in areas with a high amount of vegetation cover, but can also appear in more open areas at night.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.767"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.767"><![CDATA[Ocelots are active animals that roam over vast territories of up to 18 square kilometers. They are found at altitudes of up to 1200 meters.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.768"><![CDATA[Plush ocelot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.768"><![CDATA[They usually have only one young, which lives with its mother for up to two years.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.769"><![CDATA[Scraping rod]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.769"><![CDATA[Unlike other cat species, ocelots are not afraid of water and are excellent swimmers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.770"><![CDATA[Grass lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.770"><![CDATA[The wild boar has a very flexible upper lip, which allows it to graze even in meadows with shorter grass.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.771"><![CDATA[Tibet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.771"><![CDATA[Yaks live in the Himalayas, Mongolia, and even southern Siberia. In Tibet, people use their wool, meat, skin, milk, and even their dung, which is used as fuel.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.772"><![CDATA[Hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.772"><![CDATA[Yak hooves are quite small and strong. They have sharp tips and hard edges that allow them to descend more slowly down hills. This allows them to walk safely even on rough terrain.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.773"><![CDATA[Plush as]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.773"><![CDATA[Baby yaks can stand on their feet five to fifteen minutes after birth, after which they immediately seek their mother's udder.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.774"><![CDATA[Jumping shot]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.774"><![CDATA[Yaks like to move around. While grazing, they sometimes take a break and play fetch.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.775"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.775"><![CDATA[Coatis use their snouts to search for small invertebrates. They also eat fruit for dessert.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.776"><![CDATA[Argentina]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.776"><![CDATA[Coatis live in tropical rainforests and are widespread from the USA to Argentina.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.777"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.777"><![CDATA[Coatis scurry along the ground on their black paws, searching for food. At night, they climb trees to sleep.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.778"><![CDATA[Plush coati]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.778"><![CDATA[The young are born high in the treetops. During this period, the males search for small animals and fruit to protect their young from predators.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.779"><![CDATA[Muzzle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.779"><![CDATA[Their flexible snout reaches into all sorts of holes, nooks and crannies, where they catch their prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.780"><![CDATA[Crocodile balloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.780"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.781"><![CDATA[Kangaroo balloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.781"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.782"><![CDATA[Koala balloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.782"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.784"><![CDATA[red magic potion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.784"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.785"><![CDATA[green magic potion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.785"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.786"><![CDATA[yellow magic potion]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.786"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.787"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.787"><![CDATA[Fruit bats love to feast on nectar, pollen, and fruit, but during Halloween, these flying foxes come to life and swoop down on their victims!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.788"><![CDATA[Romania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.788"><![CDATA[As pets of the infamous Count Dracula, they can be seen all over Romania. Otherwise, they live in Africa, Asia, or Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.789"><![CDATA[Claws]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.789"><![CDATA[Fruit bats are distinguished from common bats by their claws on the second finger, which have a membranous structure extending over the fingers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.790"><![CDATA[Plush fruit bat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.790"><![CDATA[A fruit bat can live up to 30 years. They give birth to a young one once a year.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.791"><![CDATA[Blood]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.791"><![CDATA[Like werewolves, fallow deer like to drink blood sometimes. They can even smell fresh blood, uuuuaaaaaaaahhhhhh!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.792"><![CDATA[Herbivore]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.792"><![CDATA[Kashmiri goats enjoy grass, making them ideal for maintaining the landscape. The only problem is that they smell pretty bad.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.793"><![CDATA[China]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.793"><![CDATA[The Kashmir goat is originally from Tibet, but nowadays it can also be seen in Kyrgyzstan and Uzbekistan.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.794"><![CDATA[Hoof]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.794"><![CDATA[Kashmiri goats hop across the mountains and are not cold at all. They feel good in the steppes, even in extreme climatic conditions.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.795"><![CDATA[Cuddly toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.795"><![CDATA[Kashmiri goats have such fluffy, soft wool that you would love to cuddle them. Their large horns are sometimes hidden under their long ears.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.796"><![CDATA[Sweater]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.796"><![CDATA[Weavers all over the world admire this wool goat. A nice sweater made from cashmere is very luxurious and warm.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.797"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.797"><![CDATA[There are many species of birds of paradise. It is said that their appearance is determined by their diet. They all enjoy fruit, but some are very specialized, eating nutmeg, for example.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.798"><![CDATA[Papua New Guinea]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.798"><![CDATA[The bird of paradise is on the national emblem of Papua New Guinea. Birds of paradise got their name from the sailors who discovered the worlds there - a true paradise in the middle of the ocean!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.799"><![CDATA[Claw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.799"><![CDATA[Male birds of paradise perform an interesting mating dance to attract females. Hmmmm... would you like to dance too?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.800"><![CDATA[Cuddly toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.800"><![CDATA[They are extravagant, rash and incredibly colorful - birds of paradise are thrill seekers. Some are monogamous and others are polygamous - variety is the spice of life.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.801"><![CDATA[Mosaic]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.801"><![CDATA[The trademark of this bird is its magnificent plumage. Its tail feathers stand out and its body is like a dazzling mosaic of colors.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.802"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.802"><![CDATA[Seagulls love fish the most. But they will pounce on anything that looks tasty! They often take pizza, chocolate or ice cream from tourists.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.803"><![CDATA[Germany]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.803"><![CDATA[Gulls are abundant along the northern coast of Germany. They hunt worms, crustaceans and molluscs in the Wadden Sea. Every tide brings them fresh fish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.804"><![CDATA[Feet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.804"><![CDATA[Clap, clap! They have three webbed toes on each foot, which makes it easier for them to move across the muddy sand left behind at low tide.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.805"><![CDATA[Little birds]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.805"><![CDATA[The chicks are kept warm by thick down feathers. As they grow, their feathers change to those found in adults. Gulls can live up to 30 years!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.806"><![CDATA[Sailboat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.806"><![CDATA[During a coastal storm, seagulls can glide beautifully over the water in strong winds. That's beautiful!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.807"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.807"><![CDATA[Night has fallen, it's raining... the Cape cobra emerges from its burrow to hunt small mammals and reptiles. Grab it and it's gone!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.808"><![CDATA[South Africa]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.808"><![CDATA[This small snake lives in the sandy semi-desert of South Africa, where it feels warm and comfortable under the sand.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.809"><![CDATA[Footprints in the sand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.809"><![CDATA[The Cape ladder crawls its way through warm or damp sand, leaving light tracks behind. Isn't that cute?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.810"><![CDATA[Cuddly toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.810"><![CDATA[In summer, the Cape cobra lays 3 to 11 eggs, which it incubates in its hole.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.811"><![CDATA[Drill]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.811"><![CDATA[The Cape ladder digs into the ground like a drill. When threatened, it straightens and inflates its neck, but its venom is not very strong.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.812"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.812"><![CDATA[The Bércoun most enjoys eating insects, spiders, and centipedes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.813"><![CDATA[Central African Republic]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.813"><![CDATA[The African wildcat feels at home in Africa... except in the western region. For some reason, it hasn't jumped there yet.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.814"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.814"><![CDATA[Short legs and a funny gait are its most distinctive features. Who would have thought it could run so fast?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.815"><![CDATA[Stuffed animal]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.815"><![CDATA[They grow up very quickly... In just 6-10 weeks they will leave their parents and establish their own home.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.816"><![CDATA[Rings]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.816"><![CDATA[The Bércoun is monogamous and stays with its chosen partner for the rest of its life. That's romantic!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.817"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.817"><![CDATA[The striped mongoose feeds on small insects, reptiles, and birds, which it picks from the ground and trees with its long claws.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.818"><![CDATA[Eritrea]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.818"><![CDATA[The savannas and grasslands in the central-eastern zone of Africa stretching from Eritrea provide them not only with a home but also with abundant prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.819"><![CDATA[Paw]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.819"><![CDATA[The striped mongoose lives in a variety of hiding places. It makes its home in rocks, bushes, gorges, and even termite mounds!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.820"><![CDATA[Cuddly toy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.820"><![CDATA[The striped mongoose is very social and lives in groups of about 20 individuals. Both males and females live together and have a hierarchy based on age.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.821"><![CDATA[Mosaic]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.821"><![CDATA[The pack is matriarchal and all members are taken care of, especially the young and old.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.822"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.822"><![CDATA[Crabs feed primarily on algae, but they will also feast on mollusks, worms, sponges, and even other crustaceans.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.823"><![CDATA[Norway]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.823"><![CDATA[Crabs are found in every ocean in the world, both in fresh water and on land. They have even been found in smoking volcanic vents or climbing trees!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.824"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.824"><![CDATA[Most crabs walk sideways due to the direction of their leg joints, but some move forward or backward.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.825"><![CDATA[Plush crab]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.825"><![CDATA[The hard shell of the crab prevents them from growing, so young crabs must molt 6 or 7 times in their first year. As adults, they only molt once or twice a year.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.826"><![CDATA[Chatterbox]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.826"><![CDATA[Crabs use their claws for a variety of purposes including nutrition, defense, and mating. If they lose a claw or leg, they will grow new ones!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.827"><![CDATA[red candle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.827"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.828"><![CDATA[blue candle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.828"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.829"><![CDATA[yellow candle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.829"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.830"><![CDATA[Red teddy bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.830"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.831"><![CDATA[Blue teddy bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.831"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.832"><![CDATA[Yellow teddy bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.832"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.833"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.833"><![CDATA[The blue-footed booby is quite picky about fish. Its favorite foods are sardines, anchovies, and mackerel.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.834"><![CDATA[Ecuador]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.834"><![CDATA[The blue-footed booby is found along the Pacific coast of Central America. It is a purely marine bird that uses land for breeding.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.835"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.835"><![CDATA[The blue legs play a role during the courtship ritual. Males display their legs to females, who then evaluate them and choose their mate.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.836"><![CDATA[Plush blue-footed booby]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.836"><![CDATA[Its name comes from the Spanish word "bobo", which means clumsy or stupid, because that's how it moves on land.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.837"><![CDATA[Blue socks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.837"><![CDATA[The blue-footed booby is a large bird. The female is larger than the male and can grow up to 90 cm tall and have a wingspan of up to 1.5 meters!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.838"><![CDATA[Blue chocolate bunny]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.838"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.839"><![CDATA[Green chocolate bunny]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.839"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.840"><![CDATA[Red chocolate bunny]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.840"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.841"><![CDATA[Pile of Easter eggs]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.841"><![CDATA[A nice collection of Easter eggs. In the past, painted chicken eggs were used. Nowadays, chocolate eggs are more common.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.842"><![CDATA[Dotted egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.842"><![CDATA[Previously, painting was not only done on chicken eggs, but also on ostrich eggs, and even an ostrich egg that was 60,000 years old was found!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.843"><![CDATA[Star Egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.843"><![CDATA[Egg hunts are a popular tradition around the world. Children win prizes for collecting the most eggs or finding the smallest or largest egg.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.844"><![CDATA[Striped egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.844"><![CDATA[In some Slavic countries, it is a custom to symbolically whip the backs of girls and women from the neighborhood and pour water over them, for which boys win ribbons and eggs. It is said that this will increase their beauty and health.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.845"><![CDATA[Painted egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.845"><![CDATA[Egg dancing is a traditional game in which eggs are placed on the ground and people try to dance around them without breaking any.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.846"><![CDATA[Rainbow egg]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.846"><![CDATA[Easter eggs specially adapted for visually impaired children to participate in the Easter hunt. The eggs beep or play a melody.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.847"><![CDATA[Plant lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.847"><![CDATA[The dromedary mainly eats desert plants. It can store up to 36 kilos of fat in its hump, which gradually decomposes and allows it to survive in the desert.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.848"><![CDATA[Mauritania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.848"><![CDATA[The dromedary has not existed in the wild for 2,000 years, but occasionally a stray one can be found.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.849"><![CDATA[Hoofprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.849"><![CDATA[Dromedaries usually roam freely in herds of up to 20 individuals, mostly females led by a single male.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.850"><![CDATA[Plush dromedary]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.850"><![CDATA[After a 15-month gestation period, a single calf is born. The female cares for the calf for two years.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.851"><![CDATA[A drop of water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.851"><![CDATA[The dromedary has adapted to life in the desert and can tolerate more than 30% water loss. This means that it only needs to drink once every 10 to 15 days.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.852"><![CDATA[Plant lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.852"><![CDATA[Like other antelopes, the greater kudu likes to feast on leaves and grass and sometimes even tangerines and oranges.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.853"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.853"><![CDATA[The greater kudu roams throughout southern Africa. It likes populated areas and seeks food and safety in forests, abandoned fields and pastures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.854"><![CDATA[Hoofprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.854"><![CDATA[The horns of a greater kudu are fully curled by the age of six. If they were straightened, they would measure 120 cm or more!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.855"><![CDATA[Plush large kudu]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.855"><![CDATA[The greater kudu usually has only one young, which hides in the vegetation from predators for several weeks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.856"><![CDATA[Jumping pole]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.856"><![CDATA[Despite its size, the greater kudu is a good jumper and can even jump over a 3-meter fence!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.857"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.857"><![CDATA[The spotted woodpecker is a solitary predator that hunts insects, small mammals, birds, and snakes at night. It also eats vegetables and fruits.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.858"><![CDATA[Tasmania]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.858"><![CDATA[The spotted kunoichi is mainly known in Tasmania, and an attempt to reintroduce it into the wild has recently begun in Australia.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.859"><![CDATA[Paw print]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.859"><![CDATA[Each spotted marten has up to 5 different dens, which it lives in alternately. Each den has several dug holes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.860"><![CDATA[Plush spotted marten]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.860"><![CDATA[Civets are marsupials, which means that females care for their young in a pouch on their front.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.861"><![CDATA[Polka dot shirt]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.861"><![CDATA[The kunovci are black or golden brown in color, but all have distinctive white dots on their backs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.862"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.862"><![CDATA[Dolphins feed on fish and squid, but larger dolphin species such as killer whales feed on smaller mammals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.863"><![CDATA[Shallow water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.863"><![CDATA[Most dolphins prefer warmer tropical waters, but some species of dolphin can also be found in cold waters. Some dolphins have even found their way into rivers.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.864"><![CDATA[Tail fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.864"><![CDATA[The dolphin is very active and social. Its tail fin allows it to make long leaps above the surface.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.865"><![CDATA[Plush dolphin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.865"><![CDATA[The young are usually born in spring and summer and stay with their mother for a long time.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.866"><![CDATA[Bulb]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.866"><![CDATA[Dolphins are very intelligent. They learn, cooperate and grieve together.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.867"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.867"><![CDATA[The sperm whale dives to a depth of 2 kilometers, where it searches for medium-sized squid. It also feeds on octopuses and fish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.868"><![CDATA[Deep water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.868"><![CDATA[The sperm whale lives in the ocean. Like all whales, the sperm whale must surface to breathe.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.869"><![CDATA[Tail fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.869"><![CDATA[The sperm whale has the largest brain of any animal in the world - five times larger than a human brain!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.870"><![CDATA[Giant sperm whale plush]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.870"><![CDATA[Sperm whales reproduce slowly. Females give birth once every 4 to 20 years and care for their young for up to 10 years.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.871"><![CDATA[Tooth]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.871"><![CDATA[Each sperm whale tooth weighs up to 1 kilo, but they are not needed to catch or eat squid.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.872"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.872"><![CDATA[The giant squid feeds on deep-sea fish or smaller squid, capturing its prey with its long tentacles.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.873"><![CDATA[Deep water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.873"><![CDATA[The giant squid lives deep in the ocean, which is why it grows to such large sizes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.874"><![CDATA[Tentacle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.874"><![CDATA[The giant squid has the largest eye of any living creature, measuring up to 27 cm in diameter with a pupil of up to 9 cm. Thanks to its eyes, it can detect even the slightest light on the ocean floor.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.875"><![CDATA[Giant octopus plush]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.875"><![CDATA[Genetic research has shown that there is little difference between octopuses, suggesting that there is only one species in the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.876"><![CDATA[Jumper]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.876"><![CDATA[The inside of the tentacles is covered with suction cups, which are lined with so-called "teeth". Thanks to them, it repels predators, especially sperm whales.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.877"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.877"><![CDATA[Marlin feed on fish such as mackerel and tuna. They use their long, sword-like tentacles to catch fish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.878"><![CDATA[Shallow water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.878"><![CDATA[Marlin prefer warmer water near the surface. They are migratory and follow warm water currents.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.879"><![CDATA[Tail fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.879"><![CDATA[Fishermen must prepare for a great struggle when fishing. Writer Ernest Hemingway writes about one such struggle in his book "The Old Man and the Sea."]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.880"><![CDATA[Plush marlin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.880"><![CDATA[Females are much larger than males - up to 4 times! They lay up to a million eggs at a time, but only one of them reaches adulthood.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.881"><![CDATA[Rocket]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.881"><![CDATA[Blue marlin is one of the fastest fish in the ocean and can reach speeds of up to 100 km per hour!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.882"><![CDATA[Insect lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.882"><![CDATA[The clownfish feeds mainly on plankton in the water, but will also enjoy the undigested food of its hosts.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.883"><![CDATA[Surface water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.883"><![CDATA[Clownfish prefer warm, shallow water around coral reefs and shallow lagoons. They need anemones to survive!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.884"><![CDATA[Tail fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.884"><![CDATA[Before the clownfish swims into the anemone, it dances in front of it to acclimatize. The anemone provides it with food and safety. In return, the clownfish removes parasites from it.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.885"><![CDATA[Plush clown with eyes]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.885"><![CDATA[All clownfish are born male at birth. They have the ability to change their sex to become the leader female in the group.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.886"><![CDATA[Aquarium]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.886"><![CDATA[The clownfish is the most popular aquarium fish, especially after becoming famous in Hollywood. Due to their hunting, clownfish are losing their population in the wild.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.887"><![CDATA[Insect lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.887"><![CDATA[Jellyfish feed on plankton, eggs, crustaceans, and even other jellyfish - basically anything their tentacles can grab.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.888"><![CDATA[Shallow water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.888"><![CDATA[Jellyfish are ubiquitous. They live in every sea, ocean, and lake in the world. It is estimated that there are over 10,000 different species.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.889"><![CDATA[Jacket]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.889"><![CDATA[Jellyfish are invertebrates, meaning they have no bony structure. If a jellyfish is cut in two, it can regenerate into two new organisms - just like an earthworm.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.890"><![CDATA[Plush jellyfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.890"><![CDATA[Jellyfish lay eggs every day. The egg develops into a larva, which then develops into a polyp - a mouth opening surrounded by tentacles. Over time, the polyp becomes a jellyfish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.891"><![CDATA[Bottle of water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.891"><![CDATA[Jellyfish are almost entirely made of water, with certain species containing between 95 and 98% water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.892"><![CDATA[Shellfish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.892"><![CDATA[The four-toothed catfish prefers invertebrates and algae. Large four-toothed cats can crack open clams, mussels, and clams with their large beaks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.893"><![CDATA[Surface water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.893"><![CDATA[Most species live near the coast and estuaries of marine waters, but a few species live exclusively in freshwater.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.894"><![CDATA[Tail fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.894"><![CDATA[The quadruped moves very slowly, but is capable of sprinting at breakneck speeds. It has excellent eyesight, which helps it escape predators and prepare for defense.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.895"><![CDATA[Plush four-toothed cat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.895"><![CDATA[Reproduction occurs on the surface of the water. The males push the females to the surface and the eggs float away.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.896"><![CDATA[Balloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.896"><![CDATA[The four-toothed fish inflates itself by filling its stomach with water. It sticks out its spines, making itself less attractive to predators.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.897"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.897"><![CDATA[Don't believe all those tales that the kraken feasts on lost sailors. The Kraken in Waterworld has fish on its menu.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.898"><![CDATA[Deep water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.898"><![CDATA[The Kraken lives on the ocean floor, from where it emerges to capture its prey. It prefers the cold waters around Norway and Greenland.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.899"><![CDATA[Tentacle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.899"><![CDATA[The exact size of the kraken is unknown, but its tentacles can wrap around an entire ship, suggesting it is much larger than a giant squid.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.900"><![CDATA[Plush kraken]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.900"><![CDATA[There is speculation that the kraken does not reproduce and that only two individuals exist. Both were reportedly sighted in the same location in the Greenland Sea.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.901"><![CDATA[Huge eye]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.901"><![CDATA[Like the giant squid, the kraken has large eyes with which it searches for prey. Encountering one in the deep ocean would be terrifying for any diver!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.902"><![CDATA[Ice mass]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.902"><![CDATA[Dress warmly because it is quite cold here. Ice masses can be found at both poles, where they form the "land" of vast expanses of ice.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.903"><![CDATA[Ice drill]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.903"><![CDATA[For hundreds of years, people have fished by drilling a hole in the ice. With this drill, you can remove the ice ring and then put it back in place.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.904"><![CDATA[Skate]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.904"><![CDATA[Skating began in Finland 3,000 years ago. Since then, skating has become popular all over the world. People skate not only for fun, but it is also a practical way to get from place to place.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.905"><![CDATA[Ice cube]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.905"><![CDATA[The first ice machine was built in the 19th century as a means of cooling hospital rooms. Before long, people were putting ice cubes in their drinks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.906"><![CDATA[Glacier]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.906"><![CDATA[Only a tenth of the iceberg is visible above the water surface. The tip of an iceberg can be up to 75 meters high above the water surface. This means that the largest icebergs can be up to 750 meters underwater!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.907"><![CDATA[Swimming pool]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.907"><![CDATA[Almost every animal in the world (including humans) prefers to bathe in water during hot weather.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.908"><![CDATA[Guard]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.908"><![CDATA[When boats are tied together, these plastic protectors are needed to be placed between them so that they don't constantly bang into each other and cause damage.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.909"><![CDATA[Sediment]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.909"><![CDATA[Underwater equipment accumulates deposits containing dirt, rust and even crustaceans! The equipment must therefore be cleaned regularly to prevent it from breaking.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.910"><![CDATA[Network]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.910"><![CDATA[Fishing nets have been used for thousands of years. Although the material they are made of has changed over time, the principle remains the same.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.911"><![CDATA[Node]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.911"><![CDATA[This nautical knot is simple but very useful for tying boats to poles. It is also commonly used in mountaineering.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.912"><![CDATA[Pirate's Cove]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.912"><![CDATA[We usually imagine pirates as described by Robert Louis Stevenson in his book Treasure Island.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.913"><![CDATA[Eye patch]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.913"><![CDATA[People usually imagine a pirate with an eye patch. According to the book, other accessories include a wooden leg and a parrot.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.914"><![CDATA[Hook]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.914"><![CDATA[This hook is used to attach a rope to another object. Pirates use it to capture an enemy ship, which they then pull to get on board.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.915"><![CDATA[Jolly Roger]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.915"><![CDATA[Pirates only fly a jolly roger flag when they plan to attack another ship. The most famous flag depicts a skull and crossbones, but originally each pirate captain had their own design.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.916"><![CDATA[Treasure map]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.916"><![CDATA[The map marked X, which leads to the treasure, comes from the book Treasure Island.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.917"><![CDATA[Coral reef]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.917"><![CDATA[The largest and most famous is the Great Barrier Reef off Australia, but coral reefs can be found in warmer seas and oceans around the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.918"><![CDATA[Old tire]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.918"><![CDATA[Coral reefs are home to 25% of marine life. In an effort to preserve nature, artificial reefs have been built around the world from various materials, such as old tires.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.919"><![CDATA[Coral jewelry]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.919"><![CDATA[Beautiful jewelry can be made from coral material. In the interest of coral conservation, jewelry has been made less recently.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.920"><![CDATA[Coral skeleton]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.920"><![CDATA[Corals are not plants, but invertebrate animals (like jellyfish). Corals secrete calcium carbonate, which forms a solid skeleton, and together they build reefs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.921"><![CDATA[Sickle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.921"><![CDATA[Coral has been mined for centuries and is used for various purposes. However, over-mining threatens corals, which is why they are internationally protected.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.922"><![CDATA[Caribbean island]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.922"><![CDATA[The Caribbean is the region east of Mexico that includes seas and islands. There are over 700 islands in the Caribbean, and they are all beautiful.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.923"><![CDATA[Palm leaf]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.923"><![CDATA[The Caribbean is located in a tropical region where trade winds blow, making this climate suitable for all kinds of plant species.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.924"><![CDATA[Sun]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.924"><![CDATA[The Caribbean is sunny and warm all year round, with minimal temperature variations, making it a popular destination for people from all over the world.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.925"><![CDATA[Bermuda Triangle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.925"><![CDATA[This hypothetical triangle stretches from Miami to San Juan and Bermuda. Since the 1950s, the region has been associated with mysterious phenomena involving the disappearance of ships and planes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.926"><![CDATA[Coconut]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.926"><![CDATA[Coconut palms are found in tropical regions around the world. Coconuts are used for many purposes. And most importantly, they taste good!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.927"><![CDATA[Expedition tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.927"><![CDATA[For centuries, people have been diving and searching for food and treasure underwater. Diving equipment has undergone many innovations.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.928"><![CDATA[Diving light]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.928"><![CDATA[The deeper you dive, the darker it gets! These waterproof lights provide visibility in deep waters and watery caves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.929"><![CDATA[Remote control]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.929"><![CDATA[Various remote-controlled machines are used during diving operations. They have lights, cameras, and detection or other devices attached to them. They are usually used to explore new areas.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.930"><![CDATA[Hand hook]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.930"><![CDATA[Although this hook is associated with pirates, it was previously used as a replacement for amputated hands, most famously worn by Captain Hook from the film Peter Pan.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.931"><![CDATA[Titanic]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.931"><![CDATA[The Titanic sank on its maiden voyage in 1912. The wreck was found in 1985, and thousands of artifacts have been recovered since then.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.932"><![CDATA[Fish lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.932"><![CDATA[Some killer whales hunt large fish such as salmon and herring, while others hunt sharks and rays.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.933"><![CDATA[Shallow water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.933"><![CDATA[Killer whales are found all over the world, but they are most common around Scandinavia, the North Pacific, and around Antarctica.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.934"><![CDATA[Tail fin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.934"><![CDATA[Despite years of research, little is known about the movements and migrations of killer whales. Killer whales travel all over the world, making them difficult to track.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.935"><![CDATA[Plush killer whale]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.935"><![CDATA[Killer whales can live up to 90 years, similar to humans. Females give birth to one calf approximately every 5 years.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.936"><![CDATA[Movie poster]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.936"><![CDATA[After Hollywood showed everyone the life of killer whales in captivity, there was huge pressure to release them back into the wild.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.937"><![CDATA[Insect lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.937"><![CDATA[The seahorse feeds on small crustaceans. Thanks to its excellent camouflage skills, it is able to ambush its unsuspecting prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.938"><![CDATA[Surface water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.938"><![CDATA[The seahorse is most often found in shallow water or coral reefs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.939"><![CDATA[Prehensile tail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.939"><![CDATA[The seahorse measures 1.5 to 35 cm. It moves using its dorsal fin.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.940"><![CDATA[Plush seahorse]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.940"><![CDATA[Courtship between seahorses lasts for several days, after which the female deposits her eggs in a pouch on the male's body. The male cares for them until they hatch, then releases them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.941"><![CDATA[Anchor]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.941"><![CDATA[The seahorse uses its tail as a counterweight to maintain an upright posture. It also uses it to grab onto plants or coral tendrils to ambush its prey.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.942"><![CDATA[Green starfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.942"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.943"><![CDATA[Purple starfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.943"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.944"><![CDATA[Orange starfish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.944"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.945"><![CDATA[Red vegetables]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.945"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.946"><![CDATA[Green vegetables]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.946"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.947"><![CDATA[Yellow vegetables]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.947"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.948"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.948"><![CDATA[Bonobos prefer to enjoy fruit, but as omnivores they also like leaves, honey, eggs, small animals, or insects.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.949"><![CDATA[Democratic Republic of the Congo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.949"><![CDATA[Bonobos are an endangered species and are found only in the Congo. Unfortunately, they face many human threats, such as hunting.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.950"><![CDATA[Handprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.950"><![CDATA[Like chimpanzees, bonobos are closely related to humans, as can be seen in their hands with four fingers and a thumb.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.951"><![CDATA[Plush bonobo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.951"><![CDATA[Bonobos live in a matriarchal society. Females give birth every 5 to 6 years and care for their young for up to 5 years.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.952"><![CDATA[The birds and the bees]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.952"><![CDATA[Bonobos are the only animals besides humans that mate face to face and enjoy sexual intercourse for pleasure as well as reproduction.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.953"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.953"><![CDATA[Cockatoos mainly enjoy seeds, fruits and vegetables. Thanks to their strong beaks, they can open seeds.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.954"><![CDATA[Australia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.954"><![CDATA[Cockatoos are found in Australasia. They can be found in a variety of habitats – each species has its own preferred home.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.955"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.955"><![CDATA[Cockatoos share many characteristics with other parrot species, such as strongly curved beaks and zygodactyl feet.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.956"><![CDATA[Plush cockatoo]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.956"><![CDATA[Cockatoos are monogamous and mating pairs remain together for many years. Unlike many birds, they do not start mating until they are several years old and they only care for their young for a year.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.957"><![CDATA[Fan]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.957"><![CDATA[The cockatoo raises its magnificent crest when landing after a flight and during courtship. Both males and females have crests.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.963"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.963"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.964"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.964"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.965"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.965"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.966"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.966"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.967"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.967"><![CDATA[all]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.968"><![CDATA[Blue bottle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.968"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.969"><![CDATA[Orange bottle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.969"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.970"><![CDATA[Purple bottle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.970"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.971"><![CDATA[Plant lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.971"><![CDATA[Like other antelopes, the greater kudu likes to feast on leaves and grass and sometimes even tangerines and oranges.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.972"><![CDATA[Botswana]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.972"><![CDATA[The greater kudu roams throughout southern Africa. It likes populated areas and seeks food and safety in forests, abandoned fields and pastures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.973"><![CDATA[Hoofprint]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.973"><![CDATA[Despite its size, the greater kudu is a good jumper and can even jump over a 3-meter fence!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.974"><![CDATA[Plush large kudu]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.974"><![CDATA[The greater kudu usually has only one young, which hides in the vegetation from predators for several weeks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.975"><![CDATA[Corkscrew]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.975"><![CDATA[The horns of a greater kudu are fully curled by the age of six. If they were straightened, they would measure 120 cm or more!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.976"><![CDATA[Yellow gingerbread man]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.976"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.977"><![CDATA[Red gingerbread man]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.977"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.978"><![CDATA[Green gingerbread man]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.978"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.979"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.979"><![CDATA[Owls are excellent nocturnal hunters and feed mostly on small mammals and insects, which they can see thanks to their excellent night vision.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.980"><![CDATA[Germany]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.980"><![CDATA[Owls are found throughout the world, although many species prefer the temperate climates of Europe and North America.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.981"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.981"><![CDATA[The smallest owl measures 13.5 cm and the largest has a wingspan of up to 2 meters!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.982"><![CDATA[Plush owl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.982"><![CDATA[Females are considerably larger than males. They stay in the nest while the males hunt.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.983"><![CDATA[Periscope]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.983"><![CDATA[Owls have 14 cervical vertebrae (compared to 7 in humans), which allows them to turn their heads up to 270 degrees. Their eyes are firmly set in their sockets, so they must turn their heads to change their direction of vision.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.984"><![CDATA[Insect lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.984"><![CDATA[Mantas suck up food while moving. They consume large amounts of plankton, consuming around 13% of their body weight each day.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.985"><![CDATA[Pointed tail]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.985"><![CDATA[Manta rays are found in temperate, subtropical, and tropical waters around the world. They migrate across the oceans both singly and in groups.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.986"><![CDATA[Shallow water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.986"><![CDATA[They have different swimming behaviors in different waters – in the deep oceans they swim in one plane, but near the coast they like to float on the water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.987"><![CDATA[Plush blanket]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.987"><![CDATA[Mantas have a long gestation period of up to 13 months. After birth, the young resemble a miniature adult and do not require parental care.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.988"><![CDATA[Blanket]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.988"><![CDATA[Their body resembles a blanket, allowing them to blend in with the bottom. They can reach a width of up to 4 meters!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.989"><![CDATA[Brown shell]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.989"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.990"><![CDATA[Pink shell]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.990"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.991"><![CDATA[Blue shell]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.991"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.992"><![CDATA[Yellow khon mask]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.992"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.993"><![CDATA[Red khon mask]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.993"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.994"><![CDATA[Blue khon mask]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.994"><![CDATA[#VALUE!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.995"><![CDATA[Pointer]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.995"><![CDATA[Cambodia's tropical forests are in grave danger. Deforestation is destroying the home of sun bears.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.996"><![CDATA[Cambodian flag]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.996"><![CDATA[The Cambodian flag has two blue and one red stripes. The Angkor Wat temple is depicted in the center.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.997"><![CDATA[Paw print]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.997"><![CDATA[Don't be afraid of this print. The Malayan bear is an omnivore. It likes insects and of course honey!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.998"><![CDATA[Malayan teddy bear]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.998"><![CDATA[This plush toy looks just as cute as a real Sun Bear! It has fewer teeth and claws than the real thing, so you can cuddle it!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.999"><![CDATA[Tetrameles tree]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.999"><![CDATA[Tetrameles is a famous tree that grows in Cambodia. It is famous worldwide mainly because it grows over ancient ruins, which adds to the mysterious and magical feel of the place.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1005"><![CDATA[Fruit lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1005"><![CDATA[The Kakapo has a very small stomach compared to other birds of its size. It is exclusively herbivorous and mainly enjoys seeds, fruits, plants and pollen.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1006"><![CDATA[New Zealand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1006"><![CDATA[The Kakapo is native to New Zealand, and the remaining birds live on these islands. They are threatened by the introduction of non-native species such as cats and ferrets, and by overhunting.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1007"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1007"><![CDATA[The Kakapo is part of the psittaciformes family. It is one of the heaviest parrots and the only flightless one. It is also probably one of the longest-living birds in the world, with a lifespan of up to 120 years!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1008"><![CDATA[Plush Kakapo Owl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1008"><![CDATA[Due to their long lifespan, the kakapo is one of the few animals, other than humans, that does not start breeding until they are in their teens. Females usually start looking for males when they are around 9 to 11 years old.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1009"><![CDATA[Bee hive]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1009"><![CDATA[The Kakapo is known for its pleasant scent, which is similar to honey and pollen.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1010"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1010"><![CDATA[The beautiful bird of paradise travels through the forest hunting for prey. While it feeds on fruit and insects, it will also feast on frogs, small reptiles, or other birds.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1011"><![CDATA[Papua New Guinea]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1011"><![CDATA[The beautiful bird of paradise can be seen in the rainforests of New Guinea in the treetops.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1012"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1012"><![CDATA[Males are black with a green crown and breast and extravagant plumage. Females are reddish-brown and hoodless. During courtship, the male spreads his hood and dances around the female.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1013"><![CDATA[Plush bird of paradise beautiful]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1013"><![CDATA[There are many more males than females, which is why they court so extravagantly. It takes males several years to fully develop the feathers on their hood, which they use to attract a female.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1014"><![CDATA[Smile]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1014"><![CDATA[When a beautiful bird of paradise opens its comb, the feathers resemble a smiling face.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1015"><![CDATA[Meat lover]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1015"><![CDATA[Dart frogs feed on ants, mites, and termites. The degree of toxicity depends on this diet.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1016"><![CDATA[Bolivia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1016"><![CDATA[Arrow frogs can be found throughout Central and South America, mainly in rainforests. They move around on the ground, but also high in the treetops!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1017"><![CDATA[Track]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1017"><![CDATA[Their bright color is related to their toxicity, and thus deters potential predators!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1018"><![CDATA[Plush dart frog]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1018"><![CDATA[They lay their eggs in moist places near leaves and roots. After hatching, the adult frogs carry their tadpoles to the water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.name.1019"><![CDATA[Blowing arrow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.collectableItems.setInfo.1019"><![CDATA[Arrow frogs got their name from natives who used the poisonous secretions of some species to ward off their arrows.]]></item>
    <category name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZoo">
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZoo.title"><![CDATA[Tools]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZoo.text"><![CDATA[Collect tools and exchange them for expansions for your hidden zoo.<br><br>You get tools in safari and on the wheel of fortune. Then take them to the shop and exchange them.<br><br>The current number of tools you own is:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZooTools.title"><![CDATA[Tools]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZooTools.text.1"><![CDATA[The 3rd zoo expansion will give you access to the hidden zoo. It doesn't look like a very big expansion, but you can expand it using tools. And here's how it works:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZooTools.text.2"><![CDATA[<ol><li>Enter the hidden zoo, go to the store and click on "add-ons".</li><li>You will get 2 cards to expand the zoo - one in exchange for tools, the other for zoodollars.</li><li>Collect enough tools on the wheel of fortune or on safari and exchange them for a map.</li></ol>]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.forgottenZooTools.text.3"><![CDATA[Expand your zoo using both maps - simply with tools and zoodollars.<br> You own exactly as many tools as you need:]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.collectableItems.easterEvent">
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.easterEvent.title"><![CDATA[Easter eggs]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.easterEvent.text"><![CDATA[From April 21st to April 27th, you'll experience a flood of Easter eggs! Collect them and exchange them for Easter enclosure decorations, Easter bunnies, and enclosures. Your current Easter egg status:]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.collectableItems.book">
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.tab.animals"><![CDATA[Animals]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.tab.cages"><![CDATA[Paddocks]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.tab.assistants"><![CDATA[Assistants]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.tab.specials"><![CDATA[Accessories]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.more"><![CDATA[More...]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.collectableItems.rewards">
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.rewards.unlocked.title"><![CDATA[Win!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.rewards.unlocked.text"><![CDATA[Choose your price:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.rewards.locked.title"><![CDATA[Keep collecting...]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.rewards.locked.text"><![CDATA[... you will get:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.collectableItems.book.rewards.button"><![CDATA[Choose]]></item>
    </category>
  </category>
</language>
