<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.news">
    <category name="zoo.news.buttons">
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.zooadvisor"><![CDATA[Zoo Meter]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.shop"><![CDATA[To the store]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.inventory"><![CDATA[Zoo warehouse]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.safari"><![CDATA[Safari]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.start"><![CDATA[Start]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.bank"><![CDATA[To the bank]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.safariStart"><![CDATA[Start the safari]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.buy"><![CDATA[Buy]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.download"><![CDATA[download]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.buttons.twitter"><![CDATA[Tweet!]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.news.text">
      <item name="zoo.news.text.subheader"><![CDATA[News]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.welcome.login"><![CDATA[Welcome back, %username%!<br> Your zoo is really busy again!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.welcome.general"><![CDATA[Hello %username%!<br> Your zoo is as busy as ever!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.upgrade"><![CDATA[With paws, you can beautify your enclosures and make them even more valuable.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.safari"><![CDATA[Yay! Jump straight into the wild: from level 7, the Safari ride is here for you! Discover unusual animals and win great prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.valentines_1"><![CDATA[Exclusively from 11-18.2.11 CET]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.valentines_2"><![CDATA[50% discount on attempted addition]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.valentines_3"><![CDATA[Many, many surprises]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.pawprint_4x"><![CDATA[more paws for superfood, the best food and for supermedicine!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.pawprint_2x"><![CDATA[more paws for feeding, watering and healing!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.storage"><![CDATA[Finally more space! Expand your water and feed storage space - new tanks are now available! From water tanks to underground storage, there's plenty of space everywhere. This will save you some trips.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.visitFriend"><![CDATA[From now on, all your friends from your address book will be displayed right next to the playing field. You can visit each of their zoos. You can then check the qualities of the zoo and its director in a friendly manner. Have fun!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.premiumPackage"><![CDATA[Great premium benefits are now waiting for you in the zoo-bank! Whether it's paws or a BZ package, your zoo will shine. And you will be even more successful. Order great packages!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.asiaSafari"><![CDATA[NEW for players level 8 and up! A new continent lies at your feet: Head to Asia! Experience the great Asian safari and discover new regions.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.pawPackage"><![CDATA[NEW: Paw Packs! Silver, Gold or Platinum - Paw rations will brighten up your enclosures! Get the benefits: They are only available for a limited time.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.wishes"><![CDATA[Thought bubbles will show you the wishes of your visitors. Fulfill them and your wallet will start to ring. You can re-pack the wishes in the settings.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.buyAllZooExpansion"><![CDATA[Great deal! Do you want to expand your zoo to the maximum immediately? Then buy the 100% maxi zoo expansion for only 400 zoodollars. Don't hesitate and buy now! The offer is valid for a short time only.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.fullscreen"><![CDATA[New: Full screen preview! Experience your ZOO in all its glory with all the details!<br> <br>Click on the 4-arrow symbol to see your ZOO in full screen.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.forgottenZoo"><![CDATA[Discover the path to the hidden zoo<br>with your 3rd zoo expansion.<br> <br>Finally, there will be even more room for more animals.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.megaXPDays_title"><![CDATA[April 16th & 17th only!<br>Buy Zoodollars & collect double BZ!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.megaXPDays_body"><![CDATA[Earn zoodollars in the zoo bank from April 16-17.<br>You will benefit from your purchase for 24 hours.<br>You will get this great bonus:<br><br>Every action related to the enclosure will bring you double BZ!<br> <br>Take advantage of the offer 5 times and get the most.<br>5 days of big BZ bonus!*]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.megaXPDays_note"><![CDATA[*Payments by bank transfer are excluded.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.easterEvent"><![CDATA[The Easter Bunny is here!<br>From April 21st to April 27th, there will be a lot of Easter eggs available.<br><br>Exchange them for Easter decorations, <br>Easter bunnies and Easter enclosures. Happy Easter!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.toolbar"><![CDATA[There's a new toolbar in Zoomumba! Download the toolbar and you'll get a stand with magic balloons, daily POI bonuses, and brand new information for your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.xpBonus_title"><![CDATA[New on the wheel of fortune:<br> Bonus BZ]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.xpBonus_body"><![CDATA[Now you can increase your BZ by 30% or even a whopping 100% for a full 8 hours!*]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.xpBonus_note"><![CDATA[*The increase applies to the standard profit from your activities!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.northAmericaSafari"><![CDATA[New safari from level 9! Explore North America and experience a thrilling adventure!<br>Discover the secrets of the continent and find exotic animals for your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.mainBuildingRedesign"><![CDATA[Your main building now shines with a completely new shine.<br>And the best part is that it now improves with<br>every 10th level increase up to level 40!<br>With every additional 10th level you get a new design!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.superPowerFoodChanges"><![CDATA[Starting next week - instead of complicated bonuses for feeding animals with the best and superfoods, these clear bonuses:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.superPowerFoodChanges_2"><![CDATA[Starting this week! Instead of complicated bonuses, you get these clear bonuses for feeding your animals super and best food:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.superFeedPacks"><![CDATA[Great promotion until June 7th: 3 different superfood packages! With the largest package, you can choose 5 more friends who will receive 5x superfood as a gift!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.starterPacks"><![CDATA[Get the "Black Panther" starter pack now and get a lot of benefits!<br>Attention - this pack is only available once for each zoo director!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.motherDay"><![CDATA[Breed cute babies today (Sat 0 am - Sun 23:59 pm) with a 50% discount on zoogroš!<br>We also have new decorations - check them out in the store!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.newSuperPowerFood"><![CDATA[From now on you will get great new bonuses for super and best food. Double BZ for super food and quadruple paws for best food. Don't hesitate and spoil your animals!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.globalRanking"><![CDATA[New! List of the best! Click on the trophy and see which players are in the top 100 in different categories! You will also immediately see the BZ values ​​of your friends.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.buddylistRanking"><![CDATA[Keep your eyes open! From now on you will see in your own friends list! And you have an overview of everything - friends, you and BZ. Who is the most diligent director?]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.collections"><![CDATA[New! ZooMumba has a new collection album! Find all the collection symbols in the enclosures, animals and assistants categories. Exchange your completed collections for great rewards!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.cashForAction"><![CDATA[From now on you can use "Cash for action"! Do you need zoodollars? Then go to the bank, click on "Cash for action" and choose one of the offers from different providers! Try it out!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.zooWheelChanges"><![CDATA[The Wheel of Fortune is celebrating its new opening in the zoo parking lot! From level 3 you will have your own Wheel of Fortune with even higher chances of getting better rewards!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.anniversaryEvent"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Zoo Director!<br> We're having a huge birthday party! Look forward to great events and lots of birthday surprises in the store!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.twitter"><![CDATA[Join us on Twitter and win a "Bird House"! We will draw 10 lucky people who "tweet" 2-3 times a week.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.cageSpecies"><![CDATA[New! Try different combinations of animals and enclosures to get more POIs and earn more zoogros. Go for it! More and more combinations are waiting for you!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.avatarBuddylist"><![CDATA[New! Create your own avatar in the main building menu! Invite friends to your friends list and view their avatars!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.travelingCircus"><![CDATA[The circus has arrived in town! Visit the traveling circus at the marketplace and check out the great assortment of animals. You have a chance to win an exclusive animal.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.powerUps"><![CDATA[Limited time offer only! Get some great Paw and BZ boosters in the shop. With the right combination you can get up to 130% more Paw or BZ!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.longerAssistants"><![CDATA[New in the shop! Now even more convenient: Hire your assistants not only for 1 day, but also for 7 or even 28 days. That way, routine work will always be done reliably!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.halloween2011"><![CDATA[Halloween at your zoo: from noon on October 25th to noon on November 1st, it's going to be pretty scary at your zoo! Be there!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.halloween2011endStep1"><![CDATA[Halloween is almost over. There are no more sweets to be had from now on. But you have until 2.11. 18:00 (CET) to activate rewards and breed baby bats.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.halloween2011endStep2"><![CDATA[Halloween is over. We hope you had fun! Thank you for your participation and see you next year!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.caravan"><![CDATA[The Animal Mobile is here! Quickly check your parking lot and take the chance to see the behavior of truly rare animals! What do they have with them this time?]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.breedingNursery"><![CDATA[Get a new breeding station and animal nursery. Raise rare, cuddly babies and watch them grow up in the animal nursery. Start with a parrot, for example!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.advent2011"><![CDATA[From December 1st to December 24th, a surprise awaits you every day! Every morning from 10 am, look for our bonus code on Facebook, Twitter or our forums. Good luck!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.christmas2011"><![CDATA[Help Santa - his reindeer have escaped! Use the breeding station from December 21st to January 2nd (12 noon, Central European Time) to replace them and look forward to many surprises!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.newBreedingAnimals"><![CDATA[New animals for your breeding station! You can now raise new %species% babies in your breeding station and watch them grow up in the animal nursery.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.breedingEvent"><![CDATA[Double the cuddly fun! For the next 5 days, your animals in the breeding station can look forward to twins! So don't waste time!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.meterRedesign"><![CDATA[Zoo management made easy! The Zoometer now shows the status of your main and hidden zoos at the same time. Entrance fees to both zoos will now only be collected at the main entrance.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.decoupling"><![CDATA[A diverse mix: Hooray! Now you can keep different subspecies of the same animals in one enclosure. Your animals will be happy to have new roommates!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.valentine2012"><![CDATA[It's going to be an animal romance! From February 8th to 15th, collect sweet Valentine's Day items and win lots of sweet prizes in our big Valentine's Day board game!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.tradeEvent"><![CDATA[Neighborly Help: Zoo director Lukáš has visited you for a short time and will exchange very rare, especially cuddly animal specimens with you for your own. So let's go!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.EasterEvent2012"><![CDATA[Come and hunt for Easter eggs with us! The bunny has hidden lots of them in your enclosures. Collect them all and get fantastic rewards and surprises!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.Expansion3"><![CDATA[Hooray! More space for your furry friends to play! There are three new play areas for all your zoo animals.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.frogEvent2012"><![CDATA[From May 17th to 23rd, your zoo will be a fairytale. Lots of fun and great prizes await you during the Royal Frog Event!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.level100"><![CDATA[On May 30, 2012, player FernoNr.1 finished a pretty grueling battle and reached level 100. Player Chrissie76 was close behind him and reached level 100 on May 31, 2012 shortly before 1:00 PM. We would like to officially congratulate the winners! We hope you enjoy the snow leopard families.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.australienEvent2012"><![CDATA[Sun, surf and marsupials - from June 25th to July 3rd, play the Australian game at your zoo! Participate and win great prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.indiaEvent2012"><![CDATA[From July 19th to 26th, the zoo will show you its Indian side! Get ready for an Indian game with cobras and fascinating jungle ruins!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.anniversary2012"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday ZooMumba! ZooMumba will be celebrating its 2nd birthday on August 19th - and from August 17th to August 26th we'll be celebrating with fun party games and items. Join us!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.healassist"><![CDATA[New: Veterinarian! Dr. Lynn has the right medicine for every disease! Your animals will be healthy again quickly: Get a veterinarian for your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.oktoberfest2012"><![CDATA[Let the party begin! Pull out your leather pants and dress and start celebrating the traditional Oktoberfest in your zoo! Collect pretzels, loafers and traditional Bavarian hats. Get animals from the southern German region and a great, festive dwelling!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.halloween2012"><![CDATA[Wow, spooky times are coming. The Pumpkin Battle is about to begin! Win great prizes! New: Collect them all for even more fun!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.christmas2012"><![CDATA[Santa Claus needs your help! Deliver the cubs and candy apples from December 18, 2012 to January 3, 2013 and help Santa! If we all work together, we will soon be lighting the lights on the big tree with all the animals! Merry Christmas!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.valentines2013"><![CDATA[February 14th is Valentine's Day! And from the 14th to the 25th, there will be romantic rewards during the Valentine's Day event. You'll also be able to welcome storks to your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.levelcurve"><![CDATA[Hooray! ZooMumba has new levels! You can now reach level 200. With the introduction of new levels, some will notice that they are at a higher level than before. Good luck!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.easter2013"><![CDATA[Start collecting chicks and exchange them for great prizes during the Easter event, which runs from March 27 to April 8. Then climb the plush mountain together!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.butterfly"><![CDATA[New animals for your zoo: beautiful butterflies and cute little otters - now in the zoo store!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.city"><![CDATA[More space in your zoo! It's finally here: a new city with all the buildings you'll need! Click on the menu in the bottom left and redesign your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.stores"><![CDATA[New shops at the zoo: Treat your zoo visitors to delicious strawberries and crispy churros! Don't know what to do with your zoo pennies? Set up a Russian enclosure at your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.mole"><![CDATA[To all gardeners: Get a garden for recreation as an enclosure and give a mole a home! Do you like exotic animals? Don't miss the news: Kiwi!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.inventory"><![CDATA[Now even more convenient: Spring cleaning at the zoo! Move paths and trash cans to your inventory, individually or all at once with one click!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.91"><![CDATA[From level 90 you can unlock a new game field - a riverside zoo. There's plenty of room for animals, shops and decorations along the river!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.92"><![CDATA[Summer at the Zoo: Pamper your animals in a heavenly habitat and offer your visitors a new flower shop and waffle shack!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.frenchEvent2013"><![CDATA[Vive la France: Discover the French way of life in your zoo! From July 11th to 24th, the French tricolor will be flying in ZooMumba!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.43"><![CDATA[Hooray, ZooMumba is 3 years old! Hurry up to the shooting festival, throw darts at balloons and play a board game! Great birthday gifts are waiting for you!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.hungaryEvent2013"><![CDATA[Hooray for Hungary! From September 12th to 23rd, we'll be going to Hungary to collect peppers! You can exchange them for zootastic rewards until September 24th!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.doubleXP"><![CDATA[Take care of your animals and get double the BZ! From 8pm on Friday (CET) to 8am on Monday (CET), Zoomumba will be giving away double the BZ!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.101"><![CDATA[New in the zoo shop: Flags from trips around the world - this time from Hungary, Australia and India. Discover also another new product: A clam hut! For all clam lovers!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.103"><![CDATA[October sale in the zoo shop! Delicious pretzels and Bavarian houses are now available. Another new item: the German flag!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.104"><![CDATA[Wow, Halloween is just around the corner and those crazy penguins have conjured up spooky ghosts! It's time to hunt ghosts! Catch them with your Plasma Blobs and trade them in for spooky fun prizes from October 17th to 31st!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.106"><![CDATA[Thanksgiving at the zoo! This time we're going to America to celebrate! Collect colorful leaves and win great prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.107"><![CDATA[Merry Christmas! From December 19th to January 7th, we will be celebrating Christmas at the zoo. Animals love sweet treats - collect colorful decorations and decorate your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.111"><![CDATA[Travel with us to the Orient and discover ancient Egypt! Start by excavating pyramids, sarcophagi and mummies. Collect scarabs and turn your zoo into an oriental paradise!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.112"><![CDATA[To celebrate St. Valentine's Day, let's climb to the top of the plush pile together! Love is in the air! Sell your animals and win great prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.113"><![CDATA[Get all the hearts: Collect cards from February 20th to March 10th and create a romantic atmosphere for your animals and visitors with red roses and health oases.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.114"><![CDATA[New on the wheel of fortune: Spin it, whether it's your first time or not. Win a shy and very rare clouded leopard! Try your luck!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.116"><![CDATA[The fantastic Easter event can begin: Collect colorful Easter eggs from April 10th to 28th and exchange them for super spring rewards in the Easter board game.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.117"><![CDATA[New areas in your zoo: three new enclosures and various matching decorative items await you! Create themed areas in your zoo now!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.118"><![CDATA[More new areas for your zoo: decorate your zoo with new enclosures and matching decorative items. Create themed areas in your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.120"><![CDATA[Football fever in your zoo: Travel with us to Brazil from June 19th to July 1st. Samba, football and exotic drinks await you. Collect colorful cocktail fruits and exchange them for super summer prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.123"><![CDATA[Don't miss the big birthday party in Zoomumba: from August 19th to September 2nd, we'll be celebrating our 4th birthday! Collect balloons and exchange them for zootastic birthday prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.124"><![CDATA[Do your animals crave sweets? Then become the owner of Sugar Land today with 5 levels of construction and a choice of favorite enclosures!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.130"><![CDATA[Follow the slimebugs across the Halloween Swamp! Win spooky prizes during the Halloween festivities from October 30th to November 10th!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.131"><![CDATA[Grand Opening! Discover a brand new recycling facility and workshop in town. Collect trash, recycle it, and use the resources to craft new decorations for your zoo's themed areas.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.132"><![CDATA[Help the penguins decorate the zoo for Christmas. From December 11th to December 29th, treats will be popping out of your enclosures. Exchange them for Christmas rewards!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.133"><![CDATA[Help the penguins decorate the zoo for Christmas. From December 11th to December 29th, treats will be popping out of your enclosures. Exchange them for Christmas rewards!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.134"><![CDATA[Celebrate Indian Republic Day with us on January 26th. For players level 86 and up, the Indian Bistro is now available in the store for zoogrosh!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.135"><![CDATA[The coast is calling: From level 15 you have the opportunity to unlock the zoo on the coast and take advantage of the new area!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.136"><![CDATA[Play the Valentine's Day board game from February 12th to 23rd and find your true love!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.138"><![CDATA[Let's climb together to the top of the plush mountain: Let's pull together and win great prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.140"><![CDATA[New in the zoo shop: There are now a variety of paths to choose from! From now on, you can also build your own beautiful paths in the zoo workshop.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.141"><![CDATA[Chicken coop alarm! Help the Easter Bunny collect eggs! From April 2nd to 13th, a strange creature will be lurking around the chicken coop during the Easter board event!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.142"><![CDATA[Unlock new animals: Get Helenka the possum (from level 37) and the honeyeater (from level 62). From level 100, a striped hyena will be waiting for you in the shop!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.144"><![CDATA[Attention fans: New decorations for additional themed worlds are now available in the Workshop. Create an Asian, Swamp, and Jungle area in your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.147"><![CDATA[Travel with us to Asia for a dragon dance! Collect colorful lanterns and win great prizes in an Asian board game!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.150"><![CDATA[Zoomumba is 5 years old! And we're celebrating in the Australian wilderness: Head to the Australian outback and have fun shooting funny balloons!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.151"><![CDATA[Magic at the Zoo! Perry Schlotter has been transformed into a giant pumpkin! Play our Halloween game, help him find the right spell to turn him back into his original form and collect magic potions!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.153"><![CDATA[Help the penguins decorate the zoo for a big Christmas party. As you take care of your animals, colorful Christmas candles will pop out of their enclosures. Exchange them for Christmas prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.154"><![CDATA[Love is spreading around! Play the board game called Love's Path on Lily Pads and meet the new Mongoose Brindle!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.156"><![CDATA[There's a lot of chocolate around this Easter! We've got an Easter board game and new zoo features for you!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.158"><![CDATA[The keeper Soňa and the penguins found an old water park behind a hidden zoo! Head to the Underwater World, build new buildings and meet new sea animals!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.159"><![CDATA[It's time to get a little wet! Play our board game "Water Fun" and get lots of new items for the Undersea World, including a cute seahorse!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.160"><![CDATA[It's time for some monkey business! The monkeys are out to get the meerkats in some mischief. Help them play our new board game. Great rewards await!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.161"><![CDATA[Want to be scared? Play our Halloween board game "Hocus Pocus" and get cool rewards for your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.162"><![CDATA[Want some bonus pearls? Then you're in luck! For a limited time, extra pearls will be popping out of the enclosures in the Underwater World! Happy hunting!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.163"><![CDATA[Christmas is coming and the penguins are decorating. Play our board game and win great rewards for your zoo!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.164"><![CDATA[Our Valentine's Day board game comes with a dose of romance! Play today and get great rewards for the Undersea World! And who knows, you might even meet your true love!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.news.text.165"><![CDATA[Are you ready for an adventure? Travel with us to Cambodia! The secrets of ancient Khmer temples are waiting for you!]]></item>
    </category>
  </category>
</language>
