<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.eventValentine">
    <category name="zoo.eventValentine.comic">
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.comic.1"><![CDATA[Welcome to our Valentine's Day event! From February 8th to February 15th, there will be a romantic atmosphere! Have fun playing our Valentine's Day game and look forward to lots of great prizes!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.comic.1.1"><![CDATA[Check out how to do it:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.comic.2"><![CDATA[Take care of your animals and collect Valentine's Day items: Hearts, Love Notes, and Cupid's Bow and Arrows. Use them to win adorable surprises during the romantic Valentine's Day game!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.comic.3"><![CDATA[With your collected items, you can move around the playing field and collect prizes: Majestic deer and supplies of Tolija essence and growth potions await you!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.comic.3.1"><![CDATA[Also check out the shop - you'll find useful boosters there that will ensure even greater success and fun in the game!]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.eventValentine.tooltip">
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.tooltip.powerUp"><![CDATA[Doubles the number of Valentine's Day items for 1 hour.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.tooltip.restart"><![CDATA[Restart the board game]]></item>
    </category>
    <category name="zoo.eventValentine.layer">
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.layer.end"><![CDATA[Our Valentine's Day event is almost over! You won't be receiving any more bows, letters, or hearts. But don't give up! You still have this much time to win Valentine's Day rewards:]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.eventValentine.layer.restart"><![CDATA[Now that you have won the stag and doe, you can start the board game again! Simply click on the green check mark or the new button on the game board!]]></item>
    </category>
  </category>
</language>
