<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.shop.specials">
    <category name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps">
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.9.title"><![CDATA[Booster 30% EP]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.9.text"><![CDATA[With the 30% booster you will get 30% more BZ for 1 hour! If you buy 2 of the same boosters, the time will be extended. Tip: One 30% BZ booster and one 100% BZ booster are valid at the same time and will reward you with 130% more BZ for the entire 1 hour.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.10.title"><![CDATA[100% booster EP]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.10.text"><![CDATA[With the 100% BZ booster, you get 100% more BZ for the entire 1 hour! If you buy 2 of the same boosters, the time will be extended. Tip: one 100% BZ booster and one 30% BZ booster are valid at the same time, so you get 130% more BZ for the entire 1 hour!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.11.title"><![CDATA[30% paw booster]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.11.text"><![CDATA[With the 30% Paw Booster you get 30% more Paws for the entire 1 hour! If you buy 2 of the same boosters, the time will be extended. Tip: one 30% Paw Booster and one 100% Paw Booster are valid at the same time, so you get 130% more Paws for the entire 1 hour!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.12.title"><![CDATA[100% paw booster]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.12.text"><![CDATA[With the 100% Paw Booster you get 100% more Paws for the entire 1 hour! If you buy 2 of the same boosters, the time will be extended. Tip: one 100% Paw Booster and one 30% Paw Booster are valid at the same time, so you get 130% more Paws for the entire 1 hour!]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.13.title"><![CDATA[Board game booster]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.13.text"><![CDATA[With the board game booster, you'll get double the amount of collectibles that will pop out of the enclosures for 1 hour! If you want to extend this time, buy more boosters.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.14.title"><![CDATA[30% zoocoin booster]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.14.text"><![CDATA[With a 30% booster, you will get 30% extra zoogros from your shops for 1 hour! If you buy 2 of the same boosters, the time will be extended. Tip: One 30% zoogros booster and one 100% zoogros booster are valid at the same time and will reward you with 130% extra zoogros for the entire 1 hour.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.15.title"><![CDATA[100% zoocoin booster]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.15.text"><![CDATA[With a 100% booster, you will get 100% extra zoogros from your shops for 1 hour! If you buy 2 of the same boosters, the time will be extended. Tip: One 100% zoogros booster and one 30% zoogros booster are valid at the same time and will reward you with 130% extra zoogros for the entire 1 hour.]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.16.title"><![CDATA[Breeding station booster]]></item>
      <item name="zoo.shop.specials.powerUps.16.text"><![CDATA[Rare hybrids made easy! The Breeding Station Booster will ensure that your hatchlings reach at least one level higher than the lowest level of one of their parents within 24 hours. But be careful: The Booster only works if you pick up the hatchling from the Breeding Station.]]></item>
    </category>
  </category>
</language>
