<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo">
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_1"><![CDATA[Meadow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_1"><![CDATA[Luscious, green tufts of grass in a pleasant summer meadow. All animals that like grass and relax in the sun feel good here.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_2"><![CDATA[Water]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_2"><![CDATA[Splash! The enclosure with the pool is alive. Not only flamingos, but also other aquatic animals and various types of fish are having their own party there. The enclosure with the water surface is the party location among the enclosures!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_3"><![CDATA[Ice]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_3"><![CDATA[Penguins, polar bears and co. feel really good in the artificially created glacial landscape in the winter enclosure. Brrr, make sure you have fresh fish and a warm blanket.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_4"><![CDATA[Savanna]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_4"><![CDATA[The high temperatures that prevail in the savannah provide great conditions for animals from the African continent. They enjoy the heat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_5"><![CDATA[Desert]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_5"><![CDATA[Where is the nearest oasis? The desert gets really hot during the day and cools down quickly at night. The desert animals are happy, but what about the visitors?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_6"><![CDATA[Rocks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_6"><![CDATA[Small animals can hide nicely among the rocks. Larger animals have a harder time. At least they can find tasty prey among the rocks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_7"><![CDATA[Bamboo grove]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_7"><![CDATA[Your animals' home is now an elegant bamboo grove. This enclosure will earn you even more experience points than usual.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_8"><![CDATA[Swamp]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_8"><![CDATA[A swamp like this is teeming with various animals. Some like to roll around in the mud, others hunt insects and worms from the slimy substance. This enclosure will earn you even more experience points than usual.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_9"><![CDATA[Tundra]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_9"><![CDATA[Life in the tundra is harsh, but the animals have adapted optimally. It's cold here, but the mosses and lichens from the tundra taste delicious!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_10"><![CDATA[Snow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_10"><![CDATA[Winter, winter, it's snowing! Especially animals with really thick fur feel really good in a snowy enclosure.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_11"><![CDATA[Wasteland]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_11"><![CDATA[You'll hardly believe it: Many animals also feel good in the desert, and it doesn't always have to be beautiful nature. The animals that survive in the desert have adapted perfectly.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_12"><![CDATA[Halloween]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_12"><![CDATA[Slimy, gooey and terrifying: On horror nights, the wasteland turns into an inhospitable landscape where terrifying characters roam. Never before have there been so many experience points: This enclosure is at the highest level from the start.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_13"><![CDATA[Christmas]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_13"><![CDATA[Not only do the children's eyes shine, but also the festively decorated enclosures. The animals also enjoy the colorful lights and sweet lollipops. There have never been so many experience points: This enclosure has been at the highest level from the start.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_14"><![CDATA[Romance]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_14"><![CDATA[Love is in the air ... but also in your enclosures. Everything invites romantic moments. If you have a male and a female in the enclosure, then each new attempt to add a new animal takes only half the time than in other enclosures.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_15"><![CDATA[Primeval forest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_15"><![CDATA[Can you hear how life is here? The jungle is full of sounds. Animals big and small live together harmoniously here. A big family! This enclosure will bring you even more experience points than usual.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_16"><![CDATA[Terrarium]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_16"><![CDATA[A place where reptiles feel great. Visitors can also admire them up close.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_17"><![CDATA[Easter enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_17"><![CDATA[It's not just rabbits who are in their element here. Especially at Easter, the grass is a real pleasure!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_18"><![CDATA[Birthday run]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_18"><![CDATA[Traditional! It doesn't get any more colorful than this! This new enclosure will put you in the right birthday mood! Happy birthday! The party is starting!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_19"><![CDATA[Crypt]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_19"><![CDATA[All the little Halloween ghosts will feel right at home in this spooky graveyard. Bring a little terror to your Zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_20"><![CDATA[Christmas miracle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_20"><![CDATA[This will be the first animal Christmas! Festively decorated enclosures will bring a smile to the faces of both people and animals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_21"><![CDATA[Fairytale enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_21"><![CDATA[Great! This fantasy enclosure will give your zoo a fairytale atmosphere and increase its appeal. Hopefully no golden balls fall into the well!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_22"><![CDATA[Australian outback - range]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_22"><![CDATA[This habitat is a carbon copy of the Australian outback - mysterious, dry and quiet. Your animals are going to flip their lids!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_23"><![CDATA[Ruins in the jungle]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_23"><![CDATA[These long-abandoned ruins are shrouded in mystery. The animals that live there offer very good protection!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_24"><![CDATA[Party enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_24"><![CDATA[Up for a wild zoo party: Zoomumba's second birthday needs to be celebrated in style - and in the party enclosure! Hip, hip, hooray!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_25"><![CDATA[Bonsai enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_25"><![CDATA[Is your zoo too noisy? Then it's time for some Zen meditation with a cup of tea in the bonsai enclosure.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_26"><![CDATA[Oktoberfest - amusement park]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_26"><![CDATA[Oktoberfest has just begun! Great beer gardens and the rustic atmosphere of Bavaria - it's time to start having fun! Put on your leather pants and let the beer flow!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_27"><![CDATA[Volcanic range]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_27"><![CDATA[The hot lava makes this enclosure a particularly warm place, and some animals are perfectly fine with that.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_28"><![CDATA[Winter magic]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_28"><![CDATA[Turn your zoo into a winter wonderland. Whether they have feathers, claws or paws, your animals love building snowmen!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_29"><![CDATA[Love spell]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_29"><![CDATA[Be my valentine! Love has spread to animal shelters. Oh, that's beautiful!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_30"><![CDATA[Happy love]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_30"><![CDATA[The perfect place for romance! Your pets can serenade each other right here! However, if there are new members joining the family, that will have to wait.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_31"><![CDATA[Fjords]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_31"><![CDATA[Connecting with nature is the essence of spring. The fjord environment has pure nature - fresh air and glacial water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_32"><![CDATA[Heavenly habitat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_32"><![CDATA[This is a true paradise - the trees look like lollipops and the river flows with honey! A perfect treat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_33"><![CDATA[Easter meadow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_33"><![CDATA[Do you like to hunt for eggs at Easter? This meadow is full of small colorful eggs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_34"><![CDATA[Warm greetings from Russia]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_34"><![CDATA[Your animals love playing fetch among the onion domes of a Russian temple. They get so warm that they don't even mind the harsh Russian winter!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_35"><![CDATA[Garden for recreation]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_35"><![CDATA[A nice haven for your animals. There's definitely room for a garden gnome among those trees and flowers, right?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_36"><![CDATA[Vineyard]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_36"><![CDATA[The excellent French wines are known all over the world. Your animals will feel at home in the mild climate of these idyllic slopes.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_37"><![CDATA[Birthday party - paddock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_37"><![CDATA[Long live ZooMumba! It's time to start celebrating: we've got cake, balloons and lots of fun for young and old - and for your animals!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_38"><![CDATA[Puszta - paddock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_38"><![CDATA[A pasture with vegetation is a fantastic enclosure for many animals. In Hungary, this landscape is dotted with shepherds, cute farmhouses and typical wells.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_39"><![CDATA[Alps]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_39"><![CDATA[Yay! Your animals are attracted to green meadows and herbs on the mountains and in the valleys. The mountains will get higher and rockier with each level! How exciting!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_40"><![CDATA[Horror run]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_40"><![CDATA[Aaah! A voracious, five-headed plant surrounds the animals in this small horror enclosure. It's hungry, but don't worry, animals aren't on its menu. But your visitors should beware.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_41"><![CDATA[Cottage animal enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_41"><![CDATA[Celebrate Thanksgiving in a cozy country cottage surrounded by cornfields. The perfect place to relax!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_42"><![CDATA[Under the tree]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_42"><![CDATA[A colorful Christmas tree with gifts for your animals - will they open them with their claws, beaks or teeth? Whatever they use, they will definitely be happy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_43"><![CDATA[Cave]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_43"><![CDATA[Many animals like to dig their own dens. With each level, this enclosure will get deeper and deeper. What might be hidden down there? Stalactites? Cave paintings? Maybe even gems?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_44"><![CDATA[1001 nights]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_44"><![CDATA[Pamper your animals in this tent, where they will feel like they are in the Arabian Nights. It is a true oriental oasis!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_45"><![CDATA[Oasis of health]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_45"><![CDATA[Need a massage? The health and well-being of your animals is a top priority at this oasis. A bubble bath and candles? What could be better?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_46"><![CDATA[Forest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_46"><![CDATA[Many animals prefer to live in the forest. With each level, more and more trees will grow. Coniferous and deciduous trees, shrubs and bushes will create the perfect place to hide!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_47"><![CDATA[Spring run]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_47"><![CDATA[Fresh spring scents and budding flowers all around: In the spring enclosure, your animals will enjoy fresh leaves and sprouting buds. And there's even a bubbling stream!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_48"><![CDATA[Coastal enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_48"><![CDATA[Fresh air and sea breeze! Many animals feel very comfortable in coastal areas - the sound of the ocean and the rocky cliffs offer an idyllic environment.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_49"><![CDATA[Magic mushroom enclosure]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_49"><![CDATA[Offer your visitors a vibrant world full of fantasy. With each level, this mushroom will grow upwards.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_50"><![CDATA[Sugar Land]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_50"><![CDATA[You can laze around all day in a land full of cotton candy and marshmallows. Pearl decorations and candied fruit make this run even sweeter!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_51"><![CDATA[Samba paddock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_51"><![CDATA[Colorful houses and graffiti decorate the cities of Brazil. In this enclosure, your animals will be surrounded by residential buildings.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_52"><![CDATA[Amazon rainforest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_52"><![CDATA[The Amazon rainforest dominates a large part of Brazil. Your animals can bathe in the Amazon among the tropical plants. Shh! They say there are many undiscovered animals there. How exciting!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_53"><![CDATA[Picnic meadow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_53"><![CDATA[A blanket, plates, glasses... these are the basic equipment for a picnic basket. Head to the picnic meadow and enjoy a birthday snack in nature!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_54"><![CDATA[Ghost Hour]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_54"><![CDATA[The twelfth hour has struck and ghosts are emerging from the catacombs to haunt all around.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_55"><![CDATA[Snow landscape]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_55"><![CDATA[Freshly fallen snow and a small cottage in the distance create a beautiful winter landscape.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_56"><![CDATA[Hawaiian abode]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_56"><![CDATA[Aloha! A touch of the South Pacific with palm trees and white beaches. Send your pets on a romantic getaway to paradise: complete with the sounds of the waves and decorative garlands!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_58"><![CDATA[Karl Karl]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_58"><![CDATA[Karlu Karlu is a sacred place for the natives and translates to "round rocks." They are commonly called "devil's balls."]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_59"><![CDATA[Whomping Willow]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_59"><![CDATA[The limbs of the weeping willow hang in the pale moonlight on eerie nights. Young wizards hide around in mysterious caves.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_60"><![CDATA[Emergency landing]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_60"><![CDATA[Santa's sleigh landed hard in the snow, but your animals are already looking forward to the presents that have been scattered around. Hooray!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_61"><![CDATA[A place of love]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_61"><![CDATA[There's always love floating over this pretty pond. It's the perfect place for your pets to snuggle up and watch the sunset.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_62"><![CDATA[Small ice mass]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_62"><![CDATA[Brr... it's cold! Ice lovers will feel right at home here.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_63"><![CDATA[Large water tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_63"><![CDATA[Let's go for a swim! Here your aquatic animals will find plenty of space to swim, dive and splash!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_64"><![CDATA[Easter Garden]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_64"><![CDATA[There's plenty of room to hide Easter eggs in this spring enclosure, and your animals will have a blast searching for them.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_65"><![CDATA[Small water tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_65"><![CDATA[An ideal habitat for smaller fish. Visitors can look forward to a real spectacle.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_66"><![CDATA[Medium water tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_66"><![CDATA[Splash splash! Your aquatic animals will have a good time swimming in this tank.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_67"><![CDATA[Medium-sized ice mass]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_67"><![CDATA[Quick, put on another sweater! Your animals can look forward to sub-zero temperatures in this frozen habitat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_68"><![CDATA[Vast ice mass]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_68"><![CDATA[Get ready for the cold! Animals with love for sub-zero temperatures will be grateful for this icy paradise.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_69"><![CDATA[Small pirate bay]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_69"><![CDATA[Your fish will love swimming in this bay! What treasures might be hidden here?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_70"><![CDATA[Medium pirate bay]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_70"><![CDATA[In this bay, there's enough space for fish of all shapes and sizes!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_71"><![CDATA[Large pirate bay]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_71"><![CDATA[There's definitely a pirate treasure hiding at the bottom of this bay! Your animals may discover it!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_72"><![CDATA[Small expedition tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_72"><![CDATA[Pack your gear and get ready to dive into the depths. Found something? Hurry! Or the animals will overtake you!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_73"><![CDATA[Small coral reef]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_73"><![CDATA[Look at the vivid colors of the coral reef! This exotic environment is ideal for the tropical fish!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_74"><![CDATA[Medium coral reef]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_74"><![CDATA[This tropical reef is filled with corals of all colors and sizes! Each animal will find a happy home here.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_75"><![CDATA[Great Coral Reef]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_75"><![CDATA[This coral reef is teeming with life and offers plenty of space for all aquatic animals. Watch them have fun!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_76"><![CDATA[Small Caribbean island]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_76"><![CDATA[Sun and water - the perfect combination. Your animals will love this summer retreat.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_77"><![CDATA[Central Caribbean island]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_77"><![CDATA[Nothing beats walking on the white sand under the shade of palm trees. Your animals are gonna love this island!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_78"><![CDATA[Large caribbean island]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_78"><![CDATA[You won't be able to get your animals off this island! How about packing up and moving too!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_79"><![CDATA[Medium Tiki creek]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_79"><![CDATA[Lie down in a hammock, sip mango juice and enjoy Tiki Bay to the fullest. There is simply no better way to relax!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_80"><![CDATA[Medium expedition tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_80"><![CDATA[Your visitors will be curious to see what you pull out of this tank! Your animals will also enjoy swimming among the machinery.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_81"><![CDATA[Large expedition tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_81"><![CDATA[This tank is so big you could fit the Titanic in it! Your largest animals and fish will also have plenty of room to explore the crevices and cracks.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_82"><![CDATA[Small Tiki creek]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_82"><![CDATA[The vibrant colors and clear water will attract not only different species of fish and animals, but also new visitors!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_83"><![CDATA[Large Tiki creek]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_83"><![CDATA[Relax in a tropical environment, enjoy the tranquility and watch the animals frolic in the water.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_84"><![CDATA[Model railway]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_84"><![CDATA[Your animals are gonna love climbing this train and railway! Don't forget to take your visitors for a ride!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_85"><![CDATA[Spider cave]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_85"><![CDATA[Are you brave enough to step into this dark cave? Don't worry. The spider that lives there is very friendly and just wants to give you a hug.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_86"><![CDATA[North Pole]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_86"><![CDATA[Visit Santa's home at the North Pole! Your animals will have a lot of fun building snowmen and creating snow angels!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_87"><![CDATA[Romantic reservoir]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_87"><![CDATA[Even fish crave love! Place this romantic tank in the Underwater World and make your water creatures happy.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_88"><![CDATA[Temple ruin]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_88"><![CDATA[Head to the tropical rainforest of Cambodia and sit under a tetrameles tree. If you get lucky, you might even spot a sun bear.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_89"><![CDATA[Spring garden]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_89"><![CDATA[Spring is here! Put on your shoes, grab your watering can, it's time to take care of your garden!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.titel_90"><![CDATA[Elegant habitat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopCageInfo.text_90"><![CDATA[Introduce this luxurious habitat to your animals. You'll see how they'll love it!]]></item>
  </category>
</language>
